kids came
chavales venía
[Music]
[Música]
Ok here we go
Ok here we Go
the here perform for you if you know the
the here perform for you if you know the
words you can Jo put your hands together
words you can Jo put your hands Together
if you Clap as we take you through this
if you Clap as we take you through this
monkey
monkey
[Music]
[Música]
rykey
rykey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
He's the leader of the bunch you know
He's the leader of the bunch you know
him well He's Finally back to Kick some
him well He's Finally back to Kick some
ta his Coconut gum can Fire And sps If
ta his Coconut gum can Fire And sps If
he shoots you It's gna hurt He's bigger
he shoots you It's gna hurt He's bigger
faster and stronger too He's the First
faster and stronger too He's the First
member of the dk Crew
member of the dk Crew
dkey
dkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
d Donkey
d Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
here
here
Donkey Donkey Kong
Donkey Donkey Kong
got so Listen up to She can shrink in
got so Listen up to She can shrink in
size to suit her She quick and When She
size to suit her She quick and When She
needs to be She can float through the air
needs to be She can flo through the air
and climb up tre if you choose
and Climb up tre if you choose
her wrong with skip H She's
her wrong with skip H She's
cool
cool
d Donkey
d Donkey
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
[Music]
[Música]
dkey
dkey
Kong Donkey Kong is here he has no Style
Kong Donkey Kong is here he has no Style
he has no
he has no
Grace this Kong has a funny Face he can
Grace this Kong has a funny Face he can
hand when he needs to and stretch his
hand when he needs to and stretch his
Arms out Just for you inflate him
Arms out Just for you inflate him
good
bon
[Music]
[Música]
Crazy Donkey
Crazy Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
Here Donkey
here Donkey
[Music]
[Música]
He's Back Again and about time to and
He's Back Again and about time to and
this
this
[Music]
[Música]
he with his Jetpack G with his pistols
he with his Jetpack G with his pistols
out He's One tough c he'll Make You
out He's One tough c he'll Make You
Smile when he plays to but kremlin
Smile when he Plays to but kremlin
beware cuse he's after
beware cuse He's after
youkey
youkey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
Here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally He's here
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally He's here
for you It's The Last member of the dk
for you It's The Last member of the dk
Crew this K so strong it isn't funny can
Crew this K so strong it isn't funny can
make a klin Cry out for mmy can't pick
make a klin Cry out for mmy can't pick
up a b with relative ease makes crushing
up a b with relative ease makes crushing
Rocks seem such a breeze he May move
Rocks seem such a breeze he May move
Slow he can't jump high but this comes
Slow he can't jump High but this comes
One Hell Of A gu Come on cranky take it
One Hell Of A gu Come on cranky take it
to the fridge
to the fridge
[Music]
[Música]
walnuts peanuts pineapple smells grapes
walnuts peanuts pineapple smells grapes
melons oranges and coconut shell Oh yeah
melons oranges and Coconut shell Oh yeah
walnuts peanuts pineapple smells crepes
walnuts peanuts pineapple smells crepes
Melons, oranges, and coconut
melons oranges and Coconut
[Music]
[Música]
What's happening
Qué pasa
handsome How
guapos Cómo
we are finally finally finished with it
estamos por fin por fin acaban con el
Give it today, eh, that is, today, fixed, fixed, fixed
dala hoy eh o sea hoy fijo fijo fijo
fixed since yes today it is eh This time
fijo ya que sí hoy sí es eh Esta vez
Yes, this time it's going to be the right one.
sí Esta vez sí va a ser la buena
Hey Javi, tell us who's keeping the
eh Javi cuenta ya quién se queda con los
subscribers, what a tremendous divorce yours is
suscriptores tremendo divorcio el de tú
and I'll keep them for myself. Come to me.
y Dalas yo me los quedo yo Venid a mí
Okay
vale
Javi, your sweatshirt disgusts me.
Javi tu sudadera me da asco
Take it off, your father disgusts me more who
quítatela tu padre me da más asco quién
You're the one who posted it, I don't care.
eres el que lo ha puesto me da igual
but I'm sure you have a very good father
pero seguro que tienes un padre muy
disgusting Rena a
asqueroso Rena un
kiss take money so you can dance with me
beso toma dinero para que me bailes
handsome, I've already danced, I've already danced, Javi
guapo ya he bailado ya he bailado Javi
talk about sut 2 why in relation to
habla de la sut 2 por qué a cuento de
Don't go, Lina. Stay with me.
qué Lina no te vayas Quédate conmigo
not tonight
esta noche no
Lina Lina you go there I'm telling you
Lina Lina te vas ahí te lo estoy
I'm asking you to stay guys today
pidiendo yo que te quedes chicos hoy
We have a night to see, I don't know if so
tenemos una noche a ver no sé si tan
long because it is true that the one of
larga porque sí que es verdad que la de
yesterday
ayer
Eh yes it is true that yesterday was
Eh sí que es verdad que la de ayer fue
very long I mean yesterday it was so long
muy larga O sea ayer se me fue tan larga
the night I didn't record the video for the
la noche que no grabé el vídeo para el
main channel which by the way you are
canal principal que por cierto lo estáis
supporting the main channel a lot, let's go
apoyando mucho el canal principal vamos
to try to get it back on track, okay, I mean I know that
a intentar retomarlo vale o sea sé que
to the main channel eh I can't upload a
al Canal principal eh No puedo subir un
video diary I'll try it but it's
vídeo diario lo voy lo intento pero es
impossible I try but it is impossible
imposible lo intento pero es imposible
because man, these are slightly more videos
porque hombre son vídeos un poco más
elaborate elaborate I Alan Good
elaborado elaborado yo Alan Buenas
Javi, I propose chipping with Gibel.
noches Javi propongo el chipeo con gibel
the jabel so that other people who do not
el jabel para que otra gente que no
I want to say his name but it starts with
quiero decir su nombre pero empieza con
r and ends with a the crazy kis burns
r y acaba con a se arda el loquito kis
Freni, I'm taking off the crazy one, the crazy one is here
freni quito el loquito el loquito está
today here too let's see we are not going to
hoy por aquí también a ver no vamos a
see everything that has become good everything
ver todo lo que ha puesto bueno todo lo
that has been put is not that apparently
que ha puesto no es que por lo visto
crazy
loquito
yesterday he continued to do live chatter
ayer continuó haciendo directo patatín
Patatón okay talking about me but it's that
patatón vale hablando de mí pero es que
ra is already one
ra ya es una
person from the team from the team I I it
persona del equipo del equipo yo yo lo
I have asked you to please make me one
he pedido por favor que me hagáis una un
poster and hang it or put it here in
póster y lo cuelgo o lo pongo aquí en
a poster of the team on the screen
pantalla un póster del equipito de
football is worth RAE delox Peppa Loli Huerta
fútbol vale RAE delox Peppa Loli Huerta
Joan Planas, the whole team, the whole team
Joan planas todo el equipito todo el
little team okay I said it yesterday I say Hey
equipito vale Yo lo dije ayer digo Oye
take a picture of myself, not at least for
hacerme una fotito no por lo menos para
so that I feel less
que para que yo me sienta menos
persecuted I think I would feel less
perseguido Creo que me sentiría menos
persecuted if I put a photo here of
perseguido si me pongo aquí una foto de
they big like that while I'm
ellos en grande así mientras que estoy
live looking at the back of my neck that with
en directo mirándome la nuca que que con
the day to day is worth yesterday for example
el día a día vale ayer por ejemplo
when I finished the live Go to the
cuando terminé el directo Vete a la
[ __ ] wizard what are you talking to me for
[__] wizard que me estás hablando por
WhatsApp, why should I take it off?
el WhatsApp para qué que me quite la
sweatshirt that your father takes off
sudadera qué que se la quite tu padre
your father should take it away from her, damn it.
que se la quite tu padre [__] habéis
put the WhatsApp group or what O
puesto el grupo de WhatsApp o qué O
neither or do I have to put it too
tampoco o también lo tengo que poner
Me yesterday when I finished the live
yo ayer cuando terminé el directo
I find that YouTube sends me a
me encuentro con que me manda YouTube un
email you won't believe it You'll believe it if you
email no os lo Vais a creer si os lo
You're going to believe it like you won't believe it. You're going to believe it.
Vais a creer como no os lo Vais a creer
Last night I finished the live show.
ayer por la noche terminé el directo yo
I think it was 3 in the morning
creo que fueron las 3 las 3 de la mañana
or something like that okay eh And I find a
o cosa así vale eh Y me encuentro un
YouTube email
email de YouTube
warning me that Joan Planas was
avisándome de que Joan planas me estaba
trying to take down the game due to copyright
intentando tirar por copyright el game
over Rena a kiss
over Rena un beso
He was trying to throw me in the game
me estaba intentando tirar el el game
over copyright suddenly by the
over por copyright de repente por la
face come chill 5 years later I decide
cara venga chill 5 años después decido
I'll throw it at you, that is, the guy won't rest
que te lo tiro o sea el tío no descansa
not a day in Javi He doesn't rest even a day
ni un día en Javi No descansa ni un día
in
en
Javi reported that a photo from his social networks
Javi reportó que una foto de sus redes
social networks were copyrighted
sociales estaba tenían derechos de autor
because they are photos that he had taken, not
porque son fotos que había hecho él no
Are you going to believe it? He says no, no, let's see.
os lo Vais a creer dice no no a ver yo
I tell you this as an anecdote that is the same
os lo cuento como anécdota que lo mismo
I created it for you and the same. No, but okay, Joan.
os lo creé y lo mismo No pero bueno Joan
5 years later he has decided that he is
5 años después ha decidido que está
Trying to get a strike on the game
intentando Ponerme un strike en el game
over vale This is something we already value
over vale Esto es algo que ya valoramos
At the time I saw it as strange, eh, that he tried
en su día yo lo veo raro eh que intente
put a strike in the good gameover
poner un strike en el gameover bueno
YouTube will be rejected they want to throw you away
YouTube será rechazado te quieren tirar
the Javi channel Don't tell me Fer I haven't
el canal Javi No me digas Fer no me he
realized I haven't realized Well
dado cuenta No me he dado cuenta Bueno
I'm saying goodbye because I think that
yo me voy despidiendo porque creo que
Any day I say it as a joke but
cualquier día lo digo de cachondo pero
Come on, it's real Vero, a kiss I think in
vamos es real Vero un beso creo que en
any day we can meet
cualquier día nos podemos encontrar a
that they have thrown the channel at us whatever
que nos han tirado el canal lo que sea
because because yes because [ __ ] because
porque porque sí porque [__] porque
They are They are trying all the time
están Están todo el tiempo intentando
to sleep with them than to follow me on Twitter
tirárselas que seguirme en Twitter
Instagram follow me everywhere
Instagram seguirme en todas partes que
If they knock this down, I'll be in another one.
si me tumban esto pues estaré en otro
side and that's it, but they are
lado y ya está no pero que están
trying to throw it away they are trying
intentando tirarlo están intentando
throw it away and there will be consequences later or
tirarlo ya luego habrá consecuencias o
no, that would be seen, okay, we have it
no eso ya se vería vale tenemos
raised Good afternoon Javi, it gave me
planteado Buenas tardes Javi a mí me dio
courage to enter x and see all that is
coraje entrar a x y ver todos los que se
They are happy about the Dallas sentence haha
alegran de la sentencia del Dallas jaj
face crying loudly Well look at Larz that
cara llorando fuerte Pues mira larz que
He's going to be busy with something that was going to happen to him
va a estar liado con una cosa le iba a
ask Larz to leave
pedir a larz que me que me fuera
sending Who have rejoiced and who
mandando Quiénes han alegrado y quiénes
no more or less to comment on it Well I
no más o menos para comentarlo Bueno yo
I have been preparing something while
me he ido preparando algo mientras que
We had the music, eh? But well, well, yes.
teníamos la música eh Pero bueno Pues si
If someone passes us by, let's go
se nos pasa alguien vamos a ir
comment on it to see the Dallas Bueno topic
comentarlo a ver el tema de Dallas Bueno
Let's finish with Joan and you
vamos a terminar con lo de Joan y os
I say what Dalan said, eh, I say it publicly.
digo lo de dalan eh lo digo públicamente
just like I said on telesalseo eh
igual que lo he dicho en telesalseo eh
I obviously don't think it's very
yo evidentemente no creo que sea muy
lawful is worth very legitimate that you throw away
lícito vale muy legítimo que que tires
a copyright video when you are
un vídeo por copyright cuando a ti se te
Joan said a year and a half ago that
ha dicho hace un año y medio Joan que
what we had to do so that we
qué teníamos que hacer para que nos
we left both in bread, he didn't mention us
dejáramos los dos en pan no nos mencioná
nothing in life erases each one's own
nada en la vida borrar cada uno lo suyo
and each one has his own life and you said no
y cada uno su vida y tú dijiste que no
that you wanted to throw the channels at me. Okay.
que tú querías tirarme los canales Vale
then you are trying to throw
entonces que tú estés intentando tirar
a video fraudulently to throw me
un vídeo fraudulentamente para tirarme
the channels and when you have been told
los canales e cuando a ti se te ha dicho
that video if it burns you a lot it will burn you
que ese vídeo si te arde mucho se te
take it away, it's a little bit, you, you, you know, you
quita ya es un poco tú tú tú sabrás tú
continue you will know you continue But well the
sigue tú sabrás tú sigue Pero bueno la
each one with his own, each one with his own
cada uno con lo suyo cada uno con sus
things in life and his and his moves are worth it
cosas de la vida y su y sus movidas vale
But man, I don't see it, I don't see it.
pero hombre yo no lo veo yo no lo veo
Ok, but what do you want wizard?
vale Pero bueno qué quieres wizard que
tell him
le diga
flat what do you want me to tell you flat what
planas qué quieren que le diga plana qué
you burn a lot
te ardes mucho
No no, don't screw me up, don't screw me up
No no que me la liis no que me la liis
Well, the issue of Dallas is several
bueno el tema de lo de Dallas son varias
things we have to comment on
cosas las que tenemos que comentar del
Dallas eh be today but it's that you are
Dallas eh sea hoy pero es que estas
Things that amaze me and sadden me
cosas a mí me maravillan y me dan penas
at the same time because it's like it's not that anymore
a la vez porque es como que ya no es que
celebrate a
celebren un
kiss celebrate because I see it as logical
beso celebren porque yo veo lógico
even the donkey Look over there at the donkey
incluso al asne Mira por ahí al asne ha
put the WhatsApp group for which
puesto el grupo de WhatsApp para el que
don't be inside let it come in Look over there
no esté dentro que entre Mira por ahí lo
is putting lasne okay I still see
está poniendo lasne vale Yo todavía veo
logical okay I see logical and normal that that
lógico vale veo lógico y normal que que
When you win a lawsuit, celebrate it
cuando tú ganes una demanda la celebres
It was just missing no, that is, it is absurd to think
solo faltaba no o sea es absurdo pensar
the opposite but not when you win one
lo contrario pero no cuando tú ganas una
demands that you celebrate it Wait for it
demanda que tú la celebres Espérate que
I'm seeing that the black background here
estoy viendo que el fondo negro de aquí
but all the people who like you
sino que toda la gente a la que le caes
good
bien
celebrate and rejoice for you Don't wait
celebren y se alegren por ti No espérate
a moment the black background
un momento el fondo negro
dude, it's completely logical that
tío o sea es completamente lógico que
that you rejoice and celebrate a lawsuit
que tú te alegres Y celebres una demanda
that you have put you have spent money on
que has puesto te has gastar dinero en
put it okay And it is completely logical
ponerla vale Y es completamente lógico
illicit that the people to whom
ilícito que que las personas a las que
They like you, they are happy that you win one
le caes bien se alegren de que ganes una
Sue because you have suffered a lot. Not me.
demanda porque has sufrido mucho No a mí
What seems a little special to me is already
lo que me parece un poco especial ya es
about the thing about them being happy But no
lo de lo de que que se alegren Pero no
not because of you but because they hate each other but
por ti sino porque odien al otro pero
Well on the internet there is all this type of
bueno en internet hay todo este tipo de
people and each one is part of their team
personas y y cada uno es de su equipo
There are some of us who are on one side and another
Hay unos que estamos en un lado y otro
that we are in the other I am in the
que estamos en el otro yo estoy en el
another me is that on this occasion I am in
otro yo es que en esta ocasión estoy en
the other one is fine, I don't like them
el otro vale a mí no me gustan los
sides eh And the stories eh of Seville
bandos eh Y las historias eh de Sevilla
beti Madrid Barca and these things don't affect me
beti Madrid Barca y estas cosas a mí no
I like it but well they have divided
me gusta pero bueno ellos han dividido
They have divided there are some issues
ellos han dividido hay unas cuestiones
that there are some issues that when they happen
que hay unas cuestiones que cuando pasan
to one side They are very strong and they are very
a un lado Son muy fuertes y son muy
serious but if they pass to the other side they are not
graves pero si pasan al otro lado no son
so serious to me, for example, what I
tan graves a mí por ejemplo lo que me
It is surprising that this is celebrated more or
sorprende Es que esto se celebre más o
because it causes more indignation in some
porque causa más indignación unos
insults that you have made to a
insultos que daras le haya hecho a una
family with which a gentleman does not with him
familia con la que a un señor no con el
that has problem Not to me what I
que tiene problema No a mí lo que me
It is surprising that this is outrageous that it is a
sorprende Es que esto indigne que es una
sentence for taking away his
sentencia por quitarle a su
dog type this ra or rather I have
perro tipo este ra o sea yo me he
I have been informed about the sentence
enterado por ra de lo de la sentencia yo
I have learned about the sentence
me he enterado por ra de la sentencia
Okay, here you go, Javi Oliveira.
vale toma Javi oliveira aquí tienes
content so you don't have to react to
contenido así no tienes que reaccionar a
my Stream
mis Stream
faa.org I know about this
faa.org yo lo de este
guy telling me about the news and
tipo avisándome de la noticia y
passing me the link of
pasándome el enlace de
faa.org I can't, I can't take it anymore
faa.org yo no puedo yo no puedo más
Tomorrow who am I going to wake up with?
mañana con quén me voy a despertar el
another day I woke up with a mature
otro día me desperté con un de maduro
throwing myself
tirándome
[ __ ] or whatever Well look I have you
[__] o sea Pues mira yo te he
answered RAE condemns pioneering sentence
contestado RAE condena pionera condena
pioneer for me is that of David Bravo
pionera a mí es que lo de David Bravo
putting all his sentences condemn
poniéndole a todas sus sentencias conden
All the sentences are pioneers, eh, that is.
todas las condenas son pioneras eh o sea
all all all are pioneers And as
todas todas todas son pioneras Y como
why Or why Why are you going to For
por qué O sea por qué Por qué Vas a Por
What do you say to your friend from Faaca who
qué le dices a tu amigo el de faaca que
It's not a medium, it's just that I don't use the knife.
no es un medio es que yo lo de faca no
I understand, I'm sure I'm completely
lo entiendo seguro estoy completamente
convinced that it has to exist here
convencido de que tiene que existir aquí
some kind of irregularity in using
algún tipo de irregularidad por utilizar
This page is funded by
la página Esta que está financiada con
public money not this association is
dinero público no esta asociación está
subsidized Okay and you
subvencionada Vale y que tú
take a kiss Christopher good the
cojas un beso Christopher bueno los
Spanish media not only faca
medios de España no solamente faca
wait here
espérate por aquí lo
I have the newspaper.es
tengo el diario.es
from the supreme school gymnasium
de de gimnasio escolar el supremo
confirms the newspaper
confirma el diario
public face and this that neither
público faca y esto que que ni
idea Hi Javi eler is so happy but
idea Hola Javi eler está tan feliz pero
He has a similar claim for insult
él tiene una demanda igual por insulto
Who Ah a no laser has two and it goes
quién Ah una no láser tiene dos y le va
to arrive the third as soon as I have
a llegar la tercera en cuanto yo tenga
a little time and a little more
un poco de tiempo y un poco más de
money in the box m Yes but what is it
dinero en la caja m Sí pero que es
absurd or so that's what I'm telling you
absurdo o sea es lo que te digo
mm let's see I understand that each one
mm vamos a ver yo entiendo que cada uno
If you consider this a point for
Si considera que esto es un punto para
your side, your team, so celebrate now
su bando su equipo pues lo celebre ahora
good
bien
with here there are several things No
con aquí hay varias cosas No
Obviously, you cannot insult
evidentemente pues tú no puedes insultar
to people publicly to me 12000
a las personas públicamente a mí 12000
turkeys seems like a real outrage to me
pavos me parece una verdadera barbaridad
eh, I mean comparing it with all the
eh o sea comparándolo con todas las
sentences that exist regarding the right to honor
sentencias que hay de derecho al honor
because there are many even if they say you are
porque hay muchas aunque digan que estás
Pioneer is worth 12,000 to me, of course, because
pionera vale a mí 12000 claro es que por
for the insults are
por el por los insultos son
6000 of course what is an outrage is
6000 claro lo que es una barbaridad es
for the photo 6000 eh For me the thing about the
por lo de la foto 6000 eh A mí lo de la
The photo seems to me to be an outrage in the
foto me parece una barbaridad en el
sense that he is a person who
sentido de que de que es una persona que
has taken photos on social networks
se ha hecho fotos en las redes sociales
on the web pages of I don't know if in
en las páginas web de de yo no sé si en
her daughter's Instagram but in the
el Instagram de su hija pero en el
Dallas's Instagram on Instagram
Instagram de Dallas en el Instagram de
his wife is also public
su mujer no que también es pública
So I'm going to give you a photo.
entonces a mí que por una foto por tú
If you post a photo, they'll charge you 6000. But oh well.
poner la foto te metan 6000 Pero bueno
I respect what justice says and
yo lo que diga la justicia lo respeto y
I serve the sentences, that is, me
yo cumplo las sentenci eh o sea a mí
When I'm sentenced to something, hey Javi.
cuando me condenan a algo Oye Javi
You have to pay this. Hey Javi, you have to
tienes que pagar esto Oye Javi tienes
that returning this I will fulfill them
que devolver esto yo las cumplo la
sentence is what this side has
sentencia es lo que tiene este bando
Okay then, well, about the
Vale entonces eh bueno lo de los
insults the 6000 bucks for the insults
insultos los 6000 pavos por los insultos
it
lo
I understand that it could be because of the
entiendo entiendo que puede ser por la
I understand that it will be due to diffusion, not because
entiendo que será por la difusión no por
because of the great impact it has
la por la gran repercusión que tiene
Dallas which may not be the same as
Dallas que a lo mejor no es la misma que
the one we can have more youtubers
la que podemos tener youtubers más
small as like the others no but it
pequeños como como los demás no pero lo
of the
de la
image 6000 bucks for posting a photo that
imagen 6000 pavos por poner una foto que
It's already uploaded, no, that's it, no, no, such, but
ya está subida no eso no no tal Pero
Well, whatever the law says, I'll do it now.
bueno lo que diga la ley yo lo tal ahora
well condemns pioneer condemns I am that
bien condena pionera condena Yo es que
the lawyer going to friends to
lo de la abogado yendo a los amigos a
ask him please Put me Put me well Put me
pedirle por favor Ponme ponme bien Ponme
very powerful not there in Get me well
bien potente no ahí en Ponme bien
powerful in your newspaper not there that says
potente en tu periódico no ahí que diga
people Wow you know pioneering conviction of
la gente Wow sabes condena pionera de
What? So what is pioneering? How many?
qué O sea qué tiene de pionero Cuántas
There are sentences on the right to honor
sentencias de derecho al honor hay de
people by programs in which they are the
gente por programas en que son las
convictions of the right to honor are always
condenas de derecho al honor siempre son
Because you defamed someone
por Porque tú difam a alguien
publicly or on networks there are none
públicamente o en redes no las hay por
Facebook has them, Twitter is fine, Albert.
Facebook las hay por Twitter vale Albert
Rivera won a lawsuit because a
Rivera con ganó una demanda porque un
Random twitterer told him cocaine addict okay
twittero Random le dijo cocainómano vale
There are 2000 turkeys for programs
2000 pavos las hay por programas de
There are radios from YouTubers, there is already one
radio las hay de youtubers ya hay un
a lot of procedures or what do you have
montón de Procedimientos O sea qué tiene
this condemnation
esto de condena
pioneer They are all pioneers
pionera Es que todas todas son pioneras
All of David Bravo's convictions
todas las condenas de David Bravo Yo
I think that, well, look at the pioneering conviction in
creo que pues mira condena pionera en
this case because it is
este caso porque es
Dasas had no other choice, for insult was not
a dasas no tenía otra por insulto no fue
this same one not
esta misma no
Mine was there, Nauter's was not there with
estuvo la mía no estuvo la de nauter con
wismichu who also belonged to this lawyer
wismichu que también fue de este abogado
and she was also a pioneer, eh, she was also
y también fue pionera eh también fue
pioneer and but I don't understand why
pionera e pero es que no entiendo por
What is always a pioneer is no longer a problem
qué siempre es pionero no da ya cosilla
I don't understand The Pioneers But
Es que no entiendo Los Pioneros Pero
Well, that is, from save me from TV from a
bueno o sea de sálvame de la tele de un
a lot is worth it
montón vale
In this procedure the following applies:
em este procedimiento vale del que r
wants me to talk, well, if you want
quiere que hable pues si queréis
We talked about it really in depth, no.
hablamos Yo realmente en profundidad no
I can enter the subject because my opinion
puedo entrar el tema porque mi opinión
I really prefer to reserve it, it's worth it. I'll do it.
real prefiero reservá mela vale Yo lo
What can I tell you in short?
que os puedo decir en resumidas cuentas
and conclusion How good that you eh For more
y conclusión Que bueno que tú eh Por más
that you feel it is worth it And as much as you
que lo sientas vale Y por mucho que tú
you think one thing about a person and not such
pienses una cosa de una persona y tal no
You can't do it. Not everything you want.
lo puedes no No todo lo que tú quieres
You can verbalize it, okay, that is, you don't
lo puedes verbalizar vale o sea tú no
you can because it tarnishes the image of a
puedes porque mancha la imagen de una
person and then they ask you for money okay
persona y entonces te piden dinero vale
This is not a penalty okay This is not a
Esto no es una penal vale Esto no es una
penalty for slander or anything like that
penal por calumnia ni nada por el estilo
as I saw around here that it was
como he visto por ahí que estaba
saying some V this is a right to
diciendo alguno V esto es un derecho al
Honor is worth the expressions Okay for
honor vale por las expresiones Okay por
the expressions and by and by the image
las expresiones y por y por la imagen
I understand, okay, what do you think?
entiendo vale la movida mm a mí qué te
I say how do I tell you this, let's see what this is
digo cómo te digo yo esto a ver que esto
It was already discussed last year, okay, so now
ya se habló el año pasado vale o sea ya
This has been talked about twice and here
se ha hablado dos veces de esto y aquí
What happens is the following:
lo que pasa es lo siguiente la el
Supreme Court here in Spain I don't know
tribunal supremo aquí en España yo no sé
whether it will work the same in other countries or not
si en otros países funcionará igual o no
Ok, but it is not another instance as such.
vale pero no es como tal otra instancia
directly valid
vale directamente
and another instance as such where they review
e Otra instancia como tal donde revisan
all your case is valid or where
todo todo tu caso vale o sea donde
They review all the tests again.
repasan otra vez todas las pruebas todo
your case and such is the provincial court
tu caso y tal es la audiencia provincial
That is another instance, the court.
Eso sí es otra instancia el tribunal
supreme
supremo
and you appeal, you make the appeal and
e tú recurres tú haces el recurso y
several things can happen with the resource
pueden pasar varias cosas el recurso te
they have to
lo tienen que
admit And if they admit your appeal
admitir Y si te admiten el recurso
Then they assess whether you are right or
Entonces ya valoran si tienes la razón o
The other one has it, okay or I didn't admit Telo
la tiene el otro vale o no admití Telo
directly because it cannot be appealed
directamente porque no se puede recurrir
What has happened here is better and that is why
más vale aquí lo que ha pasado y por eso
It has come out again so quickly that
ha vuelto a salir tan rápido es que
Dallas files an appeal I don't
Dallas presenta un recurso yo no lo
He knew he put it there in his day that he was going to
sabía él lo puso en su día que iba a
put a resource I do not Let's see it is
poner un recurso Yo es que no A ver es
that after the hearing
que ya después de la audiencia
provincial to appeal again to the Supreme Court
provincial recurrir otra vez al supremo
It has no cassation interest, you understand?
no tiene interés casacional me entiendes
Then you will not see your decision of the
Entonces no verás tú decisión del
lawyer and his decision Okay then
abogado y decisión de él Okay entonces
What has happened here is not that now the
aquí lo que ha pasado no es que ahora el
Supreme Court makes another ruling except for
supremo haga otra sentencia sino por lo
What I understand is that the Supreme Court does not
que yo entiendo es que el supremo no
admits the appeal therefore does not
admite el recurso por lo tanto no lo
value worth And
valoran vale Y
then the sentence becomes final
entonces la sentencia que se hace firmen
It is the provincial court. Okay.
es la de la la audiencia provincial Okay
And what does Dala have to pay? Well, 12,000
e qué tiene que pagar dala pues 12000
turkeys worth it, I paid him 12,000 turkeys and that's it
pavos vale le pagado 12000 pavos y y ya
He is here and I have paid him 12,000 bucks and
está y le he pagado 12000 pavos y y
Well, you have to put it in four videos.
bueno tiene que poner en cuatro vídeos
you have to put in four video in
tiene que poner en cuatro vídeo en
any time in the video the sentence
cualquier momento del vídeo la sentencia
reading it is not worth it, for example I have seen
leerla no vale que por ejemplo he visto
to people who were saying that the
a gente que estaba diciendo de que la
had to read it doesn't have to read it or
tenía que leer no la tiene que leer o
for example, you can put the fault
sea por ejemplo é puede poner el fallo
When you finish a video, put one on
cuando termine un vídeo pues pone una
photo of the failure and out you understand me
foto del fallo y y fuera me entiendes
So well, I personally
Entonces bueno Yo es que personalmente
Yes, well yes, yes, I will see you that yes
si Bueno si a la si yo verás tú que si
the family and myare and others are in
la familia y miare y demás están en
happy not with this and and and and and and
contentos no con esto y y y le y le
It is a relief for them
supone una tranquilidad para ellos no
after everything that has happened and this
después de todo lo que ha pasado y esto
It pays to get into this for a long time
les compensa meterse en esto durante
so many years and that are compensated
tantos años y y que se ven compensados
not with all that this entails well
no con todo lo que esto conlleva bueno
everyone is happy with their things No
cada uno es feliz con con sus cosas No
What I answered RAE when I was asked
yo lo que le contestaba RAE cuando me ha
That said, it has been clear. It is that
dicho esto ha sido Pues claro Es que
We already talked about this last year, that
esto ya lo hablamos el año pasado es que
whatever has already been done is
sea lo que lo que se ha hecho ya es
confirm the same sentence that has already been
firme la sentencia misma de la que ya se
speak
habló
So for me personally there are others
entonces para mí personalmente hay otras
You know stronger things than this. I mean
cosas más fuertes que esta sabes O sea
to catch in a video and go to catch
que [__] en un vídeo e irte a [__]
Well, pick a channel and go, it takes you
bueno cogerte un canal e irte te coge
all the expressions that are negative
todas las expresiones que haya negativa
about you in a conflict no eh Well it
sobre ti en un conflicto no eh Bueno lo
made wismichu with nauter here my super
hizo wismichu con nauter aquí mi super
pioneer chat abu as if that result
chat pionero abu como si ese resultado
were to change something or convince
fuera a cambiar algo o convencer a
someone to turn their support to the
alguien de volcar su apoyo a los
Dallas haters, check these out.
odiadores de Dallas a ver estos los los
Today they celebrate the same old things more or less
celebran hoy lo los de siempre más o
except the same side that would celebrate
menos el mismo bando que celebraría
Well, and yes, yes, yes, the sentence, the the
bueno Y si si si la sentencia la la
the other people would have lost because
hubiera perdido la otra gente pues
he would just shut up and that is to say that
simplemente se callaría y o sea es que
It doesn't make sense because you are doing this
no tiene sentido porque esto lo estás
celebrating for example raet
celebrando por ejemplo raet
Raet colleague, you could do it every day
raet colega tú todos los días podrías
have a sentence like this every day
tener una condena como esta todos los
every day
días todos los días
RAE that you for the moment for the moment eh RAE
RAE que tú de momento de momento eh RAE
that you have paid 7000 for now
que tú de momento has pagado 7000 para
that they let you out of jail
que te dejen salir de la cárcel de
bail for the moment Hello tasty old man and
fianza de momento Hola viejo sabroso y
Now what happens with him?
ahora qué pasa con el
Dallas the Dallas I think it is now
Dallas el Dallas yo creo que está ahora
same
mismo
So chill then nothing then he will pay and in
así chill pues nada pues lo pagará y en
four videos
cuatro vídeos
until you have to run it
durante cuando ya lo tenga que ejecutar
Well, it will put or rather will comply with the
pues pondrá o sea cumplirá con la
sentence I understand that he will pay the 12,000
sentencia Entiendo pues pagará los 12000
turkeys and that's it for me what he would give me
pavos y y ya está a mí lo que me daría
It would be very angry that
mucha rabia sería que
and man that he fulfills the sentence and the
e hombre que él cumpla la sentencia y la
other people have not served their sentence
otra gente no haya cumplido la sentencia
that said no the no the penalty that the penalty
que decía no la no la penal que la penal
They are appealing it again and it will be
la están recurriendo otra vez y estará a
about to leave also but the civil
a punto de salir también sino la civil
No, I mean, at one time there was one
no O sea ya en su momento hubo una
civil judgment that told you that you had
sentencia civil que te decía que tenías
to return the
que devolver el
dog So I have people Wow
perro Entonces yo que haya gente Wow
Dallas lost because it insulted
Dallas ha perdido porque ha insultado
man, let me see
hombre a ver yo
What am I telling you, you don't have to insult
m que te digo no hay que insultar
family is worth it. No need to insult.
familia vale No hay que insultar
obviously but I see there
evidentemente pero yo es que yo veo hay
other things that are worse are worth it to me
otras cosas que son peores vale para mi
taste okay but well let it come to you
gusto vale Pero bueno que que te venga
raet or raed could have a conviction
raet o sea raed Podría tener una condena
Every day the first thing is that RAE
de esta Cada día lo primero es que RAE
You could get a fine because these are
Podría tener una multa Porque estos son
fines this is civil okay This is not
multas esto es civil vale Esto no es
penalty they have not gone for the penalty I good
penal no han ido por lo penal yo bueno
I don't know if they were criminal cases.
es que no sé si fueron por lo penal
First and I don't know that, I don't know, okay?
primero y no seo eso no lo sé vale
I would swear they went for the criminal court first
juraría que fueron por lo penal primero
eh I would swear but I don't know
eh juraría pero es que no lo no no lo sé
because this is that this already has so many
porque esto es que esto ya tiene tantos
years and that these people live in that year
años y que esta gente vivan en ese año
they still live in that year still
todavía es que viven en ese año todavía
literally to see if now yes Now
literalmente para ver si ahora sí Ahora
Yes It's finally the end of Dallas Now
sí Por fin es el final de Dallas Ahora
Yes, finally people will believe that
sí por fin la gente va a creer que
we have told the truth once
nosotros hemos dicho la verdad una
conviction for insult and for the
condena por insulto y por las
expressions that imply that they are
expresiones que conlleva que son
important expressions are worth it
expresiones importantes vale
em It's that you look for the video I know
em Es que es que busca tú el vídeo Yo sé
that a few years ago I spoke about a
que yo hace unos años hablé de una
complaint like that but it is
denuncia así pero es
that Miar's parents have reported to
que los padres de miar han denunciado a
Dallas again 5 years ago okay What
Dallas de nuevo hace 5 años vale Qué
pass my
pasa mi
Kid, let's see the explanation that the
chaval vamos a ver explicación que d la
here is that it lasts 21 minutes and over here
aquí es que dura 21 minutos y por aquí
I have to look for it, okay, but I
lo lo tengo que buscar vale pero yo
I would swear that they first put one on him
juraría que primero le pusieron una
criminal complaint And then later as
denuncia penal Y entonces ya luego como
It didn't work, it was civil, but I didn't
no funcionó fue la civil pero no me
Pay close attention because I haven't
hagáis mucho caso porque no me lo he
prepared is that no I can't find it eh
preparado es que no no lo encuentro eh
the thing is
es que
Uncle, I witnessed those [ __ ], that is to say,
tío fui testigo de esas [__] o sea le
They are trying to sue for slander
están intentando denunciar por calumnias
I don't know if you understand the concept of
no sé si entendéis el concepto de
slander but I'm going to explain it to you one or
calumnia pero os lo voy a explicar una o
I understand that they first put one
sea entiendo que primero pusieron una
penalty It's that that sounds familiar to me
penal Es que a mí me quiere sonar eso
Hey, I'm freaking out knowing the amount of
eh yo me flipar saber la cantidad de
pasta that will carry this
pasta que llevarán esta
people on trial uncle in suing everyone
gente en juicio tío en demandar a todo
the world That is to say the media reason not the
el mundo O sea la razón mediática no la
are going to have, so I understand that if you
van a tener o sea yo entiendo que si tú
you feel That is, when you feel
sientes O sea cuando tú te sientes
offended we all have the right to
ofendido todos tenemos el derecho de
go to the law, that is, I do it and I do it
acudir a la ley o sea yo lo hago y lo
I will continue doing it but with people
seguiré haciendo vale pero con personas
Since you say that, uncle, there is no way.
ya que dices tú tío es que no hay manera
It's that it doesn't stop It's that this but already for
es que no para Es que esto pero ya por
for trying to make it the opinion
por intentar qué O sea la la opinión
public and media and all those who
pública y mediática y todos los que
They lived through things, that is. Well, yes, well, the
vivieron las cosas o sea Pues sí pues la
They have been convicted for insulting in the middle
han condenado por por insultar en medio
of that conflict, well, yes ...
de ese conflicto pues se Pues sí pues se
I should have expressed it differently
tenía que haber expresado de otra manera
you know but well getting back to the case it is
sabes pero bueno volviendo al caso es
I would like to know, man, I'm going tomorrow.
que me gustaría saber tío mañana lo voy
to ask tomorrow tomorrow I will
a preguntar mañana mañana lo voy a
ask what exactly I have to
preguntar que precisamente tengo que
talk to my lawyer who also believes
hablar con mi abogado que Además creo
who was the one who took it
que fue el que lo llevó
that I would swear there was an attempt to
que yo juraría que hubo un intento de
criminal complaint first no no me
denuncia por lo penal primero no no me
Pay attention, well, it doesn't matter if the civil has
hagáis caso bueno da igual la civil han
won the civil war is worth it eh For me
ganado la civil vale eh Para mí
Personally, there are many other people who
personalmente hay otra mucha gente que
does things infinitely worse than
hace cosas infinitamente peores que
insulting is worth insulting I think so
insultar vale insultar yo creo que lo
We have done 80% of the work on the Internet
hemos hecho en internet el 80% de los
that we are here is not to justify it
que estamos aquí no es por justificarlo
eh You don't have to do it because if you
eh No hay que hacerlo porque si tú
you are in bad shape we have already seen that you
tienes mala forma ya hemos visto que te
They condemn no uncle, they condemned the nauter
condenan no tío al nauter lo condenaron
because he said "bastard monger"
porque dijo cabronazo monger
and my little [ __ ] I think it was. So it is
e mi putita creo que fue O sea que es
like What That's why I tell you that
como What Por eso te digo que lo de
pioneer
pionera
Well, pioneer, it depends, grandpa, and when you
bueno pionera depende abuelo y cuando tu
I already got the sentence for being so sexy
sentencia por ser tan sexy ya la tengo
to fulfill every day and the truth is that
que cumplir cada día y la verdad es que
It's something that weighs on me, eh, it weighs on me, it weighs on me
es algo que me pesa eh Me pesa me pesa
But I'll do it, man, what I was getting at, huh?
Pero lo cumplo que tío a lo que iba eh
let Raed come and celebrate this
que venga raed a celebrar esto
raet you are literally right now
raet literalmente estás ahora mismo
out of jail you are literally
fuera de la cárcel literalmente estás
right now out of jail for a
ahora mismo fuera de la cárcel por una
bail of
fianza de
7000 is literally out of the
7000 literalmente está fuera de la
jail right now for a sentence Oops
cárcel ahora mismo por una sentencia Uy
for a sentence for a bail of
por una sentencia por una fianza de
7000 for threatening to kill a woman
7000 por amenazar de muerte a una
person and not that but you could
persona y no eso sino que tú podías
have a conviction of
tener una condena de
This Every
esta Cada
day I have already received the demand for you that you
día Ya te llegó la demando a ti que te
They promised a year ago, Javi, what's up?
prometieron hace un año Javi qué va
I'll play and look at that [ __ ] Look at that already
tocaré y mira que [__] Mira que ya me
They have located it, imo, but no, no, no, no
tienen localizad imo eh pero no no no no
Come on, you haven't even touched me, eh?
que va no me has llegado a tocar eh
you give that man a little tap
pegarle tú un toquecito a ese hombre que
Aha that man celebrates I no no good in
Aha ese hombre celebra yo no no bueno en
I'm not going to talk about that man, I don't
fin no voy a hablar de ese hombre no me
Don't poke me. But hey, RAE, you
no me pinches Pero bueno RAE que tú
you could have this
podrías tener esta
that you could have this sentence
que tú podrías tener esta esta condena
You could have it every day with your
la podrías tener tú cada día con tus
Stream that you're out of jail
Stream que estás fuera de la cárcel
7000 bucks trust And you're
confianza de 7000 pavos Y estás
waiting for you
pendiente de que te
judge that you have a warrant
juzguen que tienes una orden de
RAE distancing because you threatened to
alejamiento RAE porque amenazaste de
death to that person to serene or that is
muerte a esa persona a sereno o sea
Then you come to me with this
entonces que me vengas tú con esta
story that we already commented on in the
historia que ya la comentamos en el
channel I think this was in fact
canal yo creo que esto fue de hecho
exclusive to me or so if the worst is
exclusiva mía o sea si es que lo peor es
They say no, the dog is not going to comment.
que dicen no el perro no va a comentar
this but if this was exclusive to me or
esto pero si esto fue exclusiva mía o
be this I took it out before the
sea esto lo saqué yo antes que los
media This was exclusive to me to find it
medios Esto fue exclusiva mía buscarlo
This was exclusive to me what do I do to
Esto fue exclusiva mía qué le hago al
Dallas because he has insulted ea ea ea
Dallas porque ha insultado ea ea ea
Dallas [ __ ] That others don't insult
Dallas [__] Que los otros no insultan
never for the more that the lady was
nunca por la más que la señora estaba
Today I don't know if I have it open here.
hoy Yo no sé si tengo aquí abierto si
open but Karime sent it to me
abierto pero me lo mandó Karime la
lady was here today
señora estaba hoy
like imitating my accent like a churra
como como imitando mi acento como churra
I don't know what I don't know how ma'am already ma'am already
no sé qué no sé como señora ya señora ya
Yeah, yeah, yeah, ma'am, 2025 Antonia
ya ya ya señora ya 2025 Antonia
2025 well and I have here a folder of
2025 bueno y tengo aquí una carpeta de
insults that he has been throwing at me every day
insultos que lleva haciéndome Cada día
that's good we'll see but of course it's
que bueno veremos a ver pero claro Es
What do I do? I'm going to get into a fight.
que qué me hago me meto en un pleito
To sue this lady and hit me 6
Para demandar a esta señora y me pego 6
years with that lady Knowing about her
años con esa señora Sabiendo de ella
again It's that I think the same Yes
otra vez Es que creo que lo mismo Sí
because of course I think these people are
porque claro creo que esta gente son
for life is what these people are
para toda la vida es que esta gente son
for all the
para toda la
Life, trust in you, we already discussed this.
vida fíate Tú esto esto ya lo comentamos
makes a
hace un
We already discussed this a year ago
año esto ya lo comentamos hace un año
raed do you want them to comment and comment
raed quieres que lo Comenten y comente
also the breakup of J pel red and r in
también la ruptura de J pel rojo y r en
the
la
Total network that I put to
red Total que le pongo a
RAE is that they are wanting to eat a ratio
RAE es que son ganas de comerte un ratio
every time you talk and hit me with a sasc
cada vez que hable y pegarte un sasc
case in the mouth Oh no Dallas has
caso en la boca Oh no Dallas ha
insulted someone Thank goodness that the
insultado a alguien Menos mal que la
Justice puts him in his place now yes
justicia lo pone en su sitio ahora sí
Yes, thanks for letting us know tonight.
que sí gracias por avisar ra esta noche
I will comment on it after acknowledging that
lo comentaré después de reconocer que
I parked in the second row the other day because
aparqué en segunda fila el otro día por
more healthy and exemplary people like you in
más gente sanita y ejemplar como tú en
internet dude literally yesterday the cani
internet tío literalmente ayer la cani
tiller that I don't know who it will be the truth no
tiller que no sé quién será la verdad no
I have no idea what cani tiller was like.
tengo ni idea la cani tiller estaba jav
oliveira is a
oliveira es un
offender taking a photo of me from when
infractor sacando una foto mía de cuando
I went to that demonstration in Malaga
fui a la manifestación esa de Málaga
because he put the car in the second row
porque puso el coche en segunda fila
to greet the
para saludar la
dude, there are people here breaking the law
peña tío hay gente aquí incumpliendo
civil sentence there are people here who are
sentencia civiles hay gente aquí que hay
misappropriation there are convictions of
apropiación indebida hay condenas de
document forgery eh a guy who
falsificación documental eh un tipo que
has a bail for death threats
tiene una fianza por amenaza de muerte
Hello tripe, how's it going? I just
Hola mondongo cómo va eso Acabo de
arrive what has happened sign of closure of
llegar qué ha pasado signo de cierre de
interrogation kiss a kiss Well, nothing
interrogación beso un beso Pues nada
Here we are commenting on the end of Dallas
aquí estamos comentando el fin de Dallas
I mean
o sea
literally okay it's okay that it
literalmente vale está bien que lo
celebrate the other part But you who are you
celebre la otra parte Pero tú que tú
sell this like a [ __ ] dick, that is, me
vendas esto como la [__] [__] o sea yo
I understand that the other party celebrates it
entiendo que de la otra parte lo celebre
because in the end it has been spent they have one
porque al final se ha gastado llevan una
p has been spent on trial since the year
p está gastada en juicio desde el año
2016 so far and yes, hey, they're going to win.
2016 hasta ahora y si Oye van a ganar
something now not Well look
algo ahora no Pues mira
you know but
sabes pero
you
tú
you, you are a stalker RAE and it comes to me
tú tú eres un acosador RAE y me viene
after this
después de este
ratio with
ratio con
This is what made me this little drawing
esto me ha hecho este dibujito
I have put to you don't get salty love yourself a
le he puesto a ti no te sal quiérete un
you know little about what he has done
poquito sabéis lo que ha hecho el
Crazy people telling him but man eh
loquito la gente diciéndole pero tío eh
that you start harassing neighbors
que tú te pones a acosar vecinas
taking pictures of the girls in
haciéndole fotos a a las chicas en
bikini you know what she has done
bikini sabéis lo que ha hecho la
creature like me I have not paid attention to
criatura como yo no le he hecho caso al
I draw and I told him, "Man, love yourself a little."
dibujo y le he dicho tío quiérete un
little has gone and has it and has put it on
poco ha ido y se lo ha y se lo ha puesto
to
a
Delox, uncle, is literally a crazy guy there.
delox tío literalmente es un loquito ahí
He went and put the drawing on
eh ha ido y le ha puesto el dibujito a
to see if Delos would say, oh what?
delos para ver si delos le decía ay qué
It's true that Javi hasn't told me that he is
bien que Javi No me ha dicho que está
very good drawing and since you don't know what you are
muy bien el dibujo y ya que no que eres
fool Well now we'll see what DEA people
tonto Bueno ahora veremos lo DEA gente
by the goddess it was the Dallas yes it is
por la diosa era el Dallas sí que es
horrible No no how can you insult How
horrible No no cómo puede insultar Cómo
that is possible
eso es posible
I no longer have faith in humanity.
ya no tengo fe en la humanidad ya tengo
traumas that is wrong is that with those
traumas que está mal es que con esas
expressions you can't refer to
expresiones no te no te puedes referir a
someone in public you could have said
alguien en público podías haber dicho
things in other ways are worth it or not
las cosas de otras maneras vale o sea no
We are not justifying insulting here.
no estamos justificando aquí insultar lo
What happens is that I [ __ ] on everything, I mean
que pasa es que me cago en todo o sea
I hate insulting anyone, uncle.
que me cago en todo insultar tío tengo
I have here a folder from the lady and the
yo aquí una carpeta de la señora y de la
daughter insulting
hija insultando a
tokii man by
tokii hombre por
Please, I think you know what it does to me.
favor Yo creo que sabes lo que me hace
It's funny that they sell it to you, damn it, they are
gracia es que te lo vendan [__] si están
selling with which to park how angry I am
vendiendo con que aparcar qué rabia me
that they try to humiliate you for your
da que te intenten humillarte por tu
accent is the raed To laugh at
acento está el raed Para reírse de
accents man but let Ray do it
acentos hombre pero que lo haga el Ray
you say, host, Ray is a
dices tú [__] el Ray es una
special person but make it a
persona especial pero que lo haga una
Mrs. Oh, I didn't put the part about the
señora Ay es que no he puesto lo de la
It's that I, the lady, was today
se Es que yo la señora hoy se estaba
making fun of my accent again like
burlando de mi acento otra vez como
point number one this is what I have to see
punto número uno esto qu tengo que ver
What does that have to do with me, ma'am?
Yo qué tiene que ver conmigo señora
Madam madam
Señora señora
I knew I was surra I don't know what over there the no
sab estaba surra no sé qué por ahí la no
I know now we will look for it okay but it has
sé ahora lo buscaremos vale pero me ha
put a good tit and that's what he's done
puesto un tet bueno ya eso lo ha hecho
several times a year, eh, that is to say,
ya varias veces en el año eh o sea la
lady already has one I don't say anything to her
señora lleva ya una Yo no le digo nada a
She eh I if she mentions here it's something of
ella eh yo si menciona aquí es algo de
like Antonia said this
en plan la Antonia ha dicho esto la
Anton has said the other but insults and
anton ha dicho el otro pero insultos y
contempt and so on, don't laugh at him
desprecios y demás que no se ría el
devil of lies If I'm saying
[__] de la mentira Si estoy diciendo
a lie and tell me eh but
una mentira e decírmelo eh pero
I think I don't have these forms.
yo creo que estas forma no la tengo yo
with her let's go I think I haven't found her
con ella Vamos Yo creo que no la topo
Say now, let's see if I can find
dece ya a ver si encuentro
Here I believe that these forms are not
aquí yo creo que estas formas no las
I have with her
tengo yo con ella
eh A
eh A
see shame without
ver verguenza sin
scrupulous everything for
escrúpulo todo por
money abusers and
dinero maltratadores y
stalkers here talking to this one
acosadores aquí hablándose con esta
account
cuenta
Okay, when those people surpass you, Javi No.
vale cuando te superan esa gente Javi No
I live this for life This is
viv que esto para toda la vida Esto es
for the whole life it's worth it, look, that is
para toda la vida vale mira o sea
putting up nonsense every day
poniendo barbaridades todos los días
Hey, I make 10 videos for a Live of
Eh que yo le hago 10 vídeos a un Live de
a recipe from Mrs. This This
una receta de cocina señora esto Este
tet I think it's from 2023 of 2024 that I
tet creo que es del 2023 de 2024 que yo
I make 10 videos for a like I think
le hago 10 vídeos por un like Yo creo
that is that they live in 2019 and they haven't
que es que viven en el 2019 y no lo han
overcome has been very hard for them and
superado ha sido muy fuerte para ellos y
They haven't overcome it luckily, what I
no lo han superado por suerte yo lo que
I have videos. Hey, look if I have
tengo son vídeos Oye pues mira si te he
insulted in 2019 for the situation
insultado en el 2019 por la situación
that we had and for the things that I
que teníamos y por las cosas que me
you did Well there is a video of mine
hicisteis Pues ahí hay un vídeo mío
apologizing in the
disculpándome en el
2022 I think it is or 20 I don't remember why
2022 creo que es o 20 no me acuerdo por
There is the video, okay, you can search for it.
ahí está el vídeo vale lo podéis Buscar
message for my mother Of course
mensaje para la madre de mi Claro que
After that, this lady follows everyone
después de eso esta señora siga todos
the days saying these things as if
los días diciendo estas cosas como si
were current I don't These are retweets
fueran actuales yo no Estos son retweet
Hey, these are retweets.
eh Estos son retweet
eh, I don't see it as very proportional
eh yo no lo veo muy proporcional
Hey, look here, do you remember that they're suing me?
eh mira aquí os acordáis que me demandan
Just saying cockroach doesn't leave one alone
por decir cucaracha no se queda una
cockroach Well look here it says that
cucaracha Bueno pues mira aquí dice que
we multiply like the
nosotros nos multiplicamos como las
cockroaches if they don't condemn us or they are
cucarachas si no nos condenan o sea son
many things are worth many things
muchísimas cosas vale muchísimas
lots of insults and things during
muchísimos insultos y cosas durante
for many years and I don't say anything to him
durante muchos años y yo no le digo nada
And then humiliations for
Y entonces humillaciones por
look and not just me eh Not just me but
mira y no solo a mí eh No solo a mí sino
to anyone who is in my environment eh
a cualquiera que esté en mi entorno eh
Yes Cristina Segui yes Franc this is spoken
si Cristina seguí si franc esta se habla
with me too if with whoever it is
conmigo también si con quien sea que
are that he gets along with me is are
estén que se lleve bien conmigo es son
insults mockery Hey, well if you see it
insultos burla Eh bueno si lo ve
proportional there will come a time when
proporcional llegará un momento en el
that maybe you know no I'm not very
que a lo mejor sabes no no esty muy
proportional La Movida is worth it without your cross
proporcional La Movida vale son tu cruz
Javi Bueno I understand the grudges and
Javi Bueno yo entiendo los rencores y
Things are not known but we have to overcome them
las cosas no no se pero hay que superar
things not uncle I mean what things not me
las cosas no tío O sea qué cosas no me
I said with Dross What What What What things
dije yo con Dross Qué Qué Qué Qué cosas
I didn't say it to myself with Dross and to this day
no me dije yo con Dross y a día de hoy
how well I get along with him, that is to say, I
lo bien que me llevo con él o sea me la
sweat what we said to each other are things But
suda lo que nos dijimos son cosas Pero
What am I telling you? Or what do I do?
qué es lo que te digo O sea qué hago
ma'am, that is, it's already there, but no, I don't have
señora o sea ya está no pero no no tengo
One the folder is huge I would have to
una la carpeta es inmensa me tendría que
put here now put you but they are
poner aquí ahora poneros pero son
insults that flip out, defamations that
insultos que flipas difamaciones que
you flip out that if I am garbage that if I am
flipas que si soy una basura que si soy
a [ __ ] that if a thousand things of insult
una [__] que si mil cosas de insulto
eh And there is the lady from Claro She is
eh Y está la señora de Claro Ella se
put in the first demand in the second
puso en la primera demanda en la segunda
which is the judgment I have now with my
que es el juicio que tengo ahora con mi
ar in that she no longer wears it because
ar en ese ella ya no se pone porque
Of course, ma'am, you are insulting me.
claro señora me está insultando
you don't need a lawyer or put
usted tú no necesitas un abogado o poner
You need to complain to those people
denuncias tú con esa gente necesitas
but an exorcist x from Greetings Well
pero un exorcista x de Saludos Bueno
well no, but that's what you
asasi bueno no pero es que es lo que te
I say, how many controversies there are
digo seao yo Cuántas polémicas no
We have here at the end of the year how many
tenemos aquí al cabo del año Cuántas
We don't have any controversies here, we made ourselves
polémicas no tenemos aquí nos hicimos
barbarities with one another But
barbaridades con uno con otro Pero
When the months pass it has passed But
cuando pasan los meses ha pasado Pero
There are people who are like this forever
hay gente que son para siempre como esta
the flat are people who do not overcome and are
el planas son gente que no superan y se
And they stay. And they stay.
quedan Y además ellos se quedan
discussing what happened that year, eh, that is,
discutiéndose lo de ese año eh o sea de
Suddenly the lady sends me a tweet of
repente la señora me pone un tweet de
This guy told me on WhatsApp that I was his
este me decía por WhatsApp que yo era su
mother, of course, ma'am, yes, we were friends, yes
madre claro señora si éramos amigos si
we had a relationship of talking to each other
teníamos una relación de hablarnos todos
the days Of course I told you mom and those
los días Claro que te decía mamá y esas
things I don't know the jokes like
cosas no yo que sé los cachondeos Como
I now say to Karime As I say to
le digo ahora a Karime Como le digo a
tesa As I say to beautiful things but
tesa Como le digo a cosas bonitas pero
No, no, don't argue with me about things from 2016 or 2017.
no no me discute cosas del 2016 de 2017
as if they were things from now, you know me
como si fueran cosas de ahora sabes me
the debates now well total sentence
los debate ahora bueno total sentencia
pioneer vale has published it faca These
pionera vale lo ha publicado faca Estos
They are pioneering sentences that have been published
son sentencias pioneras lo ha publicado
faca has published a lot of
faca lo han publicado un montón de
important and neutral media such as
medios importantes y neutrales como el
diario.es and as faa is worth total wiu ha
diario.es y como faa vale total wiu ha
put a tit but I already told you final boyfriend
puesto un tet pero ya te dig final novio
I understand that the groom celebrates it with
entiendo que el novio lo lo celebre con
his little drawing that he always celebrates
su dibujito no que él siempre lo celebra
these things with a drawing like when
estas cosas con un dibujo como cuando
I celebrated that Ricky Eddie reported me
celebró que Ricky Eddie me reportara
fraudulently the channel that also
fraudulentamente el canal que también
he put a little drawing
puso un dibujillo
Okay, yes, witch, I understand that in the end
vale Sí bruja Yo entiendo que al final
grudges and hatreds and those things I
los rencores y los odios y esas cosas Yo
It's that I don't, I don't, I don't feel that way about
es que no me no me yo no siento eso por
They nor for them they Yes they see themselves
ellas ni por ellos ellos Sí ellos se ven
Yes, let's see, I don't like them.
que sí a ver no me caen bien son
people who insult me ​​and who
personas que me insultan y que me
they slander every day
difaman todos los días
I mean, I don't like them obviously, but
O sea no me caen bien evidentemente pero
I don't feel hate, I don't feel it, they are not mine
no siento un odio no siento no son mi
reasons for my life okay I have to think
motivos de mi vida vale tengo que pensar
more into it than I would like because of
más en ello de lo que quisiera porque de
suddenly I have to pay a trial because
repente tengo que pagar un juicio porque
suddenly I have to worry about not
de repente tengo que preocuparme por no
I know you understand me but for me they are what
sé qué me entiendes pero para mí son qué
dude what's up dude eh what's up
as tío qué as tío eh qué cosilla
eh, what happened with Win Michu was more serious
eh fue más grave lo de Win michu los
progressive judges don't know what Win Michu does
jueces progres no lo lo de Win michu si
It was a yes, they condemned Cris for the
fue una sí lo condenaron Cris por lo del
bottle blow for which Win was not sentenced
botellazo a lo que no condenaron a Win
Michu was in the Dallas prison that for
michu fue en la penal de Dallas que por
It is true that the sentence is awaited
cierto está a la espera de la sentencia
civil let's see what happens with
civil vamos a ver qué es lo que pasa con
the civil judgment and depending on the
la sentencia civil y dependiendo del
result of the people let's see what
resultado de la gente vamos a ver qué
What do you think because of course
qué opinan porque claro
eh in that in that trial Well, I already
eh en esa en ese juicio Bueno ya lo
We'll see, we'll see, okay. But oh well.
veremos ya lo veremos vale Pero bueno
They are little things that you say, damn it.
son cositas que que tú dices [__] pues
Win michu told Dallas that she was a
Win michu a Dallas le dijo que era una
Yena is a psychopathic abuser of this
yena un psicópata maltratador de esto
abuser of the other in prison
maltratador de lo otro en el penal se
He considered that it was that he did not have the
Consideró que era que no tenía la
size as for a penalty but that
envergadura como para un penal sino que
It was a cross between a youtuber who both
era un cruce de youtuber que ambos se
They said things I don't know what we're going to see in the
decían cosas no sé cuá vamos a ver en el
civil What's up? I don't I I'm that
civil Qué pasa Yo no yo yo es que
I would have put only the
hubiera puesto solo el
civil but first of all the right to
civil pero de primera el de derecho al
honor not a competition
honor no una competencia
You know we want a criminal conviction for him
sabes queremos una condena penal para el
Dallas minimum one year in prison for the
Dallas mínimo un año de cárcel para el
gentleman who physically assaulted a woman
señor que agredió físicamente a una
woman who 12k to the gentleman because Hey what
mujer que 12k al señor porque Oye lo
insult if that's justice alanne
insulta si eso es justicia alanne
Ban him here, don't post things, don't post things
banealo aquí no pongáis no pongáis cosas
So dude, because eh, you can hurt me.
así tío Porque eh Me podéis perjudicar a
me and because there isn't any I understand
mí y porque no hay ninguna Yo entiendo
that each of you have your opinions and
que cada uno tenéis vuestras opiniones y
I have them too but I prefer
tal Yo también las tengo pero prefiero
reserve mela So don't put that type
reservá mela Así que no pongáis ese tipo
of barbarities please I can't tell you
de barbaridades por favor no os lo puedo
allow okay you don't even have to put it
permitir vale ni tenéis que ponerlo
Well
bueno
layer
capa
cape celebrates the goal
capa celebra el gol
Come to the Basilica of the Angels here
vente a la Basílica de Los Ángeles aquí
in Costa Rica and you bathe in holy water
en Costa Rica y te bañas en agua bendita
face twisting with laughter It's that
cara revolviéndose de la risa Es que
You know what happens, I'm not a believer. You know?
sabes qué pasa que no soy creyente Sabes
What happens is that I am not a believer then no
qué pasa que no soy creyente entonces no
I know if it would be of much use to me, cape celebrates
sé si me serviría de mucho capa celebra
the goal to me is that
el gol a mí lo de que
clear
claro
layer my speech with layer because there is one
capa mi habla con capa porque hay una
girl who accuses us of having
chica que acusa a de ha Us de
she clear I understand that Antonia By
ella claro Yo entiendo que Antonia Por
example if you posted a tweet to Tania pm
ejemplo si le puso a Tania pm un tweet
Telling Tania all my support although
diciéndole Tania todo mi apoyo aunque
we are at the ideological antipodes that
estemos en las antípodas ideológicas que
I don't understand why he put that when
no entiendo por qué le puso eso cuando
Tania is left-wing. I imagine that she is
Tania es de izquierda Me imagino que se
refers to the antipodes because Tania is
refiere a las antípodas porque Tania es
Moderated by Antonio Abi and Antonia Su
moderadora de Antonio Abi y Antonia su
Twitter is largely dedicated to
Twitter en gran parte está dedicado a
say that Antonio Abi is an abuser
decir que Antonio Abi es un maltratador
and that and that he stole Roso's children
y que y que le robó los hijo a roso
Carrasco but
Carrasco pero
Of course, Antonia gave Tania something.
claro bueno Antonia le puso a Tania algo
as well as my support Tania my support all my
así como mi apoyo Tania mi apoyo todo mi
support no
apoyo no
because something very strong came out of
em porque salió una cosa muy fuerte de
her husband is fine but of course he is a cloak
su marido vale pero claro capa
miare is worn with a cape because there is one
miare se lleva con capa porque hay una
girl no no reply The Good ban the
chica no no repliquen El Bueno banear al
that puts something like what has
que ponga alguna cosa como la que ha
said Dark okay Because that is not what it is
dicho Dark vale Porque de eso no eso se
You may be stupid, you're seeing that there is
puede estáis tonto estáis viendo que hay
a conviction for
una condena por
That's really cool, huh?
eso de verdad fto neró eh
I told you that there is a girl
em que lo he dicho que hay una chica
accusing Capa of abuse Then
acusando a capa de de abuso Entonces
Miar doesn't believe the girl or how I understand
miar no cree a la chica o cómo entiendo
who doesn't believe the girl
que no cree a la chica
no this one I don't know if it is to explain to you who
no este no sé si es que explicaros quién
is this you remember the Christian who is
es este os acordáis del Cristian que se
I created many multi-accounts and put one
creaba muchas multicuentas y ponía una
photo of my daughter then I put a photo
foto de mi hija luego ponía una foto
Well, this is the Christian you remember?
pues este es el Cristian ese os acordáis
It was not that much was created about Cristian
de Cristian era no que se creaba mucha
Is this already five years old or so?
Es que esto ya es de hace cinco o se
years is that what is that people already
años es que los que es que la gente ya
He has no [ __ ] idea about the lords of
no tiene ni [__] idea de de los lores De
Who are you, uncle? I mean, what do I know?
quién son tío o sea Yo qué sé cómo
I'll explain to you who this guy is.
explico yo a ti quién es este este tío
It was one like the Wilson is today
era uno como hoy en día es el el Wilson
and the canine but this one was more this one was
y el canino pero este era más este era
even more stalker or this is the one that
más acosador todavía o sea este el que
This guy impersonated you.
te hizo la suplantación este tío se
dedicated to
dedicaba a
to create a lot of accounts that are
a a crearse un montón de cuentas que se
Cristian 1 calls Cristian 2 and now
llama Cristian 1 Cristian 2 y ahora
I might put a photo of Lorena
ponía a lo mejor una foto de Lorena
pregnant and put a demon or or
embarazada y le ponía un demonio o o
I suddenly put up a picture of my daughter and
ponía de repente una foto de mi hija y y
He made fun of my daughter and things like that
se burlaba de mi hija y s cosas así
You know where Lada Amores and
sabes dónde estarán ahora lada amores y
his famous phrase about a little apartment in prison
su famosa frase de pisito en la cárcel
But what a little apartment in prison, [ __ ]
Pero qué pisito en la cárcel [__]
If it is a civil fine it is a
si es una es una multa civil es un
right to
derecho al
honor is that F you the clan
honor es que F tú el clan
Ok Well apart from ra also supports
vale Bueno aparte de ra también apoya
These people like Joan
esto gente como Joan
flat ok here it is with Sara
planas vale que aquí está con con Sara
Reverte and with Antonia the country is worth a
reverte y con Antonia vale el país un
newspaper like the country is also worth the
periódico como el país también vale el
YouTuber from the review called him an abuser
youtuber de la review llamó maltratador
and the father of his ex-partner is a criminal
y delincuente al padre de su expareja
But I don't know why, or rather you
Pero es que yo no sé por o sea te
They condemn you for calling you a criminal But
condenan por llamarte delincuente Pero
why because the criminal sentence that
por qué porque la la sentencia penal que
he considers his father a criminal, no, he is not.
tiene el padre por delincuente no es no
I mean, I have to see the sentence, I don't know.
O sea tengo que ver sentencia yo no sé
Yes, I still have it there, but I don't
si la tengo por ahí todavía pero yo no
I know if he is a criminal, but of course yes
sé si por delincuente pero claro si
you have a criminal sentence against the father
tienes una sentencia penal al padre lo
They did not criminally condemn the one who did not
condenaron penalmente no a la que no
They condemned him to the
condenaron fue a la
mother then of course these headlines to me
madre entonces claro estos titulares me
I imagine that eh
imagino que eh
relative good are headlines that the
relativo bueno son titulares que los
friends of the press with whom
amigos de la de la prensa le con los que
They help him, but well, I don't know, maybe
le ayudan no Pero bueno no sé a lo mejor
They can't call you a criminal either.
no te pueden llamar delincuente Tampoco
because you have even if you have one
porque tengas aunque tengas una
criminal sentence I don't understand or why
sentencia penal no lo entiendo o porque
He told her before she had any trouble.
se lo dijo antes que tuvier hua la
sentence no I don't understand this because I
sentencia no no entiendo esto porque yo
I understand that it is for the rest of
entiendo que es por lo por el resto de
the insults But well Joan planas that
los insultos Pero bueno Joan planas que
yesterday he tried to give me a strike
ayer me intentó poner un strike de
copyright in the game over in
copyright en el game over en
2025 yesterday Johan Planas tried to put a
2025 ayer Johan planas intentó poner un
Game copyright strike
strike por copyright al Game
over in
over en
2025 Game Over that justice has said
2025 Game Over que la justicia ha dicho
that stays
que se queda
in
en
2025 with whom
2025 con quién se
takes with the
lleva con la
Antonia everyone has the right to
Antonia cada uno tiene derecho a
get along with whoever you want
llevarse con quien quiera
worth that we are not at all a criminal and
valeur que sonos De nada delincuente y
abuser is an insult. Nothing good.
maltratador es un insulti De nada bueno
These insults have been made by you and me
estos insultos lo has hecho tú yo en
plan people also to myself you told me
plan gente también a mí mismo me dijiste
abuser Aha what else is that you
maltratador Aha que otra cosa es que tú
you dare to say it because you are
te atrevas a afirmarlo porque tú eres
at most he throws The Little Stone with the
como mucho tira La Piedrecita con la
Little hand, what those people are doing is not normal.
manita lo de esa gente no es normal Por
no matter how much time passes, they remain trapped
más que pase el tiempo siguen atrapados
in 2014, which is almost 11 years ago,
en el 2014 que son ya casi 11 años un
little bit of please No no it's not that they
poquito de por favor No no es que ellos
They discuss things with you as if they were
te discuten cosas del como si fueran
You know, look and see what the plane told me.
sabes mira a ver que el plana me lo dijo
to me and that was worth to be around
a mí y eso valía para abarloar de
destroy life but if you say so Dallas
destruir la vida pero si lo dices Dallas
or nothing happens to me, I don't understand or understand it
o yo no pasa nada eso no entiendo ni lo
what is saying here that gives us things
que está diciendo aquí que nos da cosas
Let's see what Planas told me and
a ver que el planas me lo dijo a mí y
That was worth it to kiss. Of course I did.
eso valía para bejar Claro que me lo
you said and then in the trial you put yourself
dijiste y luego en el juicio te pusiste
to cry and say that you were scared of my
a llorar a decir que te daban miedo mis
videos or so what it seems to me that
vídeos o sea a mí lo que me parece que
Yes, you can win because I insulted you.
sí que tú puedes ganar porque te insulté
I'm on the flat and I know how to put myself right now
yo en plana y yo ahora mismo sé ponerme
here to burst and insult you
aquí a reventar y a insultarte
Surely people will applaud it and
seguramente la gente lo va a aplaudir y
I can go and insult you and be condemned
te puedo ir a insultar y me condenan
again but but man that you
otra vez per pero hombre que tú te
you put insulting people to do
pongas a insultar a la gente a hacer
ugly insinuations you make And then the
insinuaciones feas que haces Y luego las
deny or then be answered with
niegues o que luego te respondan con
insult and then you
insulto y luego tú
You demand little, you know little but
demandes poquito sabes poquito pero
Well, you in your world and and and that's it, Joan
bueno tú en tu mundo y y y ya está Joan
that's how you are And that's how you have
que así estás Y así has
It is necessary to be delayed to
quedado Hay que ser [__] para
believe these monetized hate and
creerse estos monetizados de odio y
Antonia arrives and says, "Good Joan."
llega Antonia y le dice bien Joan
taking into account that he is an abuser
teniendo en cuenta que maltratador es
slander can therefore be criminal
una calumnia por tanto puede ser penal
and wink and
e guiño y
tongue what a penalty
lengüita qué penal
lady What a shame lady good And if you can
señora Qué penal señora bueno Y si puede
be a penalty because you have not called a penalty
ser penal porque no lo has puesto penal
I fight a kiss if it can be a penalty because
Lucho un beso si puede ser penal porque
she hasn't. That is to say, the lady herself is
no lo ha O sea la señora misma está
saying could go for criminal and for
diciendo podría ir por lo penal Y por
why haven't you gone to the criminal court because
qué no has ido usted por lo penal porque
Her husband has not gone for criminal proceedings as
no ha ido su marido por lo penal como
Dallas If it was for you, it was for criminal reasons.
Dallas Si fue por usted por lo penal
I don't understand, heo. I imagine that family.
no entiendo heo Me imagino a esa familia
at Christmas and New Year's dinner everyone
en la cena de Navidad y Año Nuevo todos
at the table talking about Javi and Dallas What
en la mesa hablando de Javi y Dallas Qué
sad to dedicate your entire life to living
triste dedicar su vida entera a vivir
with complaints and
con denuncias y
trials today you look very handsome all the
juicios hoy te ves muy guapo todos los
days you tell me Thank you very much
días me lo decís Muchas gracias de
true yes yes chill Okay chill let's see that
verdad sí sí chill Bueno chill a ver eso
He told it, I don't know if you remember a video
lo contó no sé si os acordáis un vídeo
I have it around here
lo tengo por ahí de
Quetzal quetzal counted last year no
Quetzal quetzal contó el año pasado no
last year or the other 2023 no
el año pasado o el otro el 2023 no
Do you have a video of you saying that
tenéis un vídeo de que sal contando que
wismichu and miare when they meet for
wismichu y miare cuando se reúnen por
There with friends they spend time. Oh and such they were
ahí con amigos pasen Ah y tal se ponían
to talk about good was in that case was of
a hablar de bueno era en ese caso era de
billin because of course villin had done
billin porque claro villin había hecho
The passes with Dallas and then well
Las pases con Dallas y entonces pues lo
Typical Well what I have already experienced No
típico Bueno lo que yo ya he vivido No
It's not that there are shady things that don't
no es que hay cosas turbias que no
You know, I don't know what. I already know, I know.
sabéis no sé qué Ya ya lo sé lo sé
places Yes, that's what he told me that salt is what it is
lugares Sí eso lo contó que sal que es
friend of yo eh I don't that
amigo de yo eh yo no que
Yes yes yes they go out with friends from
sale Sí sí sí que salen con amigos de
dinner and the Dallas the Dallas and abin for the
cena y el Dallas el Dallas y abin por el
Dallas no Dallas so you learn has you
Dallas no Dallas para que aprendas te ha
the sentence came out cheap with all the
salido barata la condena con todas las
barbarities that you said but little by little
barbaridades que dijiste pero poco a
little the problem of the monetized of
poco el problema de los monetizadas de
Hatred is reaching justice and Iran
odio va llegando a la justicia y Irán
It's true, so they should celebrate
est verdad o sea es que que celebren
This is as if it were the closing of the channel
esto como si fuera el cierre del canal
from Dallas but look what he says
de Dallas pero Fijate tú lo que le pone
the capture of when Dallas laughed at
la captura de cuando Dallas se rió de
that he lost Ase
que él perdió Ase
3 years How long has it been since I lost Yoan
3 años Cuánto hace que he perdido yoan
flat with me the first one
plana conmigo la la primera
instance Ay Alex politic
instancia Ay Alex politic
Uncle Alex Politi, do you know who this is?
tío Alex politi sabéis Quién es no este
uncle started telling yuji that it was a
tío se puso a decirle a yuji que era una
drug trafficker F
drogad dista Traficante de o sea F
you are the ones who see them celebrating this and
tú es que te los ves celebrando esto y
Okay, I understand that it is because
bueno Vale entiendo que que es por
ideology is worth Joan plan is a feminist
ideología vale Joan plan es feminista
for example also
por ejemplo también
No, but of course I understand that it is because
no pero claro entiendo que es por
ideology but man you were that you
ideología pero tío que tú estabas que tú
you were insulting yuji by saying that
estabas insultando a yuji diciendo que
She was a cocaine addict and a drug dealer
era una cocainomana y una Traficante de
drugs and I don't know what, I don't know how much for
droga y un no sé qué un no sé cuánto por
your holy balls, man, the clip of
tus Santas pelotas [__] tío el clip de
wait for the clip of this man who
espérate el clip de este hombre que me
love the click you posted the other day
encanta el click que publicó el otro día
utbh of this turkey
utbh de este pavo
Uncle, I have money to put up with you.
tío tengo dinero para aguantarte
Okay
vale
historical I have money to put up with you
histórico tengo dinero para aguantarte
Okay, you have more than me, that's plenty.
vale Tú tienes más que yo eso de sobra
but I know how it works, okay, I'm fine.
pero yo yo sé cómo funciona vale estoy
already involved in
ya metido en
I have money to endure things
movidas tengo dinero para aguantar
move eh Alex politi Alex politi is
movida eh Alex politi Alex politi está
made a move, well this is the homeland
metio movida bueno Esta es la la patri
not the friend Well this potato this potato
no la amiga Bueno esta papa esta papa
He still sends me love from time to time
todavía me manda carime de vez en cuando
t about me when it's not her it's with
t sobre mí cuando no es ella es con
Gorgon is fabric but fabric fabric aunt Y
gorgona sea tela pero tela tela tía Y
This is that it is not nor is she not of the
esta es que no es ni ella no es de la
family is not her but apart from that she
familia no es ella pero aparte se
This woman invented it, I gave her one
inventa esta mujer le puse yo una
very good complaint
denuncia buenísimo
I'm going to use it I'm going to use it
lo voy a utilizar lo voy a utilizar
then eh but there it is there it is the
luego eh pero ahí está ahí está las
I'm really looking forward to February.
ganas que tengo de que llegue febrero Eh
I'm not going to explain who it is, you can see
no os voy a explicar Quién es podéis ver
the topic of with the forego tiando and those
el tema de con el forego tiando y esas
stories not with the things he has done
historias no con las cosas que ha hecho
This lady told me about me
esta señora que me ha dicho sobre mí
about my wife about my family that is
sobre mi mujer sobre mi familia que se
He has even messed with my mother, it's worth it
ha metido hasta con mi madre vale la le
I had to file a complaint then
le tuve que poner una denuncia luego se
He started to invent what I did to him
ha puesto a inventarse que yo le hice a
your son I don't know what I published where
su hijo no sé qué que yo publiqué donde
She worked and that's how you came to
ella trabajaba y es como s viniste tú a
ask for help because you had a problem
pedir ayuda porque tenías un problema de
money and I the teteg and a few te
dinero y yo el teteg y unos cuantos te
We help the ukum I have the twit here
ayudamos el ukum tengo por aquí los twit
certificates of how we help you and why
certificados de cómo te ayudamos y por
That was known where you worked because you
eso se supo dónde trabajabas porque te
We help with your business and what
ayudamos con tu negocio y y lo
we promote you know and well And this
promocionamos sabes y bueno Y esta
while I was while I was
mientras que me estaba mientras que me
He was asking me about the pregnancy
estaba a mí preguntando por el embarazo
Lorena was behind us
de Lorena por la espalda nos estaba
saying about Lorena's physical appearance everything
diciendo de todo físico de Lorena todo
everything is worth it and then his life
vale todo todo y entonces pues su vida
It's not that I don't understand or
es esta No es que no entiendo ni
not even the Why after me
siquiera el Por qué después a mí me
They say dog ​​from Dallas But I am this
dicen perr de Dallas Pero es que yo esto
I don't understand it because, that is, the desire
no lo entiendo porque o sea las ganas
that I have to wait for February to arrive, you know
que tengo de que llegue febrero sabéis
Why Because it is the witness that carries
por qué Porque es la testigo que lleva
Miare next month to his trial takes
miare el mes que viene a su juicio lleva
a gorgon or rather takes her friend and is
a gorgona o sea lleva a su amiga y es
whatever, let's see, whatever
como o sea vamos a ver o sea
em let's see if I understand it let's see if
em a ver si lo entiendo a ver si lo
I understand your lawyer pleaded with the court
entiendo tu abogado suplicó al juzgado
that I was not a witness in Dallas
que yo no fuera testigo en el de Dallas
both in one and the other to both
tanto en uno como en el otro a los dos
that I went from Dallas that one was
que he ido yo de Dallas que uno fue
against that of wismichu and with that of such no
contra el de wismichu y con el de tal no
Please, this one cannot be a witness.
por favor este no puede ser testigo
because he gets along badly with those reported
porque se lleva mal con los denunciados
I don't know what and now you're going to get one
no sé qué y ahora tú te vas a llevar una
dad that I had to report that
papa a la que yo tuve que denunciar que
He has given me everything that is obsessing
me ha puesto de todo que está obsesionar
With me you know and trust what you put on
conmigo sabes y fíate tú lo que te pone
the desire is your life and it is like
las ganas sea su vida y es como
Patri, what's wrong with you in February? What's wrong?
patri qué te pasa en febrero qué es lo
What happens in February solves something for you?
que pasa en febrero te soluciona algo no
I know what this is, this is your life
sé qué es lo que esta esta es tu vida
this is yours
est es tu
happiness I mean fite you to the one you carry
felicidad O sea fite tú a la que llevas
as a witness, which is good, I hope because
de testigo que bueno yo espero porque
Look at the other witness that I brought, I'll bring it back.
mira el otro testigo que llevó lo vuelvo
I'll repeat what I said the other day.
a repetir lo dije el otro día lo digo
again and I say it very calmly eh without
otra vez y lo digo tranquilísimo eh sin
no fear is worth the witness that
ningún temor vale el testigo que
they took the first trial made a fake
llevaron al primer juicio hizo un falso
testimony completely lied and
testimonio mintió completamente y lo
I say Here in public And if someone
digo Aquí en público Y si alguien se
dare you tell me the opposite of the
atreve que me diga lo contrario de los
who are here following my lead
que están aquí siguiéndome el testigo
that led to the first trial was worth it
que llevó al primer juicio vale se puso
to say that and it is in the video of the
a decir que y está está en el vídeo del
judgment of the played is worth that
juicio del los jugado vale que ese
Man, then you will have to pay.
hombre Pues tendrá que pagar
Obviously you will have to answer it
evidentemente lo tendrá que responder
Well, of course he did it wrong. You can't do that.
Pues claro lo hizo mal Eso no lo puedes
I don't understand how there are people who
hacer yo no entiendo como hay gente que
lends itself to doing that for these people
se presta a hacer eso para esta gente
Okay, but well, I hope Patrick that you
vale Pero bueno yo espero Patrick que tú
don't do it I hope you answer
no lo hagas Yo espero que tú respondas a
All the questions they are going to ask you are
todas las preguntas que te van a hacer s
I'm not going to ask you not to go
yo no voy a pedir que tú no vayas de
Witness okay, I'm not going to ask for that.
testigo vale Yo no eso no lo voy a pedir
I'm going to ask you to go but
yo voy a pedir que tú vayas pero que
you answer okay Patrick
respondas vale Patrick
that the witness they brought to the first
que el testigo que llevaron al primer
judgment that it was a cowardly mess
juicio que era la lía de cobarde el
That Marti started saying that I
marti ese se puso a decir que yo
weekly he dedicated live broadcasts to it
semanalmente le dedicaba directos
whole hours to Miare and her mother
enteros de horas a miare y a su madre
telling you that you are a dirty [ __ ]
diciéndole [__] [__] que eres una
crazy old [ __ ] [ __ ] you
vieja hija de [__] loca que prostituyes
To your daughter, I don't know what nonsense she said
a tu hija No sé unas barbaridades dijo
the guy or me like this I say what and
el tipo o sea yo así Yo así digo what y
my lawyer telling him Sorry you are
mi abogado diciéndole Perdona tú estás
saying that Javi did this in
diciendo que esto lo hacía Javi en
live for hours a week Where are they?
directo durante horas seman Dónde están
Those videos and that witness are taken into account
esos vídeos y ese testigo se tiene en
It is noted in the sentence that I am condemned
cuenta en la sentencia a mí me condenan
because it says in part because of what he says
porque dice en parte por lo que dice el
the witness who is like Well then we already
el testigo que es como Bueno pues ya nos
fix oars with that We'll have to see
apañar remos con eso Tendremos que verlo
That means that I have years left with that
o sea eso me queda a mí años con ese
procedure or between what was stopped
procedimiento o sea entre lo que se paró
because they opposed a test between
porque se opusieron a una prueba entre
what is between the time that I know that
lo que se entre lo del tiempo que se que
was lost because they opposed a
se perdió porque se opusieron a una
test that I say Well let's see if
prueba que yo digo Bueno vamos a ver si
They tell me that I have something
a mí me dicen que yo tengo una cosa
You know I asked for a test of which
Sabes Yo pedí una prueba de la cual
I have certain indications and I already told you that.
tengo yo ciertos indicios y yo eso ya os
I'll explain it well, okay, I'll explain it.
lo explicaré bien vale eso lo explicaré
very good very good it will surely be a
muy bien muy bien seguramente será un
well explained video ok or here in the
vídeo bien explicado vale o aquí en el
direct But if you have one thing if you
directo Pero si tú tienes una cosa si tú
you don't have it for me, they call me Javi you
no la tienes a mí a mí me dicen Javi tú
You have a microphone here in the drawer
tienes aquí en el cajón un micrófono
Rosa and I'm sure I don't have it
Rosa y yo estoy seguro que no lo tengo
I tell you, open the drawer, take it, look at it, see.
yo te digo abre el cajón toma míralo ves
since I have nothing but well that's it
como no tengo nada pero bueno eso son
the things we already know how they are
las cosas que ya sabemos como cóm son
each one I think no it is not necessary
cada uno yo creo que no no hace falta
nothing new either, but good that you
nada nuevo tampoco no pero bueno que tu
life is that homeland Oh what Wishing that
vida sea esa patri Ay qué Deseando que
February comes, why that? I don't know.
llegue febrero para qué eso Tú no sé
daughter, well, Anuj, eh, conera, condemnation
hija bueno anuj eh conera condena
pioneer in Spain, look what I thought
pionera en España mira que yo que creía
now anuk who was almost one step away from
ahora anuk que casi estaba a un paso de
vote for
votar a
vox look I thought anuk was
vox mira que yo pensaba que anuk estaba
one step away from voting for Vox, it's worth a year
a un paso de votar a vox vale anu
pioneering conviction of what And then he will have
condena pionera de qué Y luego tendrá
that reading the sentence you have not read it or the
que leer la sentencia no has leído ni la
news colleague you have not even read the
noticia colega no has leído ni la
news
noticia
colleague who does not have to read the ruling
colega que no no tiene que leer el fallo
But well, anu being anu
Pero bueno anu siendo anu
misinforming about Fran now Then what
desinformando lo de Fran ahora Luego lo
we see no And then you start sending me
vemos no Y entonces me empezáis a mandar
in the group
en el grupo
This is this video that I say, wow, this is it.
esta este vídeo que digo [__] Este es
a journalist who with the Daniel issue
un periodista que con el el tema Daniel
Sancho if I'm not mistaken too and I
Sancho si no me equivoco también y me
I see this video but I also don't know
veo este vídeo pero es que además no sé
What is this video about? Or what is it about?
Este vídeo De qué trata O sea de Qué
program is this video or what known
programa es este vídeo o de qué conocido
in the world of YouTubers like Dallas
en el mundo de los youtubers como Dallas
He is one of the most important YouTubers
es uno de los youtubers más importantes
is the most important Spanish in Europe I
es español más importantes de Europa yo
I would dare to say that in the world
me atrevería a decir que del mundo más
11 million followers on YouTube
de 11 millones de seguidores en YouTube
I can tell you in advance that in these
les puedo adelantar que en estos
moments a woman a youtuber too
momentos una mujer una youtuber también
which also has hundreds of thousands of
que tiene también cientos de miles de
followers on YouTube is along with his
seguidores en YouTube está junto con su
law firm preparing a
despacho de abogados preparando una
very tough criminal action With what has he done
acción penal durísima Con heo qué ha
been
sido
Uncle Heo Cas
tío heo cas
been I mean no it's not my are it's not my are
sido O sea no no es mi are no es mi are
I thought about my area at first I say that
yo pensé en mi áre al principio digo que
will now denounce for God's sake what
va a denunciar ahora por Dios Qué lo que
but of course then think
pero claro luego pensar
then
luego
thinking So you're going to take
pensando O sea que tú vayas a tomar
criminal legal measures and what and what
medidas legales penales y lo y lo
you advertise with a TT with a
anuncies con un TT con un
emoji I personally believe
emoji yo personalmente creo
that shows a certain bad faith and lack of seriousness
que muestra cierta Mala Fe poca seriedad
But well, I don't know, I'll wait for anything.
Pero bueno no sé ya me espero cualquier
thing and and maybe Hey maybe
cosa y y a lo mejor Oye a lo mejor
They succeed, it sounds like a surprise to me personally.
triunfan a mí personalmente me suena un
little by little
poco a intento
from Scratch
de Scratch
media who will have been emoji with
mediático quién habrá sido emoji con
little mustache and
bigotito y
glasses now yes that yes you give sunk eh
gafas ahora sí que sí daas hundido eh
Pay attention to me, I have reported
Hacedme casito que he denunciado a
someone you don't like
alguien que os cae mal
totally not even that 500 likes of it
totalmente ya ni eso 500 likes delo
put 5 million impressions here
métele aquí 5 millones de impres
chur
chur
from put 5 million here
del métele aquí 5 millones de
impressions that these are the Live
impresiones que estos son los Live
These are the true Lives
verdaderos estos son los Live
True vs. Dallas a complaint
verdaderos contra Dallas una querella
criminal for very serious crimes one of
criminal por delitos gravísimos uno de
the most important law firms
los despachos de abogados más
important in the country are working on
importantes del país están trabajando en
these moments in the writing of this
estos momentos en la redacción de esta
complaint and it is a matter of hours
querella y es cuestión sio de horas de
days that end up being presented in the
días que se acaben presentando en los
played guard of one of the
jugados de guardia de una de las
main capitals of our country in
principales capitales de nuestro país en
the players of
los jugados de
guard By
guardia Por
What are you going to put on after 3 in the
qué la va a poner después de las 3 de la
The attorney cannot make it late
tarde no la puede poner el procurador no
you can put it in court
la puede poner en en un juzgado
normal guy really 2017 happened there
normal tío de de verdad 2017 pasó hay
to overcome the
que superar las
things are things that must be overcome 2017
cosas sea hay que superar las cosas 2017
It happened, it didn't turn out well, they stayed, but of course
pasó no quedó bien quedaron pero claro
That's what I'm telling you, the flat effect, that is.
es lo que te digo efecto yan plana o sea
They are people who are staying, that is, those of
son gente que se quedan ya o sea los de
of the in nimu those of delo and nimu I don't know
del los in nimu los de delo y nimu no sé
If you have already noticed, but the thing about
si os habéis dado cuenta ya pero lo de
delo and nimu already with d not for encouragement but
delo y nimu ya con d no por nimo sino
by delox it is forever and it is also
por delox es para siempre ya es tamb
well as miar also as the flat
bien como miar también como el planas
with me these who are forever
conmigo estos que son para siempre lo
You know not RAE
sabéis no RAE
They are also people who are already for
también son gente que son ya para
you always know not in following
siempre lo sabéis no en siguientes
connections we will have more details and
conexiones tendremos más detalles y
we will be able to give much more specificity to the
podremos dar mucha más concreción al
respect of course this is a journalist of
respecto claro esto es un periodista de
Tele5, this is a note that wants to be a gossip.
tele5 esto es un nota que quiere salseo
What do you mean, I'm going to throw this away now?
What o sea esto sí lo voy a tirar ahora
good whatever
buen da igual
No cli by Javi gubel c and more Oh it doesn't matter
No cli de Javi gubel c y más Ah da igual
It's okay if they are small clips.
No pasa nada si son clip pequeñitos No
Nothing happens. What I don't want is for them to go up
pasa nada Lo que no quiero es que suban
extract I already said the other day that
extracto ya lo dije el otro día que
upload little clips, be me what I am not
suban clips pequeñitos sea yo lo que no
I want what they are not going to upload an extract
quiero lo que no van a subir un extracto
and they are going to take away my extract
y me van a quitar el extracto me
You understand, but I'll see if today we get it
entiendes Pero yo a ver si hoy nos da
time to see this I want to see this
tiempo de ver esto que quiero ver esto
what the [ __ ] is he flirting with?
qué [__] es con quién está ligando el
Juan
Juan
Okay, let's see what he said.
Bueno vamos vamos a ver n que ha dicho
Okay people no no no I'm not going to throw it away No
bueno gente no no no lo voy a tirar No
nothing happens, no clip
pasa nada son clip
little one, we have to comment on things
pequeñito hay que comentar cosas
controversies Ah controversy Ho the channels of
polémicas Ah polémica Ho los canales de
saso they are going to
saso se van a
rechupes Don't give me strike
rechupes No me pongas strike
n Ok, it would be good to see more boys
n Ok bueno fuera ver más chicos
You trust as the complaint announces, eh?
se fíate tú como anuncia la querella eh
either you trust as the complaint announces or
sea fíate tú como anuncia la querella o
I don't know if your lawyer is Miliki.
sea yo no sé si tu abogado es Miliki
nimu but I think I would not advise
nimu pero yo creo que no aconsejaría a
My client never announced the complaint.
mi cliente nunca anunciar la querella
with
con
emojis and now with gossip channels
emojis y ahora con los canales de salseo
They are going to eat a very personal opinion, eh?
van a comer opinión personalísima eh
You see, I'm a redneck, a Lego in
verds tú que yo soy un paleto un Lego en
right as David Bravo told me and that and
derecho como me dijo David Bravo y que y
that I might as well be smoking a log
que lo mismo me Estoy fumando un tronco
incredible and yes eh I mean that's the way
increíble y sí eh o sea es la manera
pretty to announce it
guapa de anunciarlo
Yes, yes, they are aware of my networks
si si están al tanto de mis redes
social media may have noticed that I have
sociales pudieron haber notado de que he
uploaded a
subido un
video I reposted a video of a
video he reposte un videoo de un
Spanish television reporter
Informador de la televisión española
Keiko says, what do you know, Jai, if you go?
dice keiko tú que sabes Jai si vas
losing two trials already and four that
perdiendo dos juicios ya y cuatro que
I'm going to lose and four that I'm going to lose
voy a perder y cuatro que voy a perder
But well, I speak because I have a mouth and
Pero bueno hablo porque tengo boca y
because I charge for talking to you too
porque cobro por por hablar también te
I say By the way Keiko now that you mention it
digo Por cierto keiko ahora que dices Lo
of the trials
de los juicios
the best community on the internet you know
la mejor comunidad de internet sabéis
Which
Cuál
It is the best community on the internet, it is not
es la mejor comunidad de internet no es
that of
la de
Keiko is mine
keiko es la mía
gentlemen fixed value in the chat the
señoreros fijado vale en el chat el
you have the link pinned in the chat if
enlace lo tenéis fijado en el chat si
Does anyone want to make their contribution, Keiko?
alguien quiere hacer su aportación keiko
Ok, well, Keiko, you with the monetization.
vale Bueno keiko tú con la monetización
It helps me because you are here every day
me sirve porque todos los días estás
watching live is fine but for anyone
viendo directo vale pero para cualquier
person who considers that our struggle
persona que considere que nuestra lucha
with this With this
con este Con este
team is unfair okay And he loves us
equipo es injusta vale Y nos quiere
lend a hand with whatever it may be
echar una mano ya sea con lo que sea
any contribution is appreciated
cualquier aportación se agradece
very worth it you have the link fixed
muchísimo vale tenéis el enlace fijado
in it
en el
chat and and I think I think probably
chat y y creo que creo que probablemente
let's make an extensible what I have
hagamos un extensible lo que tengo lo
What I'm not clear about are the terms of the
que no tengo claro son los términos del
extensible how often we expand the
extensible cada cuanto ampliamos los
minutes of extendable that's what no
minutos de extensible eso es lo que no
I am clear because there are options that I
tengo Claro porque hay opciones que me
they seem a lot
parecen mucho
I don't know the
no sé la
true a person who works in a
verdad una persona que trabaja en un
Spanish television channel on Tele5 eh
canal de televisión español en tele5 eh
has posted a vom about a
ha ha posteado un vom acerca de un
legal procedure that is being carried out
procedimiento legal que se está llevando
carried out in Spain curiously this
a cabo en España curiosamente este
legal procedure your server is
procedimiento legal su servidor está
being the protagonist of it or good for it
siendo protagonista de él o bueno por lo
less
menos
co-star let's look at the
coprotagonista miremos el
video known in the world of
video conocido en el mundo de los
youtubers like wings is one of the
youtubers como alas es uno de los
most important youtubers in Spanish more
youtubers más importantes es español más
important in Europe I would dare to say
importantes de Europa yo me atrevería a
say that in the world more than 11 million
decir que del mundo más de 11 millones
of followers on YouTube I can tell you
de seguidores en YouTube les puedo
advance that at this time a
adelantar que en estos momentos una
woman a youtuber also who has
mujer una youtuber también que tiene
also hundreds of thousands of followers
también cientos de miles de seguidores
on YouTube is along with his office
en YouTube está junto con su despacho de
lawyers preparing a criminal action
abogados preparando una acción penal
a very harsh complaint against Dallas
durísima contra Dallas una querella
criminal for very serious crimes one of
criminal por delitos gravísimos uno de
the most important law firms
los despachos de abogados más
important in the country are working on
importantes del país están trabajando en
these moments in the ration of this
estos momentos en la racción de esta
complaint and it is a matter of hours of
querella y es cuestión si no de horas de
day they end up presenting themselves in the
día que se acaben presentando en los
played guard of one of the
jugados de guardia de una de las
main capitals of our country
principales capitales de nuestro pa sab
Well, I don't know if he'll say it now about what.
Bueno no sé si lo dirá ahora de qué
the complaint is about me that I was going to
trata la querella sa yo me que iba a
to file a claim for this but it is that
poner una demanda de esta pero es que
see if they are liars
fíjate tú si son mentirosos
Hey, pay attention to this, it just came to me.
eh atentos a esto se me acaba de venir a
the head
la cabeza
bad things has scammed its audience has
cosas mal ha estafado su audiencia ha
have done some very bad practices
hecho unas prácticas muy malas le están
We have also reported him while investigating
investigando le hemos denunciado también
Well a series of things then as a result
Bueno una serie de cosas entonces a raíz
from there even before What happened grandpa
de ahí antes incluso de Qué pasó abuelo
Grandpa, I said it in a sarcastic way or
abuelo que lo dije en modo de Sarcasmo o
irony
ironía
but you can't say that nonsense
pero no puedes decir esa barbaridad de
Today you are banned, you cannot say that
hoy te quas baneado no puedes decir esa
what a barbarity of uncle the people we are
barbaridad de tío de la gente estamos
Here we are commenting on Chile and we are
aquí comentando chile y nos estamos
laughing you can't start saying a thing
riendo no te puedes poner a decir una
thing or precisely because of the can
cosa o sea precisamente por la can
condemned Dalas and More knowing that
condenada Dalas y Más sabiendo que
We are here asking for money asking
estamos aquí pidiendo plata pidiendo
money to us for the wios, [ __ ], eh
plata a nosotros para los wios cabrón eh
and that wasn't enough for the kid.
y el chavón no le bastó con eso que
He grabbed it and made another video to reinforce it.
agarró y hizo otro video para reforzarlo
but no no no I'll take the lawsuit
más no no no la demanda se la llevo
whole and I am very very happy about it
enterita y estoy muy muy contenta de de
announce this because
anunciar esto porque
eh is to leave it here demonstrated that
eh es dejar dejar acá demostrado de que
if you do things
si hac las cosas
you have to be wrong, that is to say, there was already here
mal tenéis que o sea aquí ya había
filed the complaint, okay? And here it hasn't been filed.
puesto la denuncia vale Y aquí no la ha
put the same thing puts it in the
puesto lo mismo la pone en las
next few hours then maybe
siguientes horas entonces a lo mejor
Now if you put it on because now it is
ahora si la pone porque ahora sí se le
have occurred or have made an agreement with
han ocurrido o han hecho un acuerdo con
These people are for TV, you understand me?
esta gente para la tele me entiendes
But you are liars, here you are already
Pero fí tú si son mentirosos que aquí ya
I had put it, that is, the delox and Ricky
la había puesto o sea el delox y Ricky
They are very similar, eh, bad, eh. And
son muy similares eh de malos eh Y de
They go with dirty tricks, eh with lies with
van con guarradas eh con mentiras con
defamations in the following
difamaciones en siguientes
connections we will have more details and
conexiones tendremos más detalles y
we will be able to give much more specificity to the
podremos dar mucha más concreción al
respect this honest journalist
respecto Bueno este honrado periodista
that what is informing us is
que que nos está informando nos está
commenting that there is a supposed youtuber
comentando que hay una supuesta youtuber
with millions of followers
con millones de seguidores
that a criminal procedure has been carried out
que realizado un procedimiento penal
against Mr. Daniel Santomé Lem Bueno
contra el señor Daniel santomé lem Bueno
Guys, that person in case it wasn't clear
chicos esa persona por si no quedó claro
It's me
Soy yo
ok I am very happy very very happy to
ok Estoy muy contenta muy muy feliz de
announce this to you and how good that
anunciarles esto y que bueno que al
less also echo becomes voice of
menos también se haga eco se haga voz de
This is that it's good that people who
esto de que bueno que la gente que
commits crimes said thousands not extremely
comete delitos dijo miles no sumamente
grave is not left
grav no queda
unpunished this gentleman was informed by
impune este este señor fue informado por
my lawyer who is one of the best
mi abogado que es uno de los mejores
Spanish lawyers Javi, do you think so?
abogados de España Javi te parece al
I miss Benjamin's house button among more
extraño casa de Benjamín boton entre más
mature, younger and more handsome, a kiss
madurito más joven y más guapo un beso
Sara Thank you very much I'm glad I'm glad
Sara Muchas gracias Me alegro me alegro
I'm glad that they hit on me
alegro que que me tiren los trastos la
I'm not going to lie to you and that's why he
verdad no te voy a engañar y por eso él
He learned firsthand so he could
se enteró de primera mano para poder
communicate it on your social networks nothing
comunicarlo en sus redes sociales nada
My lawyer is a [ __ ] beast, that is.
mi abogado es una [__] bestia o sea
is
es
Who will be the lawyer one of the
un Quién será el abogado uno de los
best lawyers in Spain who will be
mejores abogados de España quién será
uncle the lawyer who has lent himself to
tío el abogado que se ha prestado para
do this
hacer esto
so very fast, that is to say we are with a
así rapidísimo o sea estamos con un
law firm that was one of the
bufete de abogados que era uno de los
best of Spain of Barcelona It was one
mejores de España de Barcelona Era uno
one of the best in Barcelona but what
de los mejores de Barcelona pero qué
We talked about this matter with my
pasa Hablamos sobre este asunto con mi
lawyer who is also a very good friend
abogado que también es muy buen amigo
our clearing when we had started
nuestro claro cuando habíamos empezado
the procedure against daas we did not have
el procedimiento contra daas no teníamos
who
quién
Who will be the canc that Peres says?
será Quién será el canc que dice peres
Of course if they are in contact with those of
Claro si están en contacto con los de
These people on TV, I think he is capable of
estos de la tele Yo creo que es capaz de
that it be
que sea
I think it's going to be the same lawyer
yo creo que va a ser el el mismo abogado
From Joan Planas I think it's going to be
de de Joan planas Yo creo que es que va
to be Joan's lawyer
a ser el abogado de Joan
Flat, that's a lawyer, Joan Plana.
plana ese es un abogado el de Joan plana
He is a lawyer who is now leading
es un abogado que está con ahora lleva a
Rodolfo Sancho and Raquel boyo a no
Rodolfo Sancho e a a la Raquel boyo a no
I know who you know is used to these
sé quién sabes está acostumbrado a estas
things don't move these little worlds don't and
cosas no se mueven estos mundillos no y
I don't know but of course it says that before
yo no sé pero claro si dice que antes
He was from Barcelona and now he's not, let's see.
era de Barcelona y ahora no a ver De
where is it let's say eh we hadn't talked
dónde es digamos eh no habíamos hablado
a lot or almost nothing with our friend
mucho o casi nada con nuestro amigo
lawyer but recently came to record a
abogado pero hace poco vino a grabar un
podcast and we have spoken a little more with him
podcast y hemos hablado poco más con él
and besides I didn't know him now
y además yo no lo conocía ahora lo
I know him and he has liked me very much and apart from that
conozco y le he caído muy bien y aparte
is a person who is a [ __ ]
es una persona que es una putísima
beast is a person who
bestia es una persona que
and he is too smart in fact he is
e es demasiado inteligente de hecho es
the person can safely say that
la persona puede decir con seguridad que
is the smartest person who
es la persona más inteligente que
I know today Then nothing was
conozco a día de hoy Entonces nada fue
It was as quick as coming to tell him a
fue tan rápido como venir contarle un
little, that is, we tell him as if by chance
poco o sea le contamos como casualmente
what was happening a little by
lo que estaba sucediendo un poco por
above and
encima y
He said, "Okay, let's do something about it."
dijo Okay vamos a hacer algo al respecto
I'm not going to say anything else, nothing, that is and it is
no voy a decir nada más nada o sea y es
and year if you had been born 20 years earlier
y año si hubieses nacido 20 años antes
would be punqui
sería punqui
total none of all the judges that
total ninguno de todos los jueces que de
the resources said
los recursos dicio
have 3 6 9 10 judges 10 judges you
poseen 3 6 9 10 jueces 10 jueces te
they call
llaman
He was guilty not long ago and he already
culpable no fue hace mucho y ya ya le
is giving With everything That is why I say
está dando Con todo O sea Por eso digo
which is fast because it is not like this
que es rápido porque no es como que esto
I started it, or rather, I started this when
lo empecé o sea esto lo empecé cuando
I sent the tweet a few months ago but
mandé el tweet hace unos meses pero
Now we start with this lawyer who is
ahora empezamos con este abogado que es
the best in Spain and was
el mejor de España y fue
ago or rather it was just a little while ago and now it's over
hace o sea fue hace nada y ya le está ya
is giving him
le está dando
hard I am very happy to announce this
duro estoy muy contenta de anunciar esto
the truth is that nothing is done
la verdad que que nada que se haga
justice and also that is, in its time
justicia y también o sea en su momento
He said he had reported it but he didn't.
dijo que había denunciado Pero no lo
there was
había
fact will also be done justice
hecho también se va a hacer justicia
I never looked forward to seeing a
nunca esperé con tantas ganas ver un
Dallas video eh Because Dallas
video de Dallas eh Porque a Dallas lo
They condemned us to go up and see what they were doing.
condenaron a subir a ver par se que
look for the publication I never expected with
buscar la publicación nunca esperé con
I'm so eager to see a video of
tantas ganas a ver un vídeo de
Dallas because it is going to put the ruling on the
Dallas porque va a poner el fallo al
end of the
final del
video he was sentenced to upload a video for
vídeo lo condenaron a subir un video por
week For a month and pay one
semana Durante un mes y a pagar una
compensation of 12000 should eliminate the
indemnización de 12000 debe eliminar los
videos to slander the father of
videos a los que calumniar al padre de
look and also goes to
miare y además va a
having to pay for things is that
tener que pagar las cosas por el es que
I don't know why they talk about slander if not
no sé por qué hablan de calumnia si no
It has been a trial for
ha sido un juicio por
slander, the crazy guy R is here
calumnias [__] el loquito de r está
active on Twitter, he's been there all afternoon
activo en Twitter eh lleva toda la tarde
there all night until now is
ahí toda la noche hasta ahora está
still breastfeeding
teteando todavía
labeling me the appeal to the Supreme Court or
etiquetándome el recurso ante supremo o
2025 is coming to Dallas
2025 para Dallas se le viene una
bombastic look here you have
bombástica mira aquí tenéis
Do you remember that I told you this?
esto os acordáis que os lo he dicho
before
antes
Look, the lady puts a gif of herself alone.
Mira la señora pone un gif de ella sola
laughing, he talks to The Wigs
riéndose habla con El pelucas
Hey lady, you are very old.
Eh señora que está usted muy mayor
It's 2025, blah blah blah, ma'am
estamos en 2025 bla bla bla señora
Tell me who they are going to condemn, huh?
coneta a quién van a condenar eh que
You have been saying for many years that
lleva usted muchos años diciendo que
it will come, it will come, it will come
llegará que va a llegar que va a llegar
Naya Oliveira of the Triplet But there is
naya oliveira d las triplete Pero hay
more obviously obviously
más obviamente obviamente
Madam, madam, now, madam, now, I'm
Señora señora ya señora ya yo ahora me
I'm laughing but the issue for me is
estoy riendo pero a mí el asunto el
the matter of defamation so harsh that
asunto de la difamación tan dura que
Dalas did against me that he accused me of
hizo Dalas contra mí que que me acusó de
sofilia and deedo nñia and a lot of
sofilia y deedo nñia y de un montón de
more super turia [ __ ]
[__] super turias más
and it affected me a lot in its in its
e me afectó muchísimo en su en su
moment and to this day it follows me
momento y hasta el día de hoy me sigue
affecting a lot. I mean, they don't know the
afectando muchísimo O sea no saben la
amount of shitty comments that
cantidad de comentarios de [__] que
I get people saying things
recibo de gente diciendo cosas
disgusting that no or spirit can go
asquerosas que no o sea nimo puede ir
doing this kind of Ay is that some
haciendo este tipo de Ay es que algunos
I deleted them not the t's that Nimu put on me
los borró no los t que me puso nimu los
deleted no
borró no
Ah, it's that he deleted it, that is to say that the
Ah es que lo borró o sea es que los
deleted but of course nimu you have to
borró pero claro nimu tú tienes que
answer when you are going to put to
responder cuando tú vayas a poner a
that you go to other creators and
quella que tú vas a otros creadores y
You tell them they are no more idiots because they are not
les dices no son más [__] porque no
They pay you, stop slandering and go to
te pagan deja de difamar y anda a
chasing your tail and sniffing
perseguirte la cola y oler
asses better the next video be
culos mejor el próximo vídeo que sea
explaining what Dallas's dick tastes like
explicando A qué sabe la pija de Dallas
You've definitely studied that. Of course.
eso sí que te lo tienes estudiado Claro
you are a person who directs you
tú eres una persona que que te dirige
Well, I have the t's that you deleted.
bueno los t que estás borrados los tengo
saved Of course you are a person who
guardados Claro tú eres una persona que
You address the creators like that.
te diriges así a los creadores eso se
always takes into account
tiene en cuenta siempre se tiene en
account of course I don't know if one
cuenta pues claro Yo no sé si una
penalty I don't know if a penalty Marlito a
penal yo no sé si una penal marlito un
kiss I don't tell you maybe that one
beso yo no te digo a lo mejor que una
civil would have made more sense But
civil hubiera tenido más sentido Pero
a penalty with certain What the [ __ ]
una penal con ciertas What the fuck
then of course, I mean I am myself, I am myself
entonces claro o sea yo me estoy yo yo
I am happy here but to get to
acá me estoy contenta pero para llegar a
I had to have a really bad time at this point and
este punto tuve que pasarla muy mal y la
People say Ah But why do you continue
gente dice Ah Pero por qué sigues
Speaking of Dallas, I don't know how much it falls
hablando de Dallas no s cae no sé cuánto
This isn't just about Dallas.
Esto no es solamente hablar de Dallas
This is talked about and apart from that Dallas is not even
esto se habla y aparte que el Dallas ni
He mentions these two, eh? And he continues on
los menciona estos dos eh Y sigue por
balls aunt made a podcast on fearless
[__] tía hizo un podcast en sin miedo
success and by balls I had to encourage
el éxito y por huevos tenía que nimo
Face review of the
Face review d la
review and by egg and in the tser about
review y por huevo y en el tser sobre
dala also, that is to say by eggs I had to
dala también o sea por huevos tenía que
be Dalas Dalas Dalas dala and here a
ser Dalas Dalas Dalas dala y aquí un
podca put it there that he has removed it
podca puso aisi que la ha quitado la ha
changed the thumbnail you know but it's like
cambiado la miniatura sabes pero es como
It's that the other doesn't touch them, it's that the
es que el otro no los topa es que el
another you don't find them haar of something beyond
otro no los topas haar de algo más allá
something that transcends the legal and that
algo que que trasciende a lo legal y Que
Obviously I want to keep my most
obviamente quiero mantener a mi más
The informed community affirms this
afrima comunidad informada Al respecto
because after all with you
porque después de todo con ustedes
I share my days, I share a lot of myself
comparto mis días comparto mucho de mi
life and this is very important because it is not
vida y esto es muy importante porque no
It's just Dallas is
es solamente Dallas es
My career as a streamer, you understand me?
mi mi carrera como streamer me entendés
It's all I've been building up to now
es todo lo que fui construyendo a lo
throughout these years Then I can't
largo de estos años Entonces no puedo
allow a person to overcome so many
permitir que una persona supere tantas
red lines and go unpunished Then
líneas rojas y quede impune Entonces
when it comes to something serious when it comes
cuando se trata de algo serio cuando se
It is about something that surpasses all
trata de algo que que sobrepasa todas
the lines have to be spoken like no No
las líneas hay que hablarlo tipo no No
If one is involved, I cannot remain silent and
se uno yo no me puedo quedar callada y
less when I see it being done
menos cuando veo que se está haciendo
Justice must also set an example
justicia también hay que dar el ejemplo
that people that youtubers that
que la gente que los youtubers que los
These popularizers who call themselves
divulgadores estos que se hacen llamar
informants or whatever it is
informadores o lo que sea que se la
think twice before you say
piensen dos veces antes de decir
lies and defame mm because you can't
mentiras y difamar mm porque no puedes
Let's talk about lies, Nimu. Let's talk.
hablemos de mentira nimu vamos a hablar
of lies
de mentira
nimu let's see if someone comes to your
nimu a ver si se te viene alguien a la
head that has
cabeza que tenga
close order of
cerca orden de
estrangement complaint for
alejamiento denuncia por
threats to police stations in Andorra
amenazas las comisarías de andorra
They close at 3 in the afternoon and you can
cierran a las 3 de la tarde y te puedes
skip any restraining order
saltar cualquier orden de alejamiento
hitmen where is serene
sicarios dónde está serene
make fun of the tumor
burlarse del tumor de
I have a lawyer who appeals to me.
Li tengo a un abogado que me apela los
strikes on YouTube and gets fired
strikes en YouTube y hace que despida a
people who work at YouTube
la gente que que trabaja en YouTube
when they don't accept me
cuando no me aceptan las
appeals that occur to me
apelaciones se me ocurren esas
little lies like that out loud eh
mentirijillas así por lo alto eh Por lo
high Where is it
alto Dónde está
serene Where is it
serene Dónde está
serene and so calm through life
serene y por la vida tan tranquilito
committing crimes
cometiendo delitos
clear bass everything is thrown over him
graves claro todo se le tira por encima
if one remains with one's arms crossed
si uno se queda con los brazos cruzados
Obviously, obviously, obviously, eh, I'm going to continue.
obvio Obvio obvio eh yo voy a continuar
until the end with all these issues and
hasta el final con todos estos temas y
nothing to do justice for me and also
nada hacer justicia por por mí y también
for all the people who were
por todas las personas que fueron
They have been mistreated, psychologically, and that
eh maltratadas eh psicológicamente y que
were ruined by the media
fueron arruinadas mediáticamente por
this
este
character doesn't go No, it doesn't go very well
personaje no va No no va muy bien
First time I became a member Although
primera vez que me hago miembro Aunque
The truth is that I've been watching the gossip for years.
la verdad ya llevo años viendo el salseo
from this channel and fighting with
desde este canal y peleando con
little people XD a hug grandpa Many
gentecita XD un abrazo abuelo Muchas
Thank you, welcome friend, I don't know if
gracias bienvenido amigo no sé yo si de
calling a psychological abuser
lo de llamar maltratador psicológico a
Dallas is coming to you
Dallas te te viene
good
bien
eh or so as I mentioned A person
eh o sea como yo mencioné Una persona
can make opinions and exposition of
puede hacer opiniones y exposición de
cases but when already ray in the
casos pero cuando ya ray en la
defamation is
difamación es
illegal Yes, let's see, he has committed very serious crimes
ilegal Sí a ver ha cometido delitos muy
serious and defamation is only one of
graves y difamación es solamente uno de
They understand me, I'm not one, I'm not
ellos me entienden no soy una yo no soy
lawyer so I'm not going to join
abogada así que me no voy a ingresar
too much in the ma But what I am
demasiado en el ma Pero lo que sí estoy
It is certain that he not only committed a
segura es que no solamente cometió un
crime against me committed some several
delito contra mí cometió algunos varios
I don't know what you're referring to, man.
es que no sé a qué se refiere tío o sea
not even when I first saw the
ni siquiera cuando vi por primera vez el
that clip of the journalist not even
clip ese de el periodista ni siquiera
I fell into who would report Dallas who
caí en quién denunciaría a Dallas quién
Damn, now who the [ __ ] is going to go out?
[__] ahora quién [__] va a salir a
report it and said that with whom What has
denunciarlo dio que con quién Qué ha
done what he said clear I say that's it
hecho qué ha dicho claro yo digo ya está
Miare is going to catch anything again
la miare otra vez va a [__] cualquier
thing and again with his but it is that no
cosa y otra vez con su pero es que no
I have neither
tengo ni
idea is that I have no idea what it is
idea es que no tengo ni idea A qué se
refers to many others
refiere otros muchos
crimes I didn't think about these people I didn't
delitos Yo no pensé en esta gente no me
I remember them as I don't know what they come out to
acuerdo de ellos como no sé cuá salen a
talking about Dallas I don't remember them
hablar de Dallas no me acuerdo de ellos
but of course I understand that I have a demand
pero claro entiendo que yo una demanda
by civil law Well yes, well okay Yes That's it
por lo civil Pues sí bueno vale Sí Esa
Yes, it can go well for you because man, if there is
sí te puede ir bien porque hombre si ha
said a strong thing about you no and
dicho una cosa fuerte sobre ti no y
It stains your image, the civilians know it goes
mancha tu imagen las civiles sabes va
about safe more or less more or less
sobre seguro más o menos más o menos
because you never know, but one
porque tampoco se sabe nunca no pero una
penalty one
penal una
penalty whatever the hell they're going to put in
penal sea qué [__] es lo que van a meter
Well that's probably what this will be.
Pues eso seguramente será esto
It is surely content for the
seguramente es contenido para el
podcast Yes but many crimes Minerva Y
podcast Sí pero muchos delitos Minerva Y
to mals the dog for for what
a mals lo del perro por por lo
penalty has been made is content for
penal se se ha hecho es contenido para
the podcast in exchange for that of the
el podcast a cambio de para el de la
There is no more TV, they have tried to see if
tele no hay más han intentado a ver si
with the journalist and taking advantage of what
con lo del periodista y aprovechando lo
From today's miare this exploded and it was
de miare de hoy esto explotaba y era
2017 and such and they try every month eh And
2017 y tal y y lo intentan cada mes eh Y
This is another topic tomorrow and tomorrow
esto ya mañana es otro tema y mañana
We are talking about Juan Guarnizo and this
estamos hablando de Juan guarnizo y esto
no no I don't know, they don't understand that no eh no
no no se no entienden que no eh no
They understand that
entienden que
no eh
no eh
The lawyer made it quite easy, huh?
al abogado se la puso bastante fácil eh
I mean, I'm telling you the truth, this lawyer
o sea te digo la verdad este abogado
defends alleged criminals
defiende a presuntos criminales
extremely dangerous
peligrosísimos
bad guys and defends them and takes them out
chungos y los defiende y los saca
and you take it out, that is, you take it out innocent men
e y lo saca o sea lo sacas inocentes men
Be careful, hide, Nimu will eat me. Not me.
cuidado escondan que nimu me zampa No yo
no dude really I mean [ __ ] it's that
no tío de verdad O sea [__] es que
You put some things that are not there, man.
ponéis unas cosas que no tío eso está
bad I can't allow that and I
mal eso no te lo puedo permitir y me
You're doing it there, you bastards, and you're not doing it there.
estáis haciendo ahí cabrones y ahí no os
I can ban you, dude. But that's not it.
puedo banear tío Pero eso no eso
No, they are not things that the girl finds funny.
no no son cosas que la chavala la gracia
I mean, the vast majority gets it right.
lo O sea la gran mayoría lo saca bien a
I think that if not to say all of them had me
la por no decir todos creo que me había
commented that he had not lost as
comentado que no había perdido como
no case of any criminal having
ningún caso de ningún criminal que haya
defended, that is, you think that one
defendido o sea vos pensas que una
top-notch criminal lawyer
abogado penalista de altísima de
very high reputation, you understand me
altísima reputación me entendés
Imagine
imagínate
Imagine not defending a criminal but
imagínate no defender a un criminal sino
defend an innocent woman who also has
defender a una inocente que encima Tiene
all of them
todas las de
win allegedly allegedly has
ganar presuntamente presuntamente tiene
To win must be said presumably before
ganar hay que decir presuntamente ante
all
todo
you saw spirit you know Mr. you saw his
viste nimo conoces a Mr vist a sus
friends no O
amigos no O
be not What the [ __ ] because What the
sea no What the fuck porque What the
[ __ ]
fuck
And cheer up, but no, it can't be done.
e nimo pero que no que no se puede
I can comment on these cases by law.
comentar estos casos por ley yo puedo
comment on what I want, what you do
comentar lo que yo quiera lo que vos si
You comment more than I have done. Yes
comentas de más que no lo he hecho Si
you comment too much
comentas de más te
It could play against your case, that is.
pued jugar en contra para tu caso o sea
if you say something
si vos decís algo
and that which can play against you plays against you
e que que puede jugar en contra te juega
against and that's it from there I guess
en contra y ya está de ahí Supongo que
There are certain cases, eh?
Hay ciertos casos eh
particular that certain things are not
particulares que ciertas cosas no se
They may say but I have not said anything
podrán decir pero yo no he dicho nada
that I can't say I'm measuring
que no pueda decir estoy midiendo
quite my words although not
bastante mis palabras aunque no lo
It seems like, eh, I mean, I'm well informed, right?
parezca eh o sea estoy bien informada no
HE
se
worry he saw you with my poodle from
preocupen te vio Con mi caniche desde
Buenos Aires Hello Nico, I'm sending you a
Buenos Aires Hola Nico te mando un
I greet you and yours
saludo a vos y a tu
poodle in fact encouragement is Mr. Beisner
caniche de hecho animo es Mr beisner
Okay, but guys, I know that's a topic.
Bueno pero eso chicos sé que es un tema
that maybe it will put you a little
que quizás a ustedes les ponga un poco
the hairs the goosebumps no Or maybe
los pelos la piel de gallina no O quizás
I caused them a little fear for me because of what
les cause un poco de miedo por mí por lo
that I can say I don't know
que yo pueda llegar a decir No se
Don't worry, this is good news
preocupen que esto es una buena noticia
it's for it's like like for
está para está como como para para
celebrate but celebrate for justice
festejar pero festejar por la justicia
that I trust that justice will be done and
que yo confío en que se hacer justicia y
Justice is the most beautiful thing there is
la justicia es de lo más bonito que hay
that it be done and see it being carried out or
que se haga y verla llevándose a cabo o
We are happy because there is
sea Estamos contentos porque hay
justice and that the people who commit
justicia y que las personas que cometen
crimes allegedly not because he committed
crímenes presuntamente no porque cometió
real crimes
crímenes de verdad
and crimes
e crímenes
don't get away with it basically That's it
no salgan impunes básicamente Eso es
That's all I have to say
todo eso es todo lo que tengo para decir
don't be afraid, don't be afraid
que no les de miedo que no les de miedo
and that there is no need to be afraid of it, there is no need to be afraid of it
y que no Hay que tenerle miedo hay que
one has to
hay que
we must be fair and talk about the
ser hay que ser justos y hablar de los
topics when it comes to
temas cuando hay que
talk to them when you feel
hablarlos sea cuando una senten
statement or your journalist friend
comunicado o tu amigo periodista
crimes colleague crimes
crímenes colega crímenes
Saul Gman's crimes against Pablo are that
crímenes saul gman contra Pablo es que
I don't know who she is part of because she
no sé quiénes forma parte porque ella
says he is a co-star of the
dice que es coprotagonista de la
complaint no Then I don't know who to complain to
querella no Entonces no sé con quién la
is going to put Because if he is going to put it with
va a poner Porque si la va a poner con
Of course, Paul cannot represent Delox.
delox claro Pablo no puede representar a
Dallas in that case there is one
Dallas en ese caso hay una
incompatibility do we have that luare or what
incompatibilidad tenemos eso luare o qué
or what
o qué
I see, let's see Fran's thing, no guys, by
veo vamos a ver lo de Fran no chicos por
end Well tomorrow Fran leaves
fin Bueno mañana mañana sale Fran
doing a live show that I don't know what
haciendo un directo lo que no sé a qué
now it's going to do it still worth it I think
hora lo va a hacer todavía vale Creo que
It's not clear yet, but there it is.
todavía no ha quedado claro eh pero ahí
they are
lo están
talking I don't know what time it will be
hablando No sé a qué hora van a ser
live but tomorrow Fran will play
directo pero mañana hará Fran jugando a
the game is worth it You already know that fortnite
al juego vale Ya sabéis que fortnite
has
tiene
a multiplayer mode okay this I know
una un modo multijugador vale esto lo sé
I for this because you already know that
yo por esto porque esto ya sabéis que
fortnite I have no idea what I played
fortnite no tengo ni idea jugué A qué
tournament was to the one of no O is fatal
torneo fue al del de no O sea fatal
fatal fatal fatal no but I will play this
fatal fatal fatal no pero esto jugaré de
done I wonder if I do
hecho me planteo me planteo que si hago
the extendable if I make the extendable
el extensible si hago el extensible
finally on Sunday I don't know if it has
finalmente el domingo Es que no sé si ha
the extendable the truth because I don't
el extensible la verdad porque yo no
I think people are going to donate to us now or
creo que la gente nos vaya a donar ya o
I think it is who wanted to donate
sea yo creo que quien ha querido donar
to the box has already donated Eh
para para la caja ha donado ya Eh
So I don't know if it has to be extensible or
entonces yo no sé si ha ser extensible o
no reason to open it so that in half an hour
no porque abrir para que a la media hora
we don't have to close no I don't know the
no tengamos que cerrar no no lo sé la
I really don't know, but I had thought that
verdad no sé Pero había pensado que
part of the extensible at least to the
parte del extensible por lo menos a lo
better the first part such as playing the map
mejor la primera parte tal jugar al mapa
play the full map with Leo would play
jugar al mapa completo con Leo jugaría
with Leo of course I would put here without camera and
con Leo claro pondría aquí sin cámara y
we had such a laugh that you already knew it
nos echamos una una risa que ya se lo ñ
to him in the in the I have already told him
a él en el en el ya se lo ya se lo he
taught to him in
enseñado a él en
the one in the videos that I have the map or that is
el en los vídeos que tengo el mapa o sea
This is a map in Fortnite.
esto es un esto es un mapa en fortnite
you have a player mode in which there is
tienes un modo jugador en el que hay
maps okay And this is a way to win
mapas vale Y esto es una forma de ganar
money the creator of the map creates this
dinero el creador del mapa esto lo crea
a company is worth And then the company
una empresa vale Y entonces la empresa
Well, when what happened happened, well,
Pues cuando pasó lo que pasó pues
contacted me so that good is a
contactó conmigo para que bueno es un
My friend, le chochi is worth it, I don't know if it
amigo mío le chochi vale que no sé si lo
You will know that other maps have been made for
conoceréis de ha hecho otros mapas para
Vegeta and these people are not good friends with
Vegeta y esta gente no bueno es amigo de
Vegeta, okay, I've known him for a long time.
Vegeta vale yo lo conozco hace mucho
time and he contacted me and told me
tiempo y él me contactó y me dijo
Le Chochi's name is not Lexi or Lexi.
de le chochi no se llama No sé Lexi o
Something like that is not pronounced La Movida is
algo así no se se pronuncia La Movida es
who contacted me and said uncle I have this
que me contactó y me dijo tío tengo esta
idea What do you think? It seemed to me
idea Qué te parece a mí me pareció
spectacular the idea of ​​the first moment
espectacular la idea del primer momento
eh And he told it to I told it to Fran I say
eh Y se lo dijo a se lo dije a Fran digo
Fran this is [ __ ] crazy man, I mean
Fran esto es una [__] locura tío o sea
very handsome and he is the [ __ ], I mean he is the
guapísimo y es la [__] o sea es la
I don't know if I've taught much here.
[__] no sé si aquí enseñado mucho
because we have the videos of all the
porque tenemos los vídeos de todo el
complete map, well there won't be any here
mapa completo buen aquí no habrá
taught everything but it's the [ __ ] is the
enseñado todo pero es la [__] es la
[ __ ] or rather very handsome very handsome
[__] o sea guapísimo guapísimo
very handsome one thing Now is that it is the
guapísimo una cosa Ahora es que es el
sanctuary literally Because in addition it
santuario literalmente Porque además lo
They have made a copy of the map, eh? Well.
han hecho calcando lo del mapa eh Bueno
Guys, the surprise is coming here and
chavales pues la sorpresa viene aquí y
is that tomorrow is Friday
es que mañana viernes
Hey, let's introduce the game now.
eh vamos a presentar ya el juego de
fortnite the map the map of de
fortnite el mapa el mapa de de
fortnite is a type map
fortnite es un mapa de tipo
creative the game is kind of type
creativo el juego es tipo de tipo
creative let's see what the hell Fran knows
creativo a ver qué [__] sabe Fran Lo que
creative type I don't know nor am I
de tipo creativo No lo sé ni yo est se
the other kid said it, let him say it
la ha dicho el otro chaval que lo diga
tyon which is called taon and is a map
tyon que se llama taon y es un mapa un
game in which Well we are going to put
juego en el cual Bueno vamos a poner
images there you are seeing the images
imágenes ahí estáis viendo las imágenes
In you you see the sanctuary, the map
en ustedes veis el santuario el mapa
comparing it the sanctuary is literal
comparándolo el santuario es literal
okay, so it's like you're going to go for it
vale o sea es como que Vais a ir por el
sanctuary but in a way
santuario pero de manera
measure the fences are measured is
medida las vallas están medidas es
exactly the same houses everything is
exactamente lo mismo las casas todo es
exactly the same V because you start
exactamente lo mismo V pues Tú empiezas
Let's see if I'm not mistaken from
a ver si no me equivoco desde
Here clearly this is the camp
aquí claramente Este es el campamento
This is the camp here you enter here
Este es el campamento aquí se entra aquí
leave the car here Fran is worth it
deja aquí deja el coche Fran vale por
Here we pull and here is the goat
aquí tiramos y por aquí está la cabra
Okay, this is where Plex sleeps.
vale por aquí es donde duerme plex aquí
exactly more or less where ple sleeps
exactamente más o menos donde duerme ple
Here a chicken attacked me okay here it is
aquí me atacó una gallina vale Aquí está
the goat and now this way if you go
la cabra y ahora por aquí si vais
[Music]
[Música]
if not me
si no me
mistaken for
equivoco por
here is a way here is another but
aquí hay un camino aquí hay otro pero
Well here's another one for the
bueno por aquí hay otro para las
ostriches, here is the entrance
avestruces por aquí está la entrada por
where We have entered the
donde Nosotros hemos entrado a las
ostriches always worth it here is another one
avestruces siempre vale aquí hay otra
I've never been there, okay, but here there is
que yo nunca ha ido vale pero aquí hay
Here is the path where the
un Aquí está el camino donde van las
Here's the snake thing
avestruces Aquí está lo de la serpiente
and
y
[Music]
[Música]
I'm smoking an amazing joint
la me Estoy fumando un porro increíble
eh sanctuary
eh santuario
of no no no of course No wait for us
de no no no claro No espera nosotros
We entered the vruce through here.
entramos a la vruce por aquí nosotros
We enter the vruce through here, okay. Here.
entramos a la vruce por aquí vale Aquí
There is the meerkat thing which is this
está lo de la suricata que es este
clear little square It's that here we are
cuadradito claro Es que aquí estamos de
far away Of course we are far away it seems
lejos Claro que estamos de lejos parece
very small but clear This is the thing about the
muy pequeño pero claro Esto es lo de los
Meerkats And this is the serpentarium
suricatos Y esto es la el serpentario
this is the reptiles this is the
esto es los reptiles esto es los
reptiles and I have not come here or come here
reptiles y yo para acá para acá no he
past me here is that beach where
pasado yo aquí tiene la playa esa donde
he recorded himself being an idiot over here
se grabó haciendo el gilipolla para acá
I haven't been through all this, it's the savannah
no he pasado yo todo esto es la sabana
all this is the savannah here in the
todo esto es la sabana que aquí en la
platform where they put Pablo and
plataforma donde pusieron a Pablo y
then Here is the other entry of the
luego Aquí está la otra entrada de la
savannah which is where here where
sabana que es por donde aquí por donde
This dog is lost here, here, here
está perrito por aquí por aquí perdido
This dog is fine. And now, no, no.
está perrito vale Y ya para acá que no
you can see what the lake and all that is now
se ve lo que el lago y todo eso ahora se
Hey
eh
Okay
vale
Look, it still doesn't look the same.
mira todavía no se ve se ve lo mismo
So you have to fight with zombies.
tienes pues que pelearte con zombis de
from time to time you have to go doing
vez en cuando tienes que ir haciendo
This is the Aryan reptilian stuff.
esto Esto es lo del reptili ario cosas
getting money for the house
consiguiendo dinero para la casa de
Paloma build everything that is the
Paloma ir construyendo todo lo que es el
sanctuary and once you are
santuario y una vez que estás
building the sanctuary and you go
construyendo el santuario y vas
getting more challenges and more challenges then
consiguiendo más retos y más retos pues
you can start getting animals
puedes empezar a a conseguir animales
dude it's literal eh I mean it's literal
tío es literal eh o sea es literal
it's going to be sparks
va a estar chispas
Plexi good puppy there will be
plexi perrito bueno va a haber
different animals that are in
diferentes animales de los que está en
the sanctuary is worth the ones you are going to go to
el santuario vale los cuales tú vas a ir
bringing it as an uncle Look at the fence, eh?
trayendo de tío Fíjate en la valla eh
Look, okay, which ones you're going to go to, dude.
Mira vale los cuales tú vas a ir tío
Look at the fence, eh?
Fíjate en la valla eh de los
balls bringing
[__] trayendo
little by little from Fran's house according to
de de poco a poco la casa de Fran según
you advance in the game is a game
vas avanzando en el juego es un juego
Well the game of the sanctuary is to say there is
Pues el juego del santuario es decir hay
that you are building it, you are seeing that
que ir construyéndolo estáis viendo que
it is a replica
es una réplica
to a perfect replica of the sanctuary Y
a una réplica perfecta del santuario Y
the truth Let's see a perfect replica
la verdad A ver una réplica perfecta
You are seeing that it is a type of game, yes.
estáis viendo que es tipo juego sí que
It's impossible to be more perfect in Fortnite.
más perfecto en el fortnite es imposible
do it You know there are things that I don't
hacerlo Sabes que hay cosas que yo no
I knew this could be done in Fortnite.
sabía que esto se poda hacer en fortnite
Uncle This is literal
tío Es que esto es literal
Okay, it's not a video, it's a video game.
vale No es un vídeo es un videojuego
So it's a replica of what it is
Entonces es una réplica de lo que de lo
that would be the sanctuary and man is
que sería el santuario y hombre está
well because because whoever likes it
bien porque pues porque al que le gusta
This sanctuary and man is fine
esto santuario y hombre está bien
because because whoever likes this
porque pues porque al que le gusta esto
[ __ ] Not done thanks I don't know the
[__] No hecho gracias No sé los
content creators who have wanted
creadores de contenido que han querido
Always support and say I support you
Siempre apoyar y decir yo te apoyo el
sanctuary Well look yes this is now safe
santuario Pues mira sí esto ahora seguro
that all these will play Vegeta and everything
que jugarán todos estos el Vegeta y todo
the now all the creators of
el ahora todos los creadores de
content what you can do is
contenido lo que podéis hacer es de
Somehow, play it one day
alguna manera pues jugarlo un día para
Let the people who are in play it
que lo juegue la gente que está en
your chats and in your live broadcasts And
vuestros chats y en vuestros directos Y
So well, that's what we get from there.
así pues bueno de ahí de lo que se saca
there where the goat is, do you remember?
ahí donde está la cabra os acordáis no
We have given ourselves a percentage and
nosotros nos dado un tanto por cento y
It is for the sanctuary is one of the things
es para el santuario es una de las cosas
that this company Well when it came out
que que esta empresa Pues cuando salió
The whole point of the problem is that it is
todo el tema del del problema es que es
I don't know how I don't understand how it can
igual No sé có no entiendo cómo puede
be so Same good grandfather extendable
ser tan Igual buenas abuelo extensible
Yes or yes Look let's do it like this for each
Sí o sí Mira hagámoslo así por cada
new member 5 minutes and for each Oar
miembro nuevo 5 minutos y por cada Remo
one minute and for every dollar donation
un minuto y por cada dólar donación
donated 3 and you limit it to 6 hours and if
donado 3 y lo limitas a 6 horas y si
you spend extra time on others
sobra tiempo lo pasas para el otro
extensible so others do it to see
extensible así le hacen otros a ver
Write me on WhatsApp because I don't
Escríbemelo por por WhatsApp que no me
It's been a long time since I read you.
ha dado tiempo a leerte ha pasado muy
Quickly let's see that we all see it and let's see
rápido a ver que lo veamos todos y a ver
if we think so
si nos parece
well let's see what we see
bien a ver que lo veamos
everyone put it to me on WhatsApp
todos pónmelo por WhatsApp las
conditions and we see them here okay when
condiciones y las vemos aquí vale cuando
we were about to lose the sanctuary
estuvimos a punto de perder el santuario
Well, they offered to do this
pues ellos se ofrecieron a hacer este
map for fortnite you want it all in
mapa para fortnite lo quieres todo en
Javi silver tray No sau is that yes
bandeja de plata Javi No sau es que si
I'm going to spend 12 hours here on Sunday
me voy a pegar 12 horas aquí el domingo
to win 500 host That's what I'm getting for
para ganar 500 [__] Para eso me pongo
to make a video of the main I put myself
a hacer vídeo del principal Me pongo
make content you understand me or I mean I have
hacer contenido me entiendes o sea tengo
that see that What is the way that we
que ver que Cuál es la forma que nos
is more interested in earning more money
interesa más de ganar más plata
and then the extensives too
y y aparte luego los extensives también
If you are super exhausted, they are not interesting either.
si estás super agotado tampoco interesan
a lot of uncle and give us a point for enough
mucho tío y darnos un tanto por bastante
stop the truth
alto la verdad
and of the income that was
e de los ingresos que se fueran
generating Well I don't know how they are generated
generando Pues no sé cómo se generan los
income from here from the game but oh well
ingresos de aquí del juego pero bueno
But basically tomorrow we are going
pero vamos que básicamente mañana vamos
to be playing so you can see it
a estar jugando para que lo veáis nos
We will connect live and you will see it in
conectaremos en directo y lo veréis en
direct and nothing and I hope you like it
directo y nada y espero que os guste al
whoever likes it and whoever doesn't like it, well
que le guste y al que no le guste pues
that he doesn't like me, what do you want me to do?
que no le guste yo que queréis que os
Say But come on that was it that was it
diga Pero vamos que eso era la eso era
the surprise that nothing was there
la sorpresa que nada ahí estaba la
little surprise that I wanted to give you that already
sorpresita que os Quería dar que ya
Tomorrow we start and you can already start
mañana empezamos y ya podéis empezar a
come down from tomorrow after
bajaros a partir de mañana después de
Let's play, I don't have a [ __ ] clue
que Juguemos nosotros yo tengo ni [__]
Now how to play So if I can
ya Cómo se juega Así que si yo puedo
play tomorrow anyone can play
jugar mañana cualquiera puede jugar
Come tomorrow, for today is for you
venga mañana que para ustedes hoy
[Music]
[Música]
Now let's see what Wizard says about each one.
ya a ver lo que dice wizard es cada
member you add 4 hours to the clock V to
miembro le sumas 4 horas al reloj V a
suck it
chuparla
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
ad the style the animals are super
ad el estilo los animales son super
cool uncle the animals the style of the
chulos tío los animales el estilo de los
those animals are super cool
animal esos son super chulos
[Music]
[Música]
and how handsome, eh, man, he's going to be very handsome
y que guapo eh tío va a estar muy guapo
Hey Javi, do you play it on the expandable? Yes.
eh Javi lo juegas en el extensible Sí
Man, if there is an extension, we play it.
hombre si hay extensible lo jugamos
obviously
evidentemente
[Music]
[Música]
Grandpa, I know a couple of streamers with
abuelete conozco un par de streamers con
a lot of audience that can play this
mucha audiencia que pueden jugar a esto
I'm going to tell you about it. Yes, surely.
Se los voy a comentar Sí seguramente a
See, I understand that these people will play
ver yo entiendo que esta gente jugarán
almost all of them, that is, the Fran sanctuary
casi todos o sea el santuario de Fran
I think that almost everyone is going to
yo creo que casi todo el mundo se va a
lend to
prestar a
[Music]
[Música]
play, that is, you are doing it
jugar o sea tú vas haciendo
things and then the rest appears
cosas y entonces va apareciendo lo demás
Look at the little fence
Mira la vallita por
Here That is the little fence on the side of the
aquí Esa es la vallita de la parte del
service the little fence on this side
servicio la vallita de es lado
that will be the one for me
eso me será la
pool let's see he says
piscina a ver dice
w for each new member 5 minutes that goes
w por cada miembro nuevo 5 minutos qu va
wale for each resusscription one minute
wale por cada resus cripción un minuto
that goes wale for each
que va wale por cada
dollar 3 minutes that one is there
dólar 3 minutos ese sí está
well and you limit it to 6 hours but of course
bien y lo limitas a 6 horas pero claro
more is missing
falta más
nocito As a friend A kiss to Argentina to
nocito Cómo amigo Un beso a Argentina a
an extension for each member for one hour
un extensible por cada miembro una hora
talking about Where is Serene a kiss to
hablando de Dónde está serene un beso a
see what W says is every dollar 3
ver lo que dice W es cada dólar 3
minutes every dollar 3 minutes would be every
minutos cada dólar 3 minutos sería cada
member 3 minutes
miembro 3 minutos
also with a limit I don't know what it would be
también con un tope Yo no sé cuál sería
the top uncle I think the top should
el tope tío Yo creo que el tope Debería
be like 12 hours no and you are from
ser como como 12 horas no y estás desde
12 until 12 and in between I invite you
las 12 hasta las 12 y por medio invito a
Trium by means of invitation
trium por medio invito
I had thought about inviting a live show to
a había pensado invitar a un directo a
Angry little guy we're talking about
tipito enojado que estamos hablando
Now about this topic of
ahora del tema este de
Michelo no
michelo no
I know Princess is invited
sé a Princesita la invitamos
We could also invite her but I
también la podríamos invitar pero yo
I think it could be something like that yes for each
creo que podría ser algo así sí por cada
dollar 3 minutes for every dollar 3 minutes
dólar 3 minutos por cada dólar 3 minutos
either in Go funding or in
ya sea en el en el Go funding o en
the or not here
el o aquí no
For every 3 minutes there are 240 12 hours
por cada D 3 minutos Son 240 12 hora
which poncito can I invite? It's that
cuá poncito puedo invitar a Es que lo
What happens is that he is with his family
que pasa es que está con la familia
Now that's why it's a little bit
ahora por eso está un poquito
disappeared too but maybe
desaparecio también pero a lo mejor
invited a
invitado un
a while
rato
there the little pool of the ones
ahí la piscinita de la de las
otters 5 a minute clear that's right that's right
nutrias 5 un minuto claro eso sí eso sí
five members sounds better one
suena mejor cinco miembros un
minute Look at the pool uncle Look at the
minuto Mira la piscina tío Mira las
pool stones uncle is perfect
piedras de la piscina tío está perfecto
I didn't know that this could be done like this
yo no sabía que esto se puede hacer así
Hey This
Eh Esto
what is this
qué esta
This table
mesa Esta
this piece of furniture wall
pared este mueble
[Music]
[Música]
Oh look, it's Villa.
Ah mira es Villa
smell
olira
Okay, okay, I've got it.
bueno bueno ya lo
You will see how Abi did it, let's see how it is done.
veréis así lo hizo Abi a ver cómo lo
Abi did a sub 2 minute 100
hizo Abi un sub 2 minutos 100
bit 1 one
bit 1 un
minute 1 1
minuto 1 1
minute 1 a minute could be Yes
minuto 1 un minuto podría ser Sí
good good let's see anyway
buenos bueno a ver de todas
ways yes 1 a minute Yes it could be 1
maneras sí 1 un minuto Sí podría ser 1
one minute yes we could do it
un minuto sí lo podríamos hacer
1 eur a minute yes we could do it yes
1 eur un minuto sí lo podríamos hacer sí
we are from
estamos de
agreement with a
acuerdo con un
stop then in the end people are going to have
tope luego al final la gente va a ha
people who are going to give more, that is me
gente que va que va a dar más O sea yo
I think that we would pass that limit there.
creo que ahí sí pasaríamos con ese tope
Yes it could be but you think that
Sí podría ser pero ustedes creéis que
we have 12 hours to fill
tenemos para rellenar 12 horas
Uncle, I would have to make a plan for him
tío tendría que hacerme un planning el
Saturday rest the whole time to be
sábado descansar lo entero para estar
with my son totally
con mi hijo totalmente
and you would like that you can do that and
y os apetecería eso tú puedes con eso y
more Javi yes we can do it
más Javi sí lo podemos hacer os
I would like that but I would do it here
apetecería eso pero yo lo haría aquí
Hey, I think I would do it here, Javi.
eh yo creo que lo haría aquí eh Javi
Watch this video of Ricky edit is the
Mira este video de Ricky edit es el
reacting to a song without saying
reaccionando a una canción Sin decir
nothing and without stopping the song So it is
nada y sin parar la canción O sea que es
practically the song
prácticamente la canción
The whole thing is going to tell you a kiss. Many
entera te va a decir un beso Muchas
Thanks for the donation, he'll tell you
gracias por la donación te va a decir
that he had permission is going to go to you
que él tenía permiso te va a
say 50 half an hour says
decir 50 media hora dice
Chari but Chari 50 half an hour what
Chari pero Chari 50 media hora qué
sense 50 half an hour what sense does it have
sentido 50 media hora qué sentido tiene
It's a lot, no, people are not going to let go.
es mucho no la gente no va a largar
Half an hour is not going to give you 50 bucks
media hora no va a dar 50 pavos por
average
media
time I also want people to
hora Yo también quiero que la gente lo
I contributed, do you understand me? Because if we put
lo aporte me entiendes Porque si ponemos
we have to cut a lot
una barbaridad tenemos que cortar
nothing 50 half an hour would be pretty good
nada 50 media hora estaría bastante bien
because we gave him a push of 1000
porque le pegamos un empujón de de 1000
turkeys on Sunday
pavos en el domingo me
you understand I don't know the truth I don't know
entiendes No sé la verdad no sé a
you guys really want to
ustedes os apetece muchísimo
That's me. In part yes, but I don't have it.
eso yo En parte sí pero no lo tengo no
It's not because I don't feel like it, eh?
no es porque no me apetezca eh que no
It would be wrong not to do a little thing either
estaría mal tampoco hacer una cosita
you know but no it's not that it's not that like
sabes pero no no es eso no es eso como
maybe it doesn't work because I see
tal sino que no funcione porque yo veo
that people have already donated a lot, man
que ya la gente ha donado mucho tío
I see that people have already donated
Yo veo que ya la gente ha donado
I also tell you a lot is an extensible
mucho también te digo es un extensible
With a limit we might not make it to 12
con tope a lo mejor no llegamos a las 12
hours Well, if we get to 5 hours
horas Bueno pues si llegamos a 5 horas
Well, not 5 hours, but of course no no no no
pues 5 horas no pero claro no no no no
It wouldn't be clear because the first hour wouldn't be
no sería Claro porque la primera hora no
count the first hour we do it And to
cuenta la primera hora la hacemos Y a
from there we started Of course but
partir de ahí arrancamos Claro pero
well then I would do you know No I don't know the
bueno entonces haría sabes No no sé la
I'm telling you the truth, suddenly what
verdad que te digo repente es que lo que
I see that people have donated a lot already.
veo es que la gente ha donado mucho ya
for the box then it is not because it is not
para la caja entonces no es porque no
want to do it but because I think that
quiera hacerlo sino porque creo que que
maybe Rick finally edited put a
puede que finalmente Rick edit puso un
that now we see This is worth it but because
esa ahora vemos Esto vale sino porque
I think they might not support us much.
creo que puede que no nos apoyen mucho
Yeah, but suddenly, maybe people
ya pero de repente A lo mejor la gente
She goes crazy, eh. I also tell you, that is.
se vuelve loca eh También te digo o sea
Today there are still people who have
hoy todavía hay gente que ha
donated a follower has donated today I think
donado una seguidora ha donado hoy creo
that there have been 200 around there eh
que han sido 200 por ahí eh
200 have donated today
200 ha donado hoy una
follower who is almost The most donation
seguidora que es casi La donación más
Big, I'm going to the bathroom for a second and we'll see
grande voy al baño un segundo y vemos
This
Esto
worth to
vale al
Well, I think we're going to get the last one.
Pues yo creo que vamos a sacar el último
excerpt eh man Because I want to record the
extracto eh tío Porque Quiero grabar el
video for the main one and we already have
vídeo para el principal y llevamos ya
almost two hours east of Nauter
casi dos horas el villo este de nauter
In the end I drag it I will never see it and
al final lo arrastrar no lo veré nunca y
I won't find out what Juan's thing is, but it is
no me enteraré que es lo de Juan pero es
what a guy we have a lot of
que tío es que tenemos un montón de
move It's that I want to record for the
movida Es que quiero grabar para el
main a little video that I think makes
principal un videíto que creo que hace
Missing guys, I'm going to see what I have
falta chicos voy a ver que me ha
compiled luare and told me that
recopilado luare y me ha dicho que
Let's see the good thing, how they have reacted more
veamos lo bueno cómo han reaccionado más
that nothing the creators to the strike of
que nada los creadores al strike de
Ricky Eddy is worth more than anything to know
Ricky Eddy vale más que nada para saber
a little bit of the opinions that there have been
un poco las opiniones que que ha habido
in the movement that I have been I super
en la movida que he estado Yo super
I'm really confused, well, the thing about Dallas, yes.
hiper me liado bueno lo de Dallas sí lo
I read it and retweeted it, Rique Son.
he leído lo he retuiteado rique son
Fosit is one of the most popular characters
fosit es uno de los personajes más
brutally pathetic that there are besides
brutalmente patéticos que hay además de
cry on his day for having dedicated himself to
llorar en su día por haberse dedicado a
revisit my entire debate with Naim that
restrear íntegro mi debate con naim que
This does affect the final source video.
eso sí perjudica el vídeo origen final
Now he goes and gives you a strike for 5
ahora va y te pone un strike por 5
seconds of a 40 video the same Nor
segundos de un vídeo de 40 igual Tampoco
I know why you played that garbage music
sé por qué pusiste esa basura de música
Ah this this t was from the first day okay
Ah este este t fue del primer día vale
If they call themselves that, they are Verreos
si es que se hace llamar así son verreos
disgusting that gives a brutal cringe and even
asquerosos que da un cringe brutal y aún
He becomes an artist with Público de Nene de
se crea artista con Público de Nene de
10 years who applaud his antics
10 años que aplauden sus payasadas
you infest in case it didn't humiliate him enough
infestas por si no lo humill suficiente
already in the debate here it was again
ya en el debate aquí se volvió a
humiliate himself here he has humiliated himself
humillar él solo aquí se ha humillado él
eh, I mean, I don't know if Ricky, I think that
eh o sea yo no sé si Ricky yo creo que
Yes, I think Ricky is aware of
sí eh yo creo que Ricky es consciente de
how bad it has been with this and
lo mal que ha quedado con esto y de
how much he has humiliated himself because he has
cuánto se ha humillado porque es que ha
It's been terrible, they've written to me a lot
quedado fatal me han escrito un montón
from creators, uncle in uncle mode, what a thing
de creadores tío en plan tío vaya vaina
the ricking but then I don't know if it is
el ricking pero luego no sé si se lo
They will say it to your face too, I tell you, but
dirán en la cara también te digo pero
because many have written to me but it is
porque me han escrito muchos pero es
like dude what are you doing I mean what the [ __ ] are you doing
como tío Qué haces O sea qué [__] haces
Uncle, why are you doing this, uncle?
tío A qué viene que hagas esto tío y
especially with the one that the Ally Because
sobre todo con la que el Aliado Porque
If it was a guy that you say, well no
si fuera un tío que tú dices Bueno no
use content from anyone or never
utiliza contenido de nadie o nunca le
They have put a strike and have never had it
han puesto un strike y nunca ha tenido
but of course, man, what the [ __ ] with the face?
que pero claro tío con la car qué [__]
it has been left in a terrible state
ha quedado fatal
Well, and this thing about 10-year-old children
bueno Y esto de los niños de 10 años la
What Ricky did, I don't know if he uploaded it.
que lió a el Ricky yo no sé si la subió
and your main one is not that in theory
ya el principal suyo no eso en teoría
I was like clapping and stuff like that.
estaba así aplaudiendo y esas cosas era
to upload it to your channel
para subirla a su canal
he won't upload it tomorrow or whatever
no lo subirá mañana o lo que sea no
Of course I understand that this will be raised.
Claro entiendo que eso lo va a subir
edited to his to his move and to his to his
editado a su a su movida y a su a su
Style does not convince the kids
Estilo no topa convencer a los chavales
that they follow him that he has not done it
que le siguen que no que no ha hecho lo
who criticizes as much as Ricky, well,
que tanto critica como Ricky bueno los
kids who follow you will be worth it
chavales que te siguen ti van a valer
Okay, and what you tell them will affect them.
vale Y lo que tú les digas les va a
worth But you know just as we know
valer Pero tú sabes igual que sabemos
all the all the adults and all the
todos los todos los adultos y todos los
creators that what you have done is a
creadores que lo que has hecho es una
filth and also a very hypocrisy
guarrada y aparte una hipocresía muy
great and that you are
grande y que eres
bad finally Ricky edit put a
malo finalmente Ricky edit puso un
strike on my channel and removed the rewi
strike en mi canal y eliminó el rewi
2024 a shame with a lot of work
2024 una pena con un trabajo de muchos
months of the team with great enthusiasm and with
meses del equipo con mucha ilusión y con
many collaborations This was for the
muchas colaboraciones Esto fue por la
This song from Rick's Sorry is
canción de esta de Lo siento de Rick es
where the problems began there you have
donde empezaron ahí los problemas tenéis
All Lore We have already commented on it in the
todo Lore Ya lo hemos comentado en el
I'm not going to repeat the channel again. But
canal no voy a volver a repetir Pero
Well basically it was because of the song that
bueno básicamente fue por la canción que
He put into the disposition a declamation of
metió en el est dispo una declamación de
Copyright submitted by you
derechos de autor presentado por you
Planet Star knew that Rick was enet But
Planet Star sabía que Rick est enet Pero
Well, considering he was a friend
bueno teniendo en cuenta que era amigo
of wism as I would say, I would say man, he knows it
de wism como diría diría hombre se se la
sucked Well ate him
chupaba Bueno le comía el
banana another right now we
plátano otro ahora mismo nosotros
we are inside the cave and we are
estamos dentro de la caverna y estamos
seeing shadows
viendo sombras
Uncle the judge indirectly calls Javi
tío el juez Llama indirectamente a Javi
oliveira and the pambisitos people with
oliveira y a los pambisitos personas con
average intelligence What or what
intelcia a la media What o sea en qué
moment you take a news clipping
momento coges un recorte de una noticia
of the first sentence not of the no of
de la primera sentencia no de la no de
the second is worth the first sentence
la segunda vale de la primera sentencia
of the procedure this good if it is that
del procedimiento este bueno si es que
That [ __ ] Wilson the other day
el [__] este de Wilson el otro día
denied the Med Johan Plana sentence
negó la sentencia Med Johan plana la
He denied what he thought was what he put
negó lo que a él le o sea lo que ponía
He denied it and says that the game has
lo negó y dice que el juego nos ha
called me to the pisit It is that of
llamado a mí a los pisit Es que de
true sick completely sick
verdad enfermo enfermo completamente
sick okay
enfermo vale
and the shadows that make us think Javi
y las sombras que nos dan a pensar Javi
Lira makes Javi Olira puts song of
Lira hace Javi olira mete canción de
Ricky Ed Ricky edit hits him with a strike but
Ricky Ed Ricky edit le mete strike pero
I think behind the cave outside
creo que detrás de la caverna fuera de
Things are happening in the Cave
la Cueva están pasando cosas que
We don't know why there is here
nosotros no sabemos porque aquí hay
many things that when we see everything No
muchas cosas que cuando veamos todo No
I know now you understand me
sé ahora me entendéis cre
that even the angel will not take off his
queue aunes elío no se quitará la
is missing and is challenging this
falta y está retando esto
that's it
eso es dale
[Laughs]
[Risas]
I don't know if that's what lawyers are doing.
caña eso de los abogados no sé si sera
True, that thing about lawyers drives me crazy.
verdad eh eso de los abogados me vuele
a little bit like a charred thing, it flies a little bit to me
un poco a chamusquina me vuele un poco a
I did it but well I'm going to say that
lo hice yo pero bueno voy a decir que lo
they did what what lawyers Although
hicieron el qué el qué abogados Aunque
Deleting the video will not remove the fault.
elimines el vídeo no se quitará la falta
I don't know if that thing about lawyers is true.
eso de los abogados no sé si sera verdad
eh Ah some of the things he said no of
eh Ah alguna de las cosas que dijo no de
that the lawyers appealed the
de que los abogados apelaban los
strikes that thing about lawyers blows my mind
strikes eso de los abogados me vuele un
little by little I get a little singed, I fly a little to the
poco a chamusquina me vuele un poco a lo
I did it but well I'm going to say that
hice yo pero bueno voy a decir que lo
My lawyers said that there is more to it
hicieron mis abogados que queda más
It's cool to be able to say it like that on YouTube.
chulo poder así decirlo YouTube las
things expire or faster because they throw away
cosas caducan o más rápido porque echan
your case into account with much more
tu caso en cuenta con bastante más
priority or because well saying
prioridad o bien porque bueno diciendo
that is going to expire whether you like it or not
que va a caducar que quieras que no
the thing is that this thing of power expires
caduca la cosa es que esto de de poder
It's a little surreal because I've heard
es un poco surrealist porque yo he oído
to many large channels much more
a muchos canales grandes mucho más
big than Ricky edit comment that to the
grandes que Ricky edit comentar que a la
time to get in touch with the platform
hora de tener contacto con la plataforma
when telling them about problems like this
a la hora de comentarles problemas esto
It's a boast to say that it is
es una fanfarrona para el decir que es
very famous Yes yes So this is that the
muy famoso Sí sí O sea esto de que los
strike dude, he might slip it in, I mean, if he
strike tío lo mismo te cuela O sea si le
He put a strike, I don't know if you remember.
puso un strike yo no sé si os acordaréis
of that story you were very
de esa historia Ustedes erais muy
little
pequeño
and then I found out that it was Jochi
e que luego me enteré que es era jochi
what was his name in his time
cómo se llamaba en su en su época
Hoi hoochi was called in the Juegi era
hoi hoochi se llamaba en la época juegi
juegi jui put an ext on the Rubius that is
juegi jui le puso un ext al Rubius o sea
hochi being Random being a Random of
hochi siendo Random siendo un Random de
Twitter he had a video that was a
Twitter él tenía un vídeo que era una
music he made in no dob eh a remix
música que él hizo en no dob eh un remix
and Ruby used it in a video and the hochi
y el Ruby lo usó en un vídeo y el hochi
He gave him a strike, do you understand? I mean, no
le metio un strike me entiendes O sea no
You don't have to be famous, there are times when
no tienes que ser famoso hay veces que
I would tell you when it is valid it sneaks in and
yo te diría cuando es válido cuela y
when it is not valid it does not count but it is that
cuando no es válido no cuela pero es que
that for me Watch YouTube there are times that
eso para mí Mira YouTube hay veces que
There is a strike that you put them and they don't work
hay strike que tú los pones Y no cuelan
and YouTube tells you no, that you don't get them
y YouTube te dice que no que no te las
mite and there are other times that suddenly
mite y hay otras veces que de repente
a silly second of pum you get it
una tontería de un segundo pum te lo
mete depends on many things
mete depende de muchas cosas
okay literally he is a crazy person
vale literalmente es un loco
eh he is literally a crazy person
eh literalmente es un loco
that they are acting like you are
que están teniendo actúan como si fueras
a normal content creator between
un creador de contenido normal entre
quotes like the typical creator of
comillas en plan el típico creador de
content that you may have access to
contenido que puede tener acceso a que
YouTube helps you treat them the same as
YouTube le ayude que te tratan igual que
having 10 million than having one
teniendo 10 millones que teniendo uno
that having 500,000 is what I'm going for, no
que teniendo 500,000 es a lo que voy no
like an npc or random that has just been
como a un npc o Random que se acaba de
create a channel and ask for help
crear un canal y que pida ayuda a
YouTube But I know how to see this in my own
YouTube Pero esto sé yo a ver yo en mi
personal experience I am also a
experiencia personal igual soy un
clearly self-conscious little [ __ ] and
[__] claramente acomplejado y
I have noticed the same treatment
desgarbado yo he notado el mismo trato
from YouTube as the same aids
de YouTube como las mismas ayudas
having 100,000 subscribers who
teniendo 100.000 suscriptores que
having half a million and I think that at the
teniendo medio millón y creo que a la
Most people have experienced it, no, I don't know.
mayoría de gente le ha pasado no a no sé
man let's see clearly Yes let's see having
hombre a ver claro Sí a ver teniendo
100,000 already gives you the chat, okay?
100,000 ya te dan lo del chat vale Yo
For example, I already have up to
por ejemplo ya es que tengo hasta
trust with those in the YouTube chat and
confianza con los del chat de YouTube y
with the support for the issue of
con los del soporte por por el tema de
from the persecution they do to me
de la persecución que me hacen me
you understand. So in the end what you
entiendes O sea que al final lo que te
That's what causes that in the end, the chat of
provoca es eso al final los del chat de
YouTube
YouTube
HM the other day I was reported This voucher
HM el otro día me reportaron Este vale
then I put something like
entonces le puse yo algo así como
It is always thanks to you that they take care of me
gracias siempre a ti es que me atienden
very well the truth I mean always me
muy bien la verdad O sea siempre me
They attend and I write to you by md of de
atienden y yo le escribo por md de de
Twitter to these people you know but it's already
Twitter a esta gente sabes pero es ya
from the ass of tiredness that they give me or
del por culo del cansancio que me dan o
Let every day be a fraudulent strike
sea todos los días un strike fraudulento
when it is not I don't know what then it is already to me
cuando no es no sé qué entonces ya a mí
Yes, but I'm telling you it's not because I have a
ya pero ya te digo no es porque tenga un
million 2 million nor 3 million or so
millón 2 millones ni 3 millones o sea
Look Dallas, do you understand me? They listen to you.
Mira Dallas me entiendes te hacen caso
They don't pay attention to you, man, yes it's true
no te hacen caso hombre sí que es verdad
that I understand that at the time of
que yo entiendo que a la hora de que
try to close a channel that gives them
intenten cerrar un canal que les da
00000 turkeys 60,000 turkeys I don't know how much
00000 pavos 60,000 pavos no sé cuánto
generate Ricky's channel Ricky's channel
generar el canal de Ricky canal de Ricky
generates a
genera un
[ __ ] money
pastón ostia hab
has gone down a lot
bajado ha bajado mucho
It has not gone down much, of course, it is that they have already
no ha bajado mucho claro es que ya los
short I don't know is that these were many
short no sé es que esto eran muchas
visits were from
visitas eran de
short many visits were from short that
short muchas visitas eran de short que
They also monetize but it is not worth much or
monetizan también pero no mucho vale o
be me for example in a short that had
sea yo por ejemplo en un short que tuvo
10 million views, yes, I did get them.
10 millones de visitas pues sí que saqué
400 I think it was you know but of course a
400 creo que fue sabes pero claro un
short of 10 million views that
short de 10 millones de visitas que
you have 10 million visits not them
tienes que 10 millones de visitas no las
You don't have any shorts of the month.
tienes tú ni en todos los short del mes
Normally you understand me but Ricky does.
Normalmente me entiendes pero Ricky si
I had all this was short now now
tenía todo esto era de short ahora ahora
They are shared less. I mean, I also like it.
se comparten menos O sea a mí también me
The number of visits to the
han bajado mucho las visitas de la
salseria because many visitors were
salsería porque muchas visitas eran
short you know and of the three channels in
short sabes y de los tres canales en
general But well the
general Pero bueno la
move
movida
Look, I think Ricky will generate 40,000
Mira yo creo que Ricky generará 40.000
pavet or something like that
pavet o por ahí
eh I think so, I think 40,000
eh yo creo que sí yo creo que 40.000
turkeys no one can take it away from you between 30 and
pavos no se lo quita nadie entre 30 y
50,000 I think you can't stop looking at it
50.000 yo creo que no se quita mirar el
video I don't know if you see it up here
vídeo no sé si lo veis aquí en lo alto
mine that the Network of recommends to you
mía que te recomienda la Network de
Ricky
Ricky
Eddie the Ricky Network Eddie no I mean
Eddie la Network de Ricky Eddie no O sea
Ricky Edy's followers, that is
Los Seguidores de Ricky edy o sea
recommended channels that come to you
canales recomendados que te salen por
you know by Ricky Eddy look
sabes por Ricky Eddy mira
video that interests the public
vídeo que le interesa al público de
Ricky
Ricky
Eddie, I don't know if you're watching it.
Eddie no sé si lo estáis viendo
Ok, but well, let's see what it was going to be like.
vale pero bueno a ver lo que iba a
tell you a channel that generates no more than 40,000
decirte un canal que genera ya no 40.000
50,000 turkeys a channel that generates 20,000
50.000 pavos un canal que genere 20.000
turkeys already already man YouTube has it more
pavos ya ya hombre YouTube lo tiene más
Even a channel that generates 6 or 7000
Incluso un canal que genere 6 o 7000
turkeys man YouTube has it a bit
pavos hombre YouTube lo tiene un poco
more important not to lose it than one that does not
más en cuenta no perderlo que uno que no
generate money you understand me and it's a
genere dinero me entiendes y es un
a little more does make it a little more
poquito más sí le hace un poquito más de
You know what, but that's how it is all
Caso sabes pero eso es así como todas
companies in all things I know that
las empresas en todas las cosas sé que
those auronplay don't talk to the boss of
esas auronplay a no habla con la jefa de
Spain but it is auronplay esty
España pero es que es auronplay esty
talking to two Google executives
hablando con dos encargados de Google
I spoke with Peña directly from Google
hablé con Peña directamente de Google
that are supposed to be put on the panel
que se supone que ponen en el panel
control when super mill of
control cuando super mill de
subscribers send the plate yita so that
suscriptores mand la placa yita para que
If you have any problem, solve it in
si tien alún problema lo resuelvas en
real time view for was the best because
tiempo real ver for fue la mejor porque
Hub mayú because you're [ __ ] nervous when
Hub mayú porque est [__] nervos cuando
But that doesn't happen to you when you have
Pero eso no te lo habitan cuando tienes
a million subscribers that's any
un millón de suscriptores eso cualquier
and when they send you the plate, that's what it means
y cuando te envían la placa eso loene
everyone who makes money with
todo el mundo que gane dinero con
YouTube when of course they get it
YouTube cuando claro acan la
monetization I think that's how it is I think
monetización creo que eso es así Creo
that they haven't changed in the last few years
que no lo han cambiado en los últimos
months when monetization is activated
meses cuando te activan la monetización
you have like a private chat with
tú tienes como un chat privado con
YouTube where you can ask for help in
YouTube en el que puedes pedir ayuda en
the creator of course or whatever but it's that I
el creator claro o sea pero es que yo
Trust me, I speak sometimes
fíate tú que yo hablo yo algunas veces
I don't even go to the chat, I sometimes talk
no voy ni al chat yo algunas veces hablo
with them via Twitter md uncle is yours
con ellos por md de Twitter tío es tuyo
in the control panel of the sea is that it is
en el panel de control del sea es que se
He is inventing something so that the
está inventando una cosa para que los
kids think he's super
chavales se crean que él es super
important on YouTube Let's go a little further and
importante en YouTube Vamos poco más y
What and what are we going to have? Ah, an office
que y que vamos que tiene Ah una oficina
On Google YouTube they don't give you that.
en Google YouTube eso no te lo dan
when you have more than a million
cuando tienes más de un millón de
subscribers nor is the treatment different
suscriptores ni es diferente el trato
that you have in plan is no different
que tienes en plan no es diferente el
access that you have, that is, this is all now
acceso que tienes o sea esto todo es ya
not only the strike And this I don't know
no solamente lo del strike Y esto no sé
If it ends in Game Over, a G is worth nothing.
si acabará en Game Over vale nada un G
I don't think it is but a good video to the
no creo que sea pero un buen vídeo a lo
better yes okay well I don't know I don't know
mejor sí vale bueno no lo sé no os
I promise nothing but that it is no longer the
prometo nada pero que ya no es el
ridiculous for older people to
ridículo para las personas mayores para
adults, that is, for people
personas adultas o sea para las personas
who are over 14 years old
que tengan más de 14 años
eh It's no longer the issue of the strike as such
eh Ya no es el tema del strike como tal
but all this that you are all
sino que todo esto que estás todos los
cli now that all the items are being viewed
cli ahora que se están viendo todas las
things this is a eh Ricky you are You are a
cosas esto es un eh Ricky eres Eres un
clown do you understand me you are a clown you are
payaso me entiendes eres un payaso estás
assuming you're stupid, you understand me.
quedando que eres tonto me entiendes
It's when you have a million
es cuando tienes un millón de
subscribers when you have less
suscriptores a cuando tienes menos te
I give reason to censure myself for two others
doy motivo para censurarme otras dos
weeks because what happens YouTube you
semanas porque qué ocurre YouTube te
puts the restriction that is two weeks
mete la restricción que son dos semanas
If you appeal and you are wrong they can
Si apelas y no tienes razón pueden
decide to even delete your channel
decidir incluso borrarte el canal
directly if they want to commit another foul
directamente si quieren meter otra falta
We have sanctioned the plan. Have you appealed this?
plan teemos sancionado has apelado esto
Deleting the channel is the same as what he said
de Borrar el canal es lo mismo que dijo
with me, that is, you don't close for a video
conmigo o sea tú por un vídeo no cierras
a channel That is because you have a video
un canal O sea porque tú tengas un vídeo
because you throw a video they put a
porque tú tires un vídeo Te ponen un
strike is the biggest thing You understand me that
strike es lo más gordo Me entiendes que
It can be very screwed up if you have other or
puede ser muy [__] si tienes otros o
whatever you are no but in the end neither
lo que seas no pero es que al final ni
Even with three strikes I'll throw you in the
siquiera con tres strikes te tir en el
channel sometimes or there are some
canal algunas veces o sea hay algunos
those who are chasing me for
los que me están persiguiendo por
example that they believe that when they have
ejemplo que se creen que cuando tienen
Three strikes and they will close the channel Y
tres strike te van a cerrar el canal Y
surely not surely not either
seguramente tampoco seguramente Tampoco
because there should already be three strikes
porque ya tendrían que ser tres strike
eh And what if the three strikes lose
eh Y que y que los tres strike pierdan
the appeals or a channel are not
las apelaciones o sea un canal no se
It doesn't close like that either because
cierra tampoco así porque
yes you are not right, you see this does not have
sí no tiene razón rón ves esto no tiene
sense with what he said before yes of course
sentido con lo que dijo antes si Claro
because
porque
lies has contact as Premium with
miente tiene contacto como Premium con
It's totally true, it's true, before you
totalmente es verdad es verdad antes te
I was saying that I had a contact
estaba diciendo que tenía un un contacto
Premium with YouTube and here it is for you
Premium con YouTube y aquí te está
saying that they wanted to screw YouTube or
diciendo que le querían [__] YouTube o
has a status on the platform
tiene como un status en la plataforma
Why do they put him with the typical person?
Por qué le ponen con la típica persona
What happened to me that on YouTube you
que me ha pasado de que en YouTube te
answer in the chat this one that looks like a
contesta en el chat este que parece un
robot that is not a robot but they are so
robot que no es un robot pero están tan
automated to say Hey man, let's see
automatizados para decir Oye tío a ver
You tell him to see, friend Ramón, it's that I
le dices a ver amigo Ramón es que me
you just put this video in yellow
acabéis de poner este vídeo en amarillo
and it's literally a Rocket Gameplay
y literalmente es un Gameplay de Rocket
League Nothing happens, it's inclusive.
League No pasa nada es inclusive está
without commenting on what sense this has
sin comentar que qué sentido tiene Esto
Can you explain it to me and good here
me lo puedes explicar y buone por aquí
you have all the details to verify
tienes todos los detalles para verificar
Why a video can be considered
Por qué un vídeo puede ser considerado
yellow because monetization is on
amarillo porque la monetización está
as enabled they respond to you like robots
como habilitada te responden como robots
They are programmed like that. Those workers
están programados así Esos trabajadores
being publicly not all are not
estando públicamente no son todos no son
They are all new, eh?
todos son los nuevos eh
YouTube
YouTube
They have some employees in the
tienen algunos algunos empleados en el
support that is by a subcontractor
soporte que son por una subcontrata
special people are worth a few
gente especial vale algunas
times and then the subcontractors
veces y entonces los de la subcontrata
Well, sometimes they are not mu no
Pues en algunas ocasiones no están mu no
They are very knowledgeable on the subject, you know.
están muy puestos en el tema sabes
agree to the country where I reside to attack
convenir al país donde resido a agredir
real actually that was actually because
real en realidad eso en realidad fue por
my fault if it is not that it is that it is that in
mi culpa si nun es que es que es que en
I actually feel a little bad. I feel
realidad me siento un poco mal me siento
a little guilty about the fact that if
un poco culpable por el hecho de que si
I would never have had those debates with
nunca hubiera hecho esos debates con
pambisitos many things that we have
pambisitos muchas cosas de las que hemos
seen today they would have passed it and in
visto hoy en día lo hubieran pasado y en
instead of giving her an indefinite leave
vez de ponerla una falta indefinida a
see the first thing in theory well let's see that
ver lo primero en teoría bueno a ver eso
It was the fault of the threats
fue culpa de lo de las amenazas
because my children were mentioned
porque se puso a mención a mis hijos me
You understand. Then listen to me, King.
entiendes Entonces ya escúchame Rey
until
hasta
There are times when it fails, but in theory
aquí hay veces que falla pero en teoría
YouTube for a while before
YouTube desde hace un tiempo antes de
uploading a video already notifies you if the
subir un vídeo ya te notifica si el
video is copyrighted or not like yes
vídeo tiene copyright o no en plan Si
It has some songs but sometimes it fails
tiene alguna canción pero a veces falla
Sometimes it has happened to me that it has taken a while
a veces a mí me ha pasado que ha tardado
a few hours to bypass copyright or
algunas horas en saltarme el copyright o
sea ​​and days but Ricky put it in by hand Eh
sea y días pero Ricky lo metió a mano Eh
He went to put it in, he told it. Yesterday he went to
fue él a meterlo lo contó Ayer fue él a
put it in, went to put it, I had it uploaded
meterlo fue a ponerlo lo tenía subido
for a long time
desde hace un
time and after 3 hours the alarm comes on
tiempo y a las 3 horas me salta el
copyright and I have to remove that part or
copyright y tengo que quitar esa parte o
I have to upload it again, that's what happened to me
tengo volver a subirlo eso me ha pasado
but normally it usually comes out
pero normalmente te suele salir al
principle warns you before publishing it and
principio te avisa antes de publicarlo y
I haven't mentioned that about the indefinite absence.
lo de la falta indefinida eso no lo he
I have never seen in my life what a foul is being called
visto en mi vida lo de ponerle una falta
indefinite that I had the option to apply it
indefinida que tuve opción de aplicarla
and that the canal would have knocked it down
y que la habría tumbado el canal
I have not heard this directly in
directamente esto no lo he escuchado en
My life is not that I have not done this
mi vida no lo es que esto no yo no lo he
heard in life either I don't want
escuchado en la vida tampoco no quiero
say it's a lie because I don't know
decir que es mentira porque no lo sé a
The best thing is suddenly true, you know
lo mejor de repente sí es verdad sabes
but I don't know that, I don't know that.
pero es que yo no lo sé yo eso No lo
I listen to life and it surprises me a lot
escucho en la vida y me extraña mucho
that I have not heard that because
que yo no no haya escuchado eso porque
I know all about that [ __ ].
yo me la sé tod allá de de esa [__] Yo
I think it's an invention
creo que es un invent
I have never heard in my life that instead of
escuchado en mi vida lo de que en vez de
give you a strike two and on the third you get
ponerte un strike dos y al tercero se te
The channel has already been taken by the ass.
a tomado por culo el canal ya tienes que
Well, then tell YouTube, Hey, no, this.
pues ahí decirle a YouTube Oye no Esto
It's not like that, please don't leave me without
no es así por favor no me dejéis sin
eat But that of indefinite absence I don't
comer Pero eso de falta indefinida No lo
I've heard in my life I don't know if it's
he escuchado en mi vida no sé si es
It is false that if I did not know, I think that
falso es que si no lo sabría yo creo que
yes yes I think it is inv I think it is
sí sí yo creo que se inv yo creo que se
He threw a three-pointer and now you cry because
ha tirado un tri y ahora lloras porque
YouTube has deleted a video where you
YouTube te ha borrado un vídeo donde
you used my content to earn
utilizabas mi contenido para ganar
money Look, as the can said, that
dinero Mira pues como decía la can eso
and now you cry because YouTube
de que y ahora lloras porque YouTube te
has deleted a video where you used my
ha borrado un vídeo donde utilizabas mi
content to make money we do not
contenido para ganar dinero nosotros no
we can say that Ricky edit Ricky edit
podemos decir eso Ricky edit Ricky edit
you can't say that man I can't say
no puede decir eso tío no puedo decir
that's the [ __ ] what we do, we dedicate ourselves to reacting
eso [__] nos dedicamos a reaccionar
comment expose things of the rest is that
comentar exponer cosas del resto es que
I don't know, it doesn't make sense, it doesn't make sense
no sé no tiene sentido no tiene sentido
and rique also is that don't [ __ ] with me man
y rique también es que no me jodas tío
don't [ __ ] with me don't [ __ ] with me the parks of
no me jodas no me jodas los parque de
top-rated attractions in the world
atracciones per valorados del mundo loa
from Twitter well this is yours me
desde Twitter bueno Esto es suyo me
I found an 11 year old boy in Fortnite.
encontré un ni 11 años en fortnite esto
It's yours, that's how the characteristics are, another
es suyo así son los caracteristas otro
reaction video a reaction video a
vídeo reacción un vídeo reacción un
reaction video This video is yours magician
vídeo reacción Este vídeo es suyo mago
reaction to clear magic It is that it is that it is
reacción a magia claro Es que es que es
content is content of others is that and
contenido es contenido de otros es que y
It's okay because it's ferus you if of the
no pasa nada porque es ferus tú si de la
work that is reacting you do a
obra que está reaccionando haces una
reaction that is considered as a
reacción que sea considerada como una
new work based on that content that
obra nueva en base a ese contenido que
is with the platform Nothing happens but
está con la plataforma No pasa nada pero
Of course, this is why you cry now because
claro esto de que ahora lloras porque
YouTube AB you from the video you used my
YouTube te AB del vídeo utilizabas mi
content to make money both
contenido para ganar dinero los dos
We know the real reason why you appeal
sabemos el motivo real por el que apelas
the claim and how well it has gone for you
la reclamación y lo bien que te ha
the strike came for other things no no
venido el strike para otras cosas no no
I understand, I don't understand this, I don't understand
entiendo no entiendo esto no entiendo
this to make content or rather but
esto para hacer contenido o sea pero
make content of a strike Yes yes for
hacer contenido de un strike Sí sí para
It refers to that to see what it is
se refiere a eso a ver a lo que se
Ricky refers to how well you have
refiere Ricky con lo bien que te ha
come for other things is
venido para otras cosas es
that evil has remained and that we are
em que ha quedado el mal y que estamos
making content but well not for the
haciendo contenido pero bueno no por el
content in Yes because I would have
contenido en Sí porque yo hubiera
preferred not to have to do this
preferido no tener que hacer este
content but the evil has remained
contenido sino que ha quedado el mal
because it has become what it criticizes and
porque ha quedado como lo que critica y
I think it looks terrible, eh. It's just that
yo es que ha quedado fatal eh Es que
look at the cell phone chat that hates me and
mira el chat de cel que a mí me odia y
They're giving the cell phone a try, he doesn't hate me but
están dándole al al cel no me odia pero
I think your ch a little yes and they are
creo que su ch un poco sí y están
giving it to Ricky, man, let's see.
dándole es que lo del Ricky tío a ver
that a strike I know that you guys
que un strike Yo sé que vosotros os lo
Take it as a joke, but a strike is a real blast.
toméis a coña pero un strike [__] es
screwed for your channel because you are a
[__] para tu canal porque estás a un
It's a little bit dirty to do that, that's because
poquito es una guarrada hacer eso es que
It has become worse than anyone, look at that
ha quedado peor de cualquiera mira que
had already been left in bad shape with a lot of
había quedado mal ya con un montón de
things eh But with this my son is that
cosas eh Pero con esto hijo mío es que
You have already crowned yourself as the worst
ya te has Coronado como que eres lo peor
Let me close it for you, so
vamos que te lo cierren yo por lo que
What happened with Dallas I'd rather see today
pasó con Dallas prefería ver hoy en día
Well, I prefer what happened to happen.
pues ya prefiero que pasó lo que pasó
But if I could go back I would prefer
pero si pudiera Volver atrás prefería
that I would never have gotten the strikes
que nunca me hubiera metido los strikes
channel is in danger I don't think this
canal está en peligro No creo que esto
I say it to create content No
lo diga que sea para crear contenido No
the truth is what I told you about the one
la verdad lo que os dije de la de la
cavern that we are seeing
caverna que nosotros estamos viendo una
thing but I don't know what the hell is behind it
cosa pero no sé qué [__] habrá detrás de
This is not there is nothing that is a
esto no s no hay nada lo que es un
burned and it's bad It's over, there's no more me
ardido y es malo Ya está no hay más yo
I have nothing to do with this guy or anything.
no tengo nada con este tío ni topo O sea
if it is not even if it is what it is
si es que ni siquiera si es que es lo
What did I tell you, I mean, I thought he was
que os dije o sea yo me creía que él se
was going to take his appearances in the well
iba a tomar bien sus apariciones en el
rewind
rewind
Uncle, so you look bad in the debate.
tío O sea que quedas mal en el debate
Ricky Let's see, the debate was...
Ricky A ver es que el debate fue fueron
those are the parts There are none
esas las partes Es que no hay ninguna
part where you look good in the debate
parte en la que quedes bien en el debate
Ricky you know but then I'll play his song
Ricky sabes pero luego pongo su canción
with his concert it was not a thing
con su concierto no que fue una cosa
viral that cli there were people who were
viral ese cli había gente que se estaba
laughing at him for the cli and the whole thing
riendo de él por el cli y todo el rollo
But well, the song is cool, no, I
pero bueno la canción está Chula no Yo
what I know
qué sé
Yesterday we saw the parts where Ricky appears or
ayer vimos las partes que sale Ricky o
I thought that on the contrary
sea yo me pensaba que al contrario que
It was like, well, he appears, no, I don't know, no
era como pues aparece él no yo que sé no
I know everything smells strange to me once I get to
sé me huele todo raro una vez llegado a
This point by Javi prefers to have the
este punto por Javi prefiere tener el
strike what the [ __ ] do you delete the song and
strike a que [__] borras la canción y
He's already on my balls, he's on my balls
ya está por mis [__] él por mis
balls because it's not like that it can't be a
[__] porque no es así no puede ser un
censor or rather, because he didn't believe that
censurador o sea y porque no creía que
I was going to go all the way too you
iba a llegar hasta el final también te
I say, eh, I mean, I didn't think I was going to
digo eh o sea yo no creía que iba a
reaching the end is that it was already
llegar hasta el final es que ya eso era
look terrible in public, that is what I say
quedar fatal públicamente o sea yo digo
Well no, he's not going to do it on his own.
bueno no no lo va a hacer por su cuenta
But when I see that it is a strike,
pero ya cuando vea que es un strike ya
yes it is
sí lo
take me away, understand me, look, look at the chat
quita me entiend mira fíjate tú el chat
from cell that hates me the cell chat Look
de cel que me odia el chat de cel Mira
There is someone here who says cell whitening
Hay alguno aquí que dice cel blanqueando
to Javi Oliveira when Ricky has all
a Javi oliveira cuando Ricky tiene toda
the
la
reason because yes I mean if Dallas puts a
razón porque sí O sea si Dallas pone un
Strike can make videos for Dallas
strike se le puede hacer vídeos a Dallas
putting a clip of Dallas but Ricky is
poniendo clip de Dallas pero Ricky si es
Jai no but this has also been proven
Jai no pero esto también ha demostrado
also the hypocrisy no longer of Ricky
también la hipocresía ya no de Ricky
as such but of any of those who
como tal sino de cualquiera de los que
They follow these people of Ricky and that's it.
siguen a esta gente de Ricky Y eso o sea
there is no more there is no more there is no more
es que no hay más no hay más está no
because you get to the end knowing
porque llegas hasta el final sabiendo
that can give you a strike does not have
que te puede meter un strike no tiene
sense has no sense if you have the
sentido no tiene sentido si tienes la
option to cut out that part that I don't believe
opción de recortar esa parte que no creo
Even if it doesn't contribute much to the video, you take it away.
ni que aporte mucho al vídeo lo quitas
I don't understand it I don't understand it
que no lo entiendo No lo entiendo
SEO pride I think is a part of it
orgullo seo creo sí que es una parte
cool man yes that is a cool part
chula hombre sí que es una parte chula
that it was not the same without that
que no quedaba igual sin esa
song I think it will reach both
canción Yo creo que llegará tanto por
Pride has no sense, I don't know if
orgullo no tiene sentido yo no sé si
I would have put a Ricky song on
hubiese puesto una canción de Ricky en
the strike knowing that things
el strike sabiendo que que las cosas
They were complicated, I said it, I don't say it anymore.
estaban complicadas lo dije ya yo no lo
I've put it eh I don't think so either It's that I
hese puesto eh tampoco creo Es que yo
This argument that they say, I don't know if
este argumento que lo dicen yo no sé si
It's because they don't want to give us everything either.
es porque nos quieren tampoco darle todo
The negative thing about Ricky is that these people are worth it but
lo negativo a Ricky esta gente vale pero
It doesn't make sense, I don't know if
es que no tiene sentido yo no sé si
I would have put on a Ricky song but
hubiera puesto una canción de Ricky pero
Let's see when Dallas is criticized.
vamos a ver cuando se critica a Dallas
They don't put on clips
no se ponen clip de
Dallas when Selin put a stray on him
Dallas cuando selin le puso un estray al
uncle
tío
shur was valid no no when Dallas gave him
shur fue válido no no cuando Dallas le
put a star sell was valid no no
puso una estrella sell fue válido no no
obviously
evidentemente
No. That is, you should never do that.
no O sea eso no se tiene que hacer nunca
I don't know if it's a channel for this.
a no s que sea un canal de esto Que
appear that your content is uploaded to me
aparezca que que sube tu contenido me
You understand Javi, trusting Ricky is already
entiendes Javi confiar en Ricky Ya es
too innocent but that is not
demasiado inocente pero que que no es
for being too much that we will see what it is
por ser demasiado que vamos a ver que es
you can't do that, dude, you understand me
que no puedes hacer eso tío me entiendes
So every time they tell me and I
Entonces yo cada vez que me dicen y me
You say it too, a lot of men are
lo decís ustedes también mucho hombre es
that I could remove the song It's that no
que podía quitar la canción Es que no
I'm going to remove the song It's that I'm
voy a quitar la canción Es que estoy
making a compilation of things
haciendo un recopilatorio de las cosas
of the year and p cli of Dallas and I click
del año y p cli de Dallas y pongo click
Ricky's and I click on the stutter and
de Ricky y pongo click del tartaja y
I put a clip of everyone who takes me or
pongo clip de todo el mundo me lleve o
don't take me or whatever but what is this now
no me lleve o sea pero esto Qué es ahora
Now this is what I have to have
esto Ahora sí es que tengo que tener
be careful with who I take
cuidado con los que me llevo
bad because they appear in the content
mal porque porque aparecen en el content
ID is that it doesn't make sense let's see
ID es que no tiene sentido vamos a ver
who appears to me in the content
quiénes me aparecen a mí en el content
ID is that no, I really do and well
ID es que no yo eso De verdad y y bueno
at least they are condemning him
por lo menos lo están condenando
at least they are condemning him no but
por lo menos lo están condenando no pero
I really do. Look, it appears to me.
yo eso De verdad Mira a mí me aparece
Here at Content ID the other day we saw
aquí en el content ID el otro día vimos
those that appear on my channel
los que me aparecen en el canal
main thing that Ricky appears to me between
principal que me aparece Ricky entre
others not Mira Quesada gbel cito clipero
otros no Mira Quesada gbel cito clipero
I don't know why the hell it appears to me
que no sé por qué [__] me aparece a mí
clipper icito
icito clipero
Ah because it's a clip of the debate
Ah porque es un cl un clip del debate
mine with delos Look it is a piece of the
mío con delos Mira es es un trozo del
my debate with delo and el and elcito
debate mío con delo y el y elcito
clipero eh goes up 25 minutes this one
clipero eh sube 25 minutos este lo
I would have thrown it away if I tell you the truth
hubiera tirado si os digo la verdad
I might throw it away because I don't put it on.
capaz y lo tiro es que no me pongo es
I'm not even going to look here. This is worth it.
que no me meto ni aquí a mirar Esto vale
Franco is a slap. Ah, go.
Franco esta bofetea Ah va
Llanos I don't know this I think this is a
Llanos no sé esto esto creo que es un
clip of my
clip de mis
official state of alarm series this this
serie estado de alarma oficial este este
Javier Negre's channel has already uploaded
es el canal de Javier negre ya ha subido
and tell him what I say is that he has
y díselo qué le digo sea es que ha
uploaded a short of mine on Javier Negre
subido un short mío el el Javier negre
Ok, it's a short of mine, but let's edit it.
vale es un short mío pero vamos editado
For my Editors, Tom is worth an ass
por mis Editores vale a Tom por culo
egun pasa debate with egun pasa I'm going to
egun pasa debate con egun pasa Yo le voy
to put a star something happens in a
a poner una estrall egun pasa en un
debate that he has had with me
debate que ha hecho conmigo
Quesada but
Quesada pero
Come on Pablo Franco, I mean, you can have me.
vamos Pablo franco o sea me puede tener
more fed up with the elun happens
más hasta los [__] elun pasa
criticizing me all [ __ ] day and
criticándome todo el [__] día y
putting on the miniatures with a necklace
poniéndome las miniaturas con un collar
As a dog, I throw him a strike.
de perrito eh le tiro un strike
No, hey, if one day I consider that such
no Oye si un día yo Considero que tal
Well, I'll file a lawsuit, but let's go now.
pues le pondré una demanda pero vamos ya
you have to have thin skin for now
tienes que tener piel fina para ya
They have to pass. It just doesn't make sense.
tienen que pasar Es que no tiene sentido
no man no no no
que no hombre que no que no
man, he pisses me off. Look, he's uploaded it.
tío me toca los [__] Mira ha subido
Here's a video that isn't even his 5
aquí un vídeo que no es ni de él 5
my multigame minutes appear here a
minutos míos multigame aparece aquí un
pile I don't even know what will go up
montón No sé ni lo que subirá
Wait for that. Let's go to another channel.
ese espérate Vamos a ir a otro canal
so you can see who appears
para que veáis Quiénes aparecen
Okay, so it doesn't occur to me
vale o sea que no se me pasa por la
head
cabeza
strike those who appear here in
poner strike a los que aparezcan aquí en
the content ID Look Ricky appears
el content ID Mira Ricky aparece
Ricky Roma Gallardo Antonio David who I
Ricky Roma Gallardo Antonio David que me
Antonio David gave me a strike, let's go
puso un strike a mí Antonio David vamos
I could perfectly put a strike on him
podría ponerle a un strike perfectamente
Look Antonio
Mira Antonio
David s Junior I don't know what it is will be
David s Junior No sé lo que es será
any reaction, let's not even think about it
alguna reacción vamos ni de coña le
I put a stress on
pongo yo un estr un
colleague a guy
colega un tío
whitewash some collaboration that looks like
blanquero alguna miraa colaboración que
we did
hiciéramos
he
el
the chomp stutters I don't even know what the hell it is
tartaja el chomp no sé ni qué [__] es
that is it
eso sea es
that that no that it doesn't make any sense
que que no que no tiene sentido ninguno
that no that no no it's not that good one
que no que no no es que bueno una
person with whom you do not get along do the
persona con la que te llevas mal has el
content and it appears there in the content
contenido y te aparece ahí en el content
ID and what and
ID y qué y
what and what the content ID appears
qué y qué que le aparezca el content ID
What I didn't expect is that this guy
lo que yo no me esperaba es que este tío
I was going to grab it and press the button
iba a [__] y le iba a dar al botón
Man, please, what are we talking about?
hombre por favor de qué estamos hablando
And what are we validating? No.
Ya Y qué es lo que estamos validando No
Man no please I think it's like
hombre no por favor creo que sea como
to strike someone, uncle, I think
para meter un strike a alguien tío creo
that an understanding can be reached
que se puede llegar un entendimiento
before but well They are there but it is not
antes pero bueno Están pero es que no es
no understanding or anything, that is to say it is
ni entendimiento ni nada o sea es que es
I see that there in the content edit and no
yo veo eso ahí en el content edit y no
I give him a strike.
le doy a que le pongan un strike sea
Ricky edit be the stutterer be Win michu
Ricky edit sea el tartaja sea Win michu
You understand me, I don't put a
me entiendes es que no no le pongo un
strike no one dude one strike for
strike a nadie tío un strike por
copyright Look the tool is called
copyright Mira la herramienta se llama
copyright strike that has to be it
strike por copyright eso tiene que ser
someone like a channel of this that uploads
alguien como un canal de esto que sube
clip That's because it is a strike for
clip Eso sí porque es es un strike por
copyright that is taking away your visits
copyright que te está quitando visita
because he is uploading the whole thing to me
porque lo está subiendo entero me
you understand but that tool is not
entiendes pero esa herramienta no se
call strike because I'm burned or
llama strike porque estoy ardido o
strike because I get along badly, not that one
strike porque me llevo mal no esa
tool is called strike by
herramienta se llama strike por
copyright is not that defaming me good for
copyright no es que me difama bueno para
that you have other tools that are not
eso tienes otras herramientas que no es
that that that is fraudulent and that's it.
esa esa eso es fraudulento y punto en
Boca, if there is no other guy, it's me.
Boca si es que no hay más tío es que yo
I don't know what is not understood about
no sé qué es lo que no se entiende de
That's the one who doesn't understand it. No, it's not that
eso el que no lo entiende No no es que
I don't understand it, I refuse to think that
no lo entienda yo me niego a pensar que
There are people who don't understand it, I think.
haya gente que no lo entienda yo creo
that is because because such and such and such is not
que es porque pues porque tal o sea y no
there is more
hay más
they are extremely they are extremely
están sumamente están sumamente
shot the truth is they are extremely that
tiroteados la verdad están sumamente que
We are very shot but I don't
estamos muy tiroteados pero que yo no le
I put a star on him and he put me
pongo una estralla a él y me ha puesto
with a dog collar on the
con un collar de perro en la
thumbnail with a video of millions of
miniatura con un vídeo de millones de
visits that are not really us
visitas que no que de verdad Nos
We dedicate ourselves to this, we dedicate ourselves to gossip
dedicamos a esto nos dedicamos al salseo
We dedicate ourselves to this what we
nos dedicamos a esto lo que nos
we dedicate and there will be things that will go to you
dedicamos y habrá cosas que te van a
bother you and there will be things that will bother you
molestar y habrá cosas que te van a
annoy
molestar
It's worth a lot. But hey, don't get involved if
muchísimo vale Pero bueno no te metas si
you're not going to burn like that when you're going to burn like that
no te vas a si si te vas a arder cuando
You don't come out a winner. Okay, then don't get involved.
no sales ganador Vale pues no te metas
[ __ ], come on, I'll get on with that.
[__] anda que yo si me pongo con esa
shot Ho Ricky also spoke for a while
tiroteado Ho hablo Ricky también un rato
live, maybe today already
en directo tal o sea hoy ya
They made the strike official as far as I can see.
oficializaron el strike por lo que veo
the video is no longer available is a
el vídeo ya no está disponible es una
a [ __ ], the truth is you are a [ __ ]
putada la verdad tí es una putada la
true, he can report such a crime
verdad tando delito él puede denunciar
the video if it is a criticism no I mean by
el vídeo si es una crítica no O sea por
that's very careful with what I told you. I mean
eso mucho ojo a lo que te he dicho O sea
If someone criticizes me and it is a criticism
si alguien me critica y es una crítica
I [ __ ] around and dance because I've been a
me jodo y bailo porque yo he sido una
person who has made criticism Now
persona que ha hecho críticas Ahora
I repeat if a person tells me
vuelvo a repetir Si una persona me
accuses crimes that are vile lies
imputa delitos que son vilmente mentiras
and I don't feel like arguing verbally
y no tengo ganas de discutir verbalmente
in video with that person then I knock him down
en vídeo con esa persona pues le tumbo
the video is not copyrighted as
el vídeo no por copyright como
perhaps but for an attack on my person I do not know
tal sino por ataque a mi persona no sé
If I explain myself, well, that's what you have for
si me explico pues eh Para eso tienes
a tool that says here eh
una herramienta que aquí pone eh
report and you will have legal problems and
denunciar y te vas a problema legal y
Here you have defamation and they will accept it.
aquí tienes difamación y te lo aceptarán
or he doesn't accept it but if you do it
o no te lo acepta pero si tú lo haces
by copyright you are using the
por copyright estás utilizando la
tool
herramienta
fraudulently that no no no no
fraudulentamente que no no no no
because I defamed you and imputed you
porque porque te difame y te impute
crime So we are in the same
delito Entonces estamos en las mismas
so every time Dallas gets
entonces cada vez que Dallas se
you come across a video you don't like
encuentre con un vídeo que no le gusta
what they are telling you because they are
lo que le están diciendo porque le están
insinuating things or I don't know what I don't know
insinuando cosas o no sé qué no sé
how much to throw it
cuánto que lo tire
No
no
Clear clear
Claro claro
no How many videos are there now from Dallas
no Cuántos vídeos hay ahora de Dallas
saying that it is a
diciendo que es un
scammer how many are there am I
estafador cuántos hay estoy
completely sure that if the Dallas
completamente seguro de que si el Dallas
He starts taking down all the videos that
se pone a tumbar todos los vídeos que
They say it's a
dicen que es un
scammer there will still be criticism to
estafador va a haber todavía críticas a
Dallas because there are those who are
Dallas porque hay que estn
censoring I explain the strikes in
censurando explico los strikes en
At first they are [ __ ], that is to say
principio son una [__] o sea los
strikes no content creator
strikes a ningún creador de contenido le
likes a strike doesn't like Ricky I don't like it
gusta un strike no le gusta Ricky No me
I like it, I don't like it, Javi doesn't like it
gusta a mí no le gusta Javi no le gusta
Dala doesn't like not doesn't like anyone
dala no le gusta not no le gusta nadie
no content creator can be
ningún creador de contenido puede estar
in favor of the strike because it is something that
a favor de los strike porque es algo que
In addition, those of us who work in that sector
además los que nos movemos en ese sector
of the gossip We are always very
del salseo Nosotros siempre estamos muy
There you can get a strike and such.
ahí que te pueden meter un strike y tal
you know and we all know that it's [ __ ]
sabes y todos sabemos que es una [__]
and therefore a strike is not usually
y por lo tanto un strike no se suele
getting to that point you know it's not worth asking for
llegar a eso sabes no digna solicitar
a cancellation which was what I did or
una anulación que fue lo que hice o
send a counter notification I don't think so
enviar una contran notificación No creo
I'm not sure what this is what I did.
que fue esto lo que hice no estoy seguro
because in the end I didn't do it, they did it
porque al final no lo hice yo lo hiceron
my lawyers okay Even if you eliminate the
mis abogados vale Aunque elimines el
video will not remove the fake lawyers
vídeo no se quitará las falsos abogados
the manager has become a clown
le gestiona ha quedado como un payaso
uncle has been left looking like a clown
tío ha quedado como un payaso
eh strike the mother who gave birth to me man, I mean
eh strik la madre que me parió tío o sea
I don't know. I'm G about my lawyer.
yo no sé A mí lo de mi abogado me lo G
It makes me laugh, I don't know if it's ghostly or
me hace gracia no sé si es fantasmada o
It's real, I really don't know. It smells to me.
es real la verdad no lo sé A mí me huele
Ricky is always a little bit like that
a Ricky siempre es un poquillo así como
It's me up here I understand that
soy yo aquí arriba Yo entiendo que lo
What the sh meant to say is that yes
que ha querido decir el sh es que si
They say a tremendous amount of things about you
dicen una barbaridad de ti tremendísima
tremendous. Ibay told me that too.
tremendísima Eso me lo dijo ibay también
for example, I wasn't going and Javi told me, I
por ejemplo no ibay me dijo a mí Javi yo
I will never throw away
no voy a tirar nunca
a video
un un vídeo
eem says maybe he told me something like that
eem dice a lo mejor me dijo algo así
as if to
como si a lo
You better publish my mother's address
mejor publicas la dirección de mi madre
or my credit card number to
o mi número de tarjeta de crédito al
you know something like that I understand that
sabes alguna cosa así entiendo que
You still say, well, it's not the one, it's not the one
todavía dices tú Bueno no es la no es
that's what the report is for, but well, you know
para eso el reporte pero bueno sabes
you know but well but man because
sabes pero bueno pero hombre porque
between us Because we criticize each other
entre nosotros Porque nos critiquemos
that does not have
que no tiene
sense So to speak on YouTube the
sentido Por así decirlo en YouTube las
things expire or faster because they throw away
cosas caducan o más rápido porque echan
your case into account with much more
tu caso en cuenta con bastante más
priority or because Well you are already
prioridad o bien porque Bueno ya te está
saying that it will expire the worst time
diciendo que va a caducar la peora vez
I hear it, right? I hope it beats you.
que lo escucho verdad que se te venza
before the strike for having more
antes el strike por por tener más
contact within the man platform
contacto dentro de la plataforma hombre
I understand that you have to have a
entiendo que tienes que tener un
contact what does Ricky say there
contacto qué es lo que dice ahí el Ricky
Uncle is always a little bit like that.
tío siempre es un poquillo así como soy
I up here you know So to speak in
yo aquí arriba sabes Por así decirlo en
YouTube things expire or faster
YouTube la cosa caducan o más rápido
because they take your case into account
porque echan tu caso en cuenta con
much more priority or because
bastante más prioridad o bien porque
Well, your strike expires sooner, yes.
bueno que te caduca antes el strike si
yes yes you are more famous uncle this uncle this
si si eres más famoso tío este tío este
Uncle has been left looking like an idiot but
tío ha quedado como un [__] pero
this is not for a video in the guy
de tío esto no es para un vídeo en el
main uncle or rather more balanced and
principal tío o sea más más compensado y
more forceful than your Stay an expires
más contundente que te caduca el Stay an
if you are famous uncle or this guy is
si eres famoso tío o sea este tío es
[ __ ]
[__]
[Laughs]
[Risas]
This guy is a real tough guy, huh?
tío este tío un mamá racho eh est
saying that it is going to expire that the first one
diciendo que va a caducar que la primera
every time I hear it, the truth is that that is not
vez que lo escucho la verdad que eso no
exists, that is to say, you have there the
existe o sea es que tú tienes ahí la
Norma and how long it lasts and what's up, man?
Norma y lo que te dura y lo que tal tío
what is more clear is that when
qué más marracho claro es que cuando
you do these things is when we get
haces estas cosas es cuando nos ponemos
Let's see its content. You realize that a
a ver Su contenido Tú date cuenta que un
normal video of Ricky Eddie eh Of course
vídeo normal de Ricky Eddie eh Como no
You know, you're having a controversy about something with us, you don't
saes polémica de algo con nosotros no lo
We see, of course, you start to see a but
vemos Claro tú te pones a ver un pero
Of course, all these videos of him
claro todas los vídeos estos de él
fighting with the YouTube kids
peleándose con los chiquillos de YouTube
kit we don't see those controversies
kit no lo vemos las polémicas esas no
we see them then he starts to tell her
las vemos entonces él se pone a decirle
These things happen to people and they happen
estas cosas a la gente y pasan
the strike went unnoticed because of having
desapercibida el strike por por tener
more contact within the platform
más contacto dentro de la plataforma
Man, I understand that you have to have a
hombre entiendo que tienes que tener un
powerful contact the truth I understand that
contacto potente la verdad entiendo que
must have a very powerful contact
ha de tener un contacto muy potente
because they are super tough, man.
porque son super recios tío los de
YouTube eh Freemasonry guys is that
YouTube eh la masonería chavales es que
I understand and I don't understand you know For one
entiendo y no entiendo sabes Por una
part because let's see They are super
parte porque a ver Ellos están super
shot and they have said everything and it is
tiroteados y se han dicho de todo y está
things are super bad between them or because of it
la cosa super mal entre ellos o por lo
less like that it ended and now with that
menos así terminó y ahora con eso
I understand that it's worse, huh?
entiendo que peor eh
I would have cut out the part of this
yo hubiese recortado la parte de est de
This guy cut out the guy part but
este tío recortado la parte tío pero
Let's see when Dallas tries
vamos a ver cuando el Dallas intenta
you put a strike cut the clips
ustedes poner un strike recort los clips
from Dallas that was not cut one
del Dallas que no voa recortado un un
video rewind that is already being worked on
vídeo rewind en el que ya está trabajado
and it's already uploaded and it's already published O
y ya está subido y ya está publicado O
whether I understand that a person puts
sea si yo entiendo que una persona pone
strike because because already from
strike porque porque ya a partir de
Now then, be careful because this guy puts
ahora pues dir cuidado que este tío pone
strike Okay, so maybe from
strike Vale pues a lo mejor a partir de
It's not Juanjo for example, well, already the
es no Juanjo por ejemplo no pues ya los
clips will always be uploaded protected
clips se van a subir siempre protegidos
okay if I have to talk about him or if
vale si tengo que hablar de él o si
look for me to talk about him again but
busca otra vez que hable de él pero
Of course I understand that this guy I
claro que yo entiendo que este tío Yo
I understand that this guy who has some
entiendo que este tío que tiene unas
super demonstrations against the
manifestaciones super en contra de los
Copyright St I understand that it is not going to work for me
St de copyright Yo entiendo que no me va
to trim a rewind a video by
a hacer recortar un rewind un vídeo por
the one I've stopped all month
el que he parado todo el mes de
December I don't understand why it comes out
diciembre no yo entiendo que porque sale
his music of
su música de
background is not going to suit me, it is not going to be cut for me
fondo no me va no me va a ser recortar
the rewind and and remove all that part
el el rewind y y quitar toda esa parte
no, I mean, it's not. Of course you guys
no o sea es que no Claro ustedes que
I would understand why the objective ended
entendería porque Finalizó el objetivo
Yes, I just arrived. Greetings, it's true now.
si acabo de llegar Saludos es verdad ya
I was surprised that the target did not rise
me extrañaba que el objetivo no subía se
It has been left at nine and a half hours
ha quedado en nueve media hora a lo
I was better off making a mistake and putting it
mejor me he equivocado y le he puesto
half an hour and it has stopped Oh f
media hora y se ha parado Oh f
f guy really I don't have to
f tío de verdad que no tengo que
cut out the part that I don't have to
recortar la parte que no tengo que
cut the southern part
recortar la parte Sur
damn what Rick has done is a
[__] que lo que ha hecho Rick es una
dirty or I would have put another one
guarrada o le hubiese puesto otra
song or whatever, man, anything and
canción o yo que sé tío cualquier cosa y
would have cut through the hoops because the
hubiese cortado por los aro porque la
The truth is that it hurts me more, uncle.
verdad es que me duele más tío me
It would hurt more to forgive the fact of knowing that
dolería Más perdón el hecho de saber que
I don't have the video anymore, it's that guy who
ya no tengo el vídeo es que tío que al
final Put the strike stays the
final Pon el strike se queda la
monetization you get a strike and you
monetización te comes un strike y te
you are left without video, it's that she's a [ __ ].
quedas sin vídeo es que es una [__] Es
that the monetization itself is already
que ya lo de la monetización en sí es
a
una
The thing about monetization is that it is dirty
guarrada es que lo de la monetización es
an outrage, that is, it's a 40 minute video
una barbaridad o sea es un vídeo de 40
minutes uncle Hey Well maybe we
minutos tío Oye Pues a lo mejor nos
would have given how much he had 300,000
hubiera dado cuánto tenía 300.000
vistillas man Well maybe we
vistillas hombre Pues a lo mejor nos
I would have given a little money, I don't know
hubiera dado un dinerillo no lo sé
me
me
you understand [ __ ] dude or if I had done
entiendes [__] tío o si hubiese hecho
only the monetization thing is a
solamente lo de la monetización es una
dirty things but well you say Well then the
guarradas pero bueno dices Bueno pues el
The video is there, Ricky 300 stays
vídeo está ahí que se queda el Ricky 300
400 100 eur I don't know how many visits
400 100 eur desconozco Cuántas visitas
I had but well This is how it turned out But
tenía pero bueno Así ha quedado Pero
Well, in that video you will be able to
bueno pues en ese vídeo que Vais a poder
Let's see, Ricky doesn't give a damn.
A ver pues que Ricky No le hace ni [__]
It's not funny that they give him strikes either.
gracia tampoco que le pongan strikes Eh
Well, like any person, uncle who is
pues como a cualquier persona tío que se
dedicated to content creation eh
dedica a la creación de contenido eh
But Javi also wanted to silence the part
Pero Javi también deo silenciar la parte
because it was obvious that she was going to sleep with him
porque era obvio que se lo iba a tirar
It's that before I ate the strike and
Es que yo antes de comerme el strike y
before he throws it at me and no no no no no
antes de que me lo tire y no no no no no
No
no
No, but how are you going to say that, people?
no pero cómo vais a decir eso personas
that you dedicate yourselves to
que os dedicáis a
this but how are you going to say this sure
esto pero cómo vais a decir esto sure
people who dedicate yourselves to putting clips on
personas que os dedicáis a poner clip de
the
la
people So what are you telling me that
gente O sea tú qué me estás diciendo que
Tomorrow threatens you with rebor And you no longer put
mañana te amenaza rebor Y tú ya no pones
plus a click of rebor no no no no no what
más un click de rebor no no no no no qué
you are me
me estás
counting and the video has to be removed
contando y el vídeo lo tenga que quitar
and I cut the whole roll
y todo el rollo yo lo recorto los
silences Apart from sucking everything
silencios A parte a chupar todo lo
possible to throw away the content because it is
posible por tirar el contenido porque es
very likely to see what happens with this
muy probable a ver lo que pasa con esto
Uncle, in the end, when you enter that
tío que al final Cuando entras ya en esa
modality what is going to happen is that
modalidad lo que va a ocurrir es que
when Ricky sees something about Javi that
cuando Ricky ve algo de Javi por lo que
the other one is going to go on fire with a
sea el otro le vaya a ir a fuego con un
strike also You know why in the end Eye
strike también Sabes porque al final Ojo
by eye in the end not like that no no no no no
por ojo al final no así no no no no no
No, I'm not going to end up like Ricky O.
no yo no voy a quedar igual que Ricky O
I already have 1000, I already have 1000 videos
sea ya tengo 1000 ya tengo 1000 vídeos
where Ricky puts things
donde Ricky pone cosas
mine, not me, I don't have to wait
mías yo no que no me tengo que esperar
have Ricky put something of mine
que Ricky ponga una cosa mía
I'm not going to do it
no lo voy a
do what I have to do
hacer para qué me tengo que
wait for what do I have to wait for
esperar a qué me tengo que esperar
Let's summarize like this
vamos a resumir así
no this is it
no esto es
mine Wow good before you start talking
mío Wow buen antes de empezar a hablar
of this
de este
topic this is mine look
tema esto es mío mira
Here I see a live show
aquí veo un directo
mine here another and here another you know how much
mío aquí otro y aquí otro sabéis Cuánta
pasta is a mill
pasta es un mill
300,000 of you know how much pasta
300.000 sabéis Cuánta pastas
1,300,000 of a one-hour video of a
1,300000 de un vídeo de una hora de un
one-hour video
vídeo de una hora
1,300,000 I eat at least 5,000 at least there are
1,300000 yo como poco 5000 como poco hay
here
aquí
like few others
como pocos
5000 I knock it down I take it away
5000 se lo tumbo le quito la
monetization
monetización
no no obviously
no no evidentemente
not here in the layer video there was a clip
no aquí en el vídeo de capa había clip
I throw the video to the layer to the
mío le tiro el vídeo a capa al
[ __ ] of cape and then also
[__] de capa y luego también se
threw it at Ricky No How much does this have a
lo tiró a Ricky No Cuánto tiene esto un
a million and a bit
millón y pico
It is also not done after
también no se hace tras
back here if I'm not mistaken too
trás aquí si no me equivoco también
I put my CP on one of these parts
ponía CP mío en una de las partes estas
What did he do with the photocopy, I think?
que hizo con la fotocopia creo que que
put my clip
puso clip mío
Also here is a clip of mine
también Aquí también tiene clip mío
Well, in fact, in fact, look
bueno es que de hecho de hecho fijaros
One thing I am Ricky, I'm going to tell you one thing
una cosa soy Ricky os voy a decir una
The thing is that he is a scoundrel but
cosa es que es un Sinvergüenza pero
Come on, look, see if it is
vamos Mira fijaros si es
Scoundrel
Sinvergüenza
Do you remember this?
esto esto que estáis viendo os acordáis
of this that he sent it to his editor and
de esto que se lo mandó él a su editor y
He also tweeted this clip.
lo lo tuiteó también el clip esto El
scoundrel This is from a live for
sinvergüenza Este es de un directo para
members this is from a live for
miembros esto es de un directo para
members and he took it all the way up her [ __ ]
miembros y el cogio por toda su [__]
face would become a member of whatever it was
cara se se haría miembro lo que fuera el
editor first took my click
editor primero cogió el click mío
talking to Pablo he edited it to lie
hablando con Pablo lo editó para mentir
because on top of that he edited it to defame, okay?
porque encima lo editó para difamar vale
saying that we had cut the live stream
diciendo que habíamos cortado el directo
running because Dala called us to
corriendo porque dala nos llamó para
filthy you filthy I'm worth he took this
guarro tú guarro yo vale él cogió este
direct that was for member took out the
directo que era para miembro sacó el
Click with his balls put it on Twitter
click con sus [__] lo puso en Twitter
and here a 700,000 video was made
y aquí se hizo un vídeo de 700,000
visits eh
visitas eh
I have thrown the video because the click
yo le he tirado el vídeo porque el click
It was for a member because the live for
era para miembro porque el directo para
member No, I haven't even thrown it at Ricky or
miembro No ni se lo he tirado a Ricky ni
to none of those who clicked that
a ninguno de los que puso el click que
They all put it because why? Because I am not
lo pusieron todos por qué Porque no soy
a [ __ ] filthy piece of [ __ ] like him
un [__] guarro de [__] como él
eh Because it is my content for
eh Porque es un contenido mío para
member to have taken and told you to go
miembro haber cogido y haber dicho iros
to see it on Javi's Channel which is for
a verlo al Canal de Javi que está para
member
miembro
Of course, but for you to lie because you are
Claro pero para tú mentir porque tú eres
for you, ...
para guarro tú guarro yo cogiste un clip
a member for the [ __ ] face is worth it
a miembro por la putísima cara vale
Here he got angry because we put the video on it
aquí se picó porque le pusimos el vídeo
of the
de la
Banana sucking Win Michu's banana
banana chupándole la banana A Win michu
and here he started to take out my clip
y aquí se puso a sacar clip mío
cropped trying to understand the
recortado intentando entender la
my controversy with my with the threats that
polémica mía con mi con las amenazas que
They made me and all that stuff without
me hicieron y todo el rollo ese sin
have no [ __ ] idea without having been there
tener ni [__] idea sin haber estado se
He invented it for the [ __ ] face and he for
lo inventó por la [__] cara y él por
because he was scratched he defended Miare from
porque estaba rayado defendió a miare de
the sentence
la sentencia
ok look here all my clips that
vale mira aquí todos los clips míos que
puts
pone
look at a
mira un
a lot of it is worth it or what are we talking about?
montón vale o sea de qué estamos
talking look here too a lot of
hablando mira aquí también un montón de
My clip
Clip mío
also that it makes no sense that there is no
también que no tiene sentido que no hay
There is no way to grasp it, that is, I am
no hay por donde cogerlo o sea yo de
It's true that No, it's not that we are in a bad mood
verdad lo de No no es que estamos a mala
It's that we are in bad shape, it's that I don't
es que estamos a mala es que yo no
I understand that we are on bad terms and then
entiendo que estamos a mala y entonces
they put strike is that no no no no no
se ponen strike es que no no no no no
none of it makes sense really. I mean
tiene sentido ninguno de verdad O sea
no sense works people in
ningún sentido funciona la gente en
General: Eh, then maybe he'll come.
general Eh entonces a lo mejor llega
Ricky who has to react something
Ricky que tiene que reaccionar algo de
Javi Because he has an exclusive because
Javi Porque tiene una exclusiva porque
I don't know what and what the other does, he takes it and
no sé qué y qué hace el otro coge y le
If you get a strike, then you start with
mete strike pues pues ya empiezas con
That and you don't end up badly, to be honest, let's see.
eso y no acabas mal la verdad a veremos
Let's see, there's some [ __ ], the truth is that
a ver hay una [__] yo la verdad es que
I do not agree at all with putting a
no estoy nada de acuerdo con poner un
strike a Javi man fraud slow you can
strike a Javi hombre fraud lento puedes
say well Okay it has been left
decir bueno Vale se ha quedado la
monetization what a dirty bastard by
monetización menudo guarro cabronazo por
200 bucks or whatever but the strike is already
200 pavos o lo que sea pero el strike ya
I think it wasn't 200 for sure
me parece 200 seguro que no era
It was probably more than that, it seems to me.
seguramente eraa más es que me parece tu
more you uncle is that we can not say another
más tí tío es que no podemos decir otra
thing Nor because it is not something else
cosa Tampoco porque no es otra cosa la
that he thinks at the end when he gives the seal
que piense al final cuando da la selida
to put strike uncle to the gang because he
a poner strike tío a la peña porque le
the [ __ ] comes out because it seems the same to me
sale la [__] pues me parece igual de
Bad, really, nothing, luckily I have one
mal la verdad nada por suerte tengo un
group of lawyers of the whorehouse
conjunto de abogados de la putísima
Damn, they've [ __ ] the ass of the
[__] que se han follado el culo de la
person who did the manual review by
persona que hizo la revisión manual por
the one where I got the second strike and
la que se me metió el segundo strike y
Mick A doesn't work for you now.
ahora no trabaja para vosotros mick A
Sometimes it's very mind-blowing, eh, I mean, trust yourself.
veces es muy alucine eh o sea fíate tú
the clowning we have seen here three or
la payasada hemos visto aquí tres o
four antics in one pleas pl we have
cuatro payasadas en un pleas pl hemos
seen here three or four antics in one
visto aquí tres o cuatro payasadas en un
pis pl that has a group of lawyers
pis pl que tiene un conjunto de abogados
who have [ __ ] someone's ass
que se han follado el culo de un
YouTube worker who are in
trabajador de YouTube que están en
Philippines those of the support of a
Filipinas los del soporte de un
YouTube worker who rejected a
trabajador de YouTube que le rechazó una
appeal and then they kicked him out
apelación y entonces lo echaron de
YouTube thanks to the lawyers of that is
YouTube gracias a los abogados de o sea
What a clown, there's no one else. I mean, yes.
es que menudo payaso no hay más O sea si
This would be done by Dallas if this was done
esto lo hiciera el Dallas si esto lo
if Dallas opened the [ __ ]
hiciera el Dallas abren los [__]
newscasts if Dallas were to get to
telediarios si el Dallas se pusiera a
Saying this opens the [ __ ] news
decir esto abren los [__] telediarios
uncle who has some [ __ ] lawyers
tío que tiene unos abogados de la [__]
host that they fired a guy from a job
[__] que echaron de un trabajo a un
YouTube worker imagine that
trabajador de YouTube imaginaros que
says
dice
alone Let's go let's go let's go Good today
solas Vamos vamos vamos vamos Bueno hoy
On Twitter I actually shared one that
en Twitter de hecho compartí una que
said Dallas that has
dijo el Dallas eso ha
said or rather he is a mythomaniac uncle and the
dicho o sea es un mitómano tío y la
People have to understand it. Now as it is
gente tiene que entenderlo Ya como lo
to identify it as what it is
que identificarlo como lo que es un
A mythomaniac who lies all the time is worth it.
mitómano que miente todo el tiempo vale
Look, Dasas says, but how can he be so
mira dice dasas pero cómo puede ser tan
liar because someone tweeted at him
mentiroso porque alguien le pone un twit
what Ricky said and to which I
lo que dijo Ricky doento y a la que yo
I do it there, Twitch, they take it away from me
le haga haí Twitch me lo quitan que
Dallas called a fraudulent strike on him
Dallas le puso un strike fraudulento
but to the one who does this to her
pero que a la que él le hace así a
Twitch Twitch I am the king of Twitch no
Twitch Twitch Yo soy el rey de Twitch no
I don't pay attention to either of them or to Gref, but to me
le hago caso ni a ni a gref pero a mí a
the one I do like this to the one I do like this
la que le hago así a la que le hago así
They obviously took it away from me after two days
me lo quitan obiamente a los dos días
less than 48 hours the strike was
men de 48 horas el strike estaba
retired because I told Twitch I
retirado porque le dije a Twitch he
state that in less than 48 hours the est
estado que en menos de 48 horas el est
he was off reacting to a
estaba quitado reaccionando a un
content above is a secondary channel
contenido encima es un canal secundario
of a person who had a debate with
de una persona que hizo un debate con
another one that does give me permission to re
otra que sí que me da permiso para re
turn it on because at that time Ah me
accionarlo porque en esa época Ah me
said reacts that friends Welcome to
dijo reacciona que amigos Bienvenidos a
It's true, but it sounds to me like this is a lie.
it tal pero me suena que esto es mentira
I think it expired. Ah, because it was
Me parece que le caducó Ah porque estaba
I got a strike on Twitch that I no longer
me metti un strike en Twitch que ya no
I have them because luckily they expire now
tengo porque ahora por suerte caducan
let's listen to this again, it's expired, you're screwed
escuchemos esto de nuevo caducó te jodes
who laugh at you to say haha ​​they have you
que se ríen de ti para decir jaj te han
I was banned for some reason, too, at one time
baneado no sé qué a mí en su día también
He told me to be careful because I was
me me dijo que que cuidado porque estaba
He gave me a strike on Twitch that was already
me metió un strike en Twitch que ya pues
I don't have any because luckily they expire now.
no tengo porque ahora por suerte caducan
the expiration on Twitch I don't know how long
el caducar en Twitch no sé cuánto tiempo
He gave me a strike with Michu Os.
es a mí me puso un strike with michu os
you agree by copyright on Twitch because
acordáis por copyright en Twitch porque
I left a Bot where I was reacting
me dejé un Bot donde estaba reaccionando
to a clip of him where he warned
a un clip de él que era donde él avisaba
that he could not be told that he was
de que no se le podía decir que se
I wanted to go to Andorra but I had
quería ir a andorra Pero tenía
background that said that there was
antecedente que decía que había
sued people for that
demandado a gente por eso
em and the and if I'm not mistaken yes it expired
em y el y si no me equivoco sí me caducó
but I didn't realize I think they are
pero no me di cuenta yo creo que son se
months I don't know I think it's three months
meses no lo sé creo que son tres meses
plus what expires maybe I think that
más lo que caduca a lo mejor yo creo que
It's a few months at best what
son unos se meses a lo mejor lo que
It takes a while to expire but I'm not sure
tarda en caducar pero no estoy seguro
But we're going in less than 4, trust you, he's going
pero vamos en menos de 4 fíate tú él va
inventing the clown act as he went along
inventando sobre la marcha la payasada
That's really cool, Ricky, eh, at times he
queé muy alucin Ricky eh a ratos el
bastard eh Look, as she said
cabrón eh Mira pues como decía la
song that the channel has sanctioned you
canción que te ha sancionado el canal lo
I feel that
siento es que
I wouldn't leave it in the hands of a person
yo no dejaría en manos de una persona
that with which I have had this type of de
que con la que he tenido este tipo de de
inconvenient I would not leave in the hands of
inconveniente yo no dejaría en manos de
that person neither the monetization nor the
esa persona ni la monetización ni el
copyright or anything dude the truth is that
copyright ni nada tío la verdad es que
No man, the truth is that no way, man.
no tío la verdad es que ni de [__] tío
This is already beyond repair.
esto ya pues esto ya no se arregla esto
Now they're going to [ __ ] on Piña La
Ahora se van a [__] a Piña La
True Well here there are too many
verdad Bueno aquí ya Hay demasiadas
moves uncle who is not saying that I
movidas tío que no está diciendo que yo
I also try to copy because of this that neither
también meo try de copy por esto que ni
I reported it because I can't be responsible for it.
lo reporté yo que no me lo puede estar
making it so easy Who is Javiel
poniendo tan fácil Quién es javiel
canine this is the war there will be movement No
canino esto es la guer habrá movida No
This has become very personal now.
ya esto se tornó muy personal ahora Está
Also the thing about Lali, which is a pain in the ass
también lo de Lali que es una putada que
that it is already in those terms because uncle
que esté ya en esos términos porque tío
There are times when Javi is going to need
hay veces que Javi va a necesitar
react to Ricky is likely Rick
reaccionar a Ricky es probable que Rick
At some point I want to respond to Javi
en algún momento quiera responder a Javi
and I have to see some video of him and if
y tenga que ver algún vídeo de él y si
is that I'm going to do it is that I'm going to do it
es que lo voy a hacer es que lo voy a
do so I understand if they close my channel
hacer as entiend si me cierran el canal
I open another one or I go to Kick and they go to
me abro otro o me voy a Kick y van a
be clear they are going to be with the with the
estar claro van a estar con las con las
sharp nails well without further ado I come
uñas afiladas bueno sin más Yo vengo
here to see it but the strikes Well
aquí a verlo pero los strikes Pues
There are always bad people, just like what happened
siempre están mal personas igual lo de
Rick throwing the video to ito eh the C the
Rick tirándole el video a ito eh el C el
Cel has condemned it more forcefully
cel lo ha condenado con más contundencia
olive tree because it burned What is it what is it
oliveira porque se ardió Qué es qué es
that burning because it used 20 seconds of
eso de arderse porque usó 20 segundos de
a song nothing for me The strikes no
una canción nada para mí Los strikes no
They are so good I'm going to have one
está tan buenos me voy a tomar una
beer with gibel when I come to Spain
cerveza con gibel cuando venga a España
eh, I mean it doesn't matter which part of the
eh o sea da igual a la parte de la
Peninsula that goes or is if it is in
Península que vaya o sea si está en
Asturias I'm going to go up to Asturias to
asturia voy a subir a asturia para
have a beer with gibel, eh, or whatever
tomarme una cerveza con gibel eh o sea
since he has become a child again and
desde que ha vuelto a ser chavalería y
pambisito how are you based
pambisito cómoo anda de basado tú
It burns a lot because you're getting into it
se arde mucho porque te estás metiendo
with the other person's work eh Y
con el trabajo de la otra persona eh Y
The crying grandfather is here too
ya está el abuelo llorón también ha
said that I'm going
dicho que me va
but what does this give a certificate?
a pero este qué da un un certificado
So don't leave me with the campaign.
Entonces no me dejéis lo de la campaña
from Go F me because if not I need it
del Go F me porque si no me hace falta
for one I will need it for the other
para uno me va a hace falta para el otro
and if I'm not going to need it for both of us
y si no me va a hace falta para los dos
has been using My Name since 2023 and
lleva desde 2023 utilizando Mi Nombre e
image to profit by lying about me
imagen para lucrar mintiendo sobre mi
life eye What does that sound like to you by Javier
vida ojo A qué os suena eso por Javier
understand Javier Oliveira using Mi
entiéndase Javier oliveira utilizando Mi
Name and image for
Nombre e imagen para
lying about my life but not only that
mintiendo sobre mi vida pero no solo so
yours, Loli's, werta, Peppa's
la tuya la de Loli werta la de Peppa
Beltrán the one from Troy the one from no no uncle
Beltrán la de de Troya la de no no tío
Nobody takes a picture of my team
nadie me hace la foto del equipito de
football with all of them, I mean, go go
fútbol con todos ellos o sea vaya vaya
clan eh or what clan if I don't come
clan eh o sea vaya clan si lo no vengo
I have also used this and it is
también la usado esto la es ha
defendant gender defects Who is the
demandado vicia de género Quién es el
Pablo's girlfriend's lawyer
abogado del abogado la novia de Pablo
Whoever comes out brings them a photo, because Pablo
quién sale los traen una foto pues Pablo
the girlfriend and the girl are going to attack me
la novia y la muchacha la es a agredirme
And what And what And if Pablo is the lawyer of
Y qué Y qué Y si Pablo es el abogado de
Ali for the complaint that the
Ali por la denuncia que le ha puesto la
Ali to Ricky about gender violence and what
Ali a Ricky de violencia de género y qué
and what and what if it is Paul if it were David
y qué y qué si es Pablo si fuera David
Bravo you would like more And what if it is
Bravo os gustaría más Y qué si es
Pablo specifically To jump all the
Pablo concretamente A saltarle todo la
glasses on the head and all the teeth and
gafas de la cabeza y todos los dientes y
instead of giving him an indefinite leave
en vez de ponerle una falta indefinida
that I had the option to apply it and I would have
que tuve opción de aplicarla y le habría
taken down the channel directly or YouTube
tumbado el canal directamente o YouTube
Studio gives you the option to change it to
Studio te da la opción de cambiarla por
another is to say that it doesn't even have to go down
otra es decir que no tiene ni que bajar
the video without losing visits or anything
el vídeo ni perder visita ni nada Muchas
thanks this Random also to you
gracias este Random también te la
you change for another one but what did Javier do?
cambias por otra pero qué hizo Javier
oliveiro yori Yoro Yoro for my saints
oliveiro yori Yoro Yoro por mis santos
balls that I can sing the r song
[__] que la canción de r yo la puedo
use because it is from my own library and
usar porque es de mi propia biblioteca y
I'm going to appeal because it is because for
voy a recurrir el porque es Es que para
What are you going to argue with this one?
qué vas a discutir con este
I have messed up the Stay or the lack that I have
pringado el Stay o la falta que me ha
stuck in that the other one doesn't stick it in the other one
metido que no se la mete el otro el otro
says he has a week to download it Who
dice tiene una semana para bajarlo Quién
Is this hairless gentleman Javi the only one?
es este señor sin pelo Javi el único
able to defend Ricky Eddy this raet
capaz de defender a Ricky Eddy este raet
Well, Joan, the gang can't do it.
bueno la Joan no la cuadrilla le puede
commit a foul at the moment commit one
meter una falta al momento meter un de
those copywriters and they knock him down and put him in
esos de copy y le tumban el y le meten
a foul on the Channel for using that but
una falta al Canal por usar eso pero le
gave the option of 7 days to remove that
dio la opción de 7 días para quitar eso
and asked to be given one more week
y solicitó que le dieren una semana más
eye was already crying before the trip to
ojo ya estaba llorando antes del viaje a
New York during the New York trip
Nueva York durante el vieje de Nueva
York kept crying What do you do with that?
York seguía llorando Qué hace con eso
generate controversy on your channel, which means
generar polémica en su canal con lo cual
What you lose from the RWI you will recover
lo que pierda del rwi lo va a recuperar
with other videos that are going to be made
con otro vídeos que va a hacer se va a
hit 2020 no no no no what I lose
pegar el 2020 no no no no lo que pierda
I'm going to recover it from the rewind here.
del rewind lo lo voy a recuperar aquí
with super chat ok or there is family
con super chat vale o sea familia hay
Here 2300 people what I have lost from
aquí 2300 personas lo que he perdido del
rewi are exactly
rewi son exactamente
2300 with a do each we arrive ok
2300 con un dó cada uno llegamos vale
Please 25 talking Remembering the rwi that
porfa 25 hablando Recordando el rwi que
He knocked him down, explaining to him that if he kept
le tumbó r explicándole que si mantenía
My song would receive a strike, that is to say
mi canción recibiría Un strike es decir
that the platform is already in contact
que ya la plataforma se pone en contacto
with Javier Oliveira telling him if you
con Javier oliveira diciéndole si te
If you persist in continuing along this path, we will
empecina en seguir por ahí te vamos a
get a strike so you already know the drills
meter un strike con lo cual ya sabes las
YouTube called me, the gentleman called me
me llamó YouTube me llamó el señor
YouTube and he said to me if you don't know how to fit in
YouTube y me dijo si te si no se cabes
Son Javi is Ricky's song, okay? No
son Javi es de Ricky la canción vale No
You have the right, Javi, that's it.
tienes derecho Javi ya está
Javier, a video in New York, to me it is
javien un vídeo en Nueva York a mí si lo
you want it, I'll give it to you, I don't care
quiere yo se lo doy a mí no me importa
I give him the money, I don't know why
el dinero yo se lo doy yo no sé por qué
the platform warms its head in
se calienta la cabeza la plataforma en
change management by changing the rules
cambiar la gestión en cambiar las normas
in adapting to the times when only
en adaptarse a los tiempos cuando solo
They have to consult with Javi Oliveira
tienen que consultar con Javi oliveira
What do they have to do because the one who puts
Qué tienen que hacer porque el que pone
the rules are he who the followers of
las normas es él que los seguidores de
Javi Oliveira Not everyone understands the
Javi oliveira No todos entienden la
Ricky's posture, eh yes, he
postura de Ricky eh si el
rwi than the followers of Javi oliveira
rwi que los seguidores de Javi oliveira
Not everyone understands Ricky's position.
No todos entienden la postura de Ricky
What I don't understand is the position that
Lo que no entiendo yo es la postura que
you are sitting in that chair and why
tienes tú sentado en esa silla y por qué
damn, you have your knee, your head, Antonio
[__] tienes la rodilla la cabeza Antonio
That's what I don't understand.
eso es lo que yo no entiendo hubiese
been up in tea, gossip is kicked
estado subido en tes salseo se da patada
in the ass to cut the 2 minutes
en el culo para recortar los 2 minutos
of song If it had been uploaded in
de canción Si hubiese estado subido en
the salseria kicks its ass for
la salsería se da patada en el culo para
cut the song Because those channels
recortar la canción Porque esos canales
You can't stop it for a week or 9 days or
no puede pararlo una semana ni 9 días ni
may have a penalty that
puede tener una penalización que
It means that they give you a sh that you
conlleva que te metan un sh que te
recommends less with which you get
recomienda menos con lo cual te entra
fewer people at the door and already quite a few
menos gente por la puerta y ya bastantes
losses have during 2024 as for
pérdidas tiene durante el 2024 como para
start 2025 with more losses
empezar 2025 con más pérdidas los
channels and
canales y
sanctioning But then if I have
sancionando Pero entonces si tengo
loss Antonio Why do you criticize me that
pérdida Antonio Por qué me criticas que
make me a box if I have losses
me haga una una caja si tengo pérdidas
I need, I need to eat, that is, if I have
necesito necesito comer o sea si tengo
losses Why why don't you leave me
pérdidas Por qué por qué no me dejas
make a box and have people donate to me
hacerme una caja y que la gente me done
in the box that you have criticized that in
en la caja que la has criticado que en
instead of enjoying the days of
vez de estar disfrutando de los días de
New York was more aware of the
Nueva York estaba más pendiente del
phone and record themselves on the street to
teléfono y de grabarse por la calle para
continue uploading content in
seguir subiendo contenido en
networks that instead of worrying about
redes que en vez de preocuparme por
New York was worried about the
Nueva York estaba preocupado del
phone to record content
teléfono por para grabar contenido
totally factor indisputably
totalmente factor indiscutiblemente
I am bitter about life, Antonio.
amargado estoy de la vida Antonio
bitter of the
amargados de la
life and to prepare content for
vida y Para ir preparando contenido para
telesalseo and the salsería because In
telesalseo y la salsería porque En
definitively whoever watches telesalseo has seen
definitiva quien ve telesalseo ha visto
What happens what will happen next in
Lo que pasa lo que luego va a pasar en
the salseria the same content repeated
la salsería el mismo contenido repetido
He tells you twice and that's it.
te lo vuelve a contar dos veces y punto
but he hasn't done it because he hasn't been given it
pero no lo ha hecho porque no le ha dado
wins her over by telling her that you have
la gana diciéndole que que te ha
your girlfriend invented the trick, they raped her
inventado tu novia el avío la violaron
Knowing the history Because besides that
Sabiendo la historia Porque además que
he told her
se la contó
Ricky doesn't even know what he's saying.
Ricky no sabe ni lo que está diciendo
this grandfather and he stands there to tell
este abuelo y se pone ahí a a contarle a
People, trust you, no one is talking
la gente fíate tú no está hablando nadie
in the chat uncle the chat is empty of the
en el chat tío el chat está vacío de la
people who will have fallen asleep, I don't know.
gente que se habrá dormido yo t sabe el
These people here in the chat are really screwed.
pringado este la gente aquí en el chat
doesn't speak This is the chat This is not a
no habla Este es el chat Esto no es un
black square on the face or this is it
cuadrado negro por la cara o sea esto es
the chat that when someone talks in it
el chat que cuando alguien habla en el
chat appears here or I don't know if in
chat aparece aquí o sea no sé si en
sometime look see it at some
algún momento mira lo ve en algún
some message will appear now
momento aparecerá algún mensaje ahora
We'll see, okay. But trust yourself what he says.
veremos vale Pero fíate tú lo que le
He is telling that Ricky told me the
está contando que Ricky me ha contado la
history that what what speaks pingado If it is
historia que qué qué habla pingado Si se
It has been told all over the internet
la ha contado todo internet que se
he invented a rape so he wouldn't swallow it
inventó una violación para no tragarse
to not assume that they had put him
los para no asumir que le habían puesto
the horns during those days took out the
los cuernos durante esos días sacó los
audios where the ex-girlfriend told the
audios donde la la exnovia le decía a la
friend you swear by your family by your
amiga tú juras por tu familia por tus
dead, I don't know what, but I swore that
muertos pu no sé qué pero que jurase que
The bride was very angry. The bride No.
la novia se enfadó muchísimo la novia No
the ex-girlfriend because Ricky currently
la exnovia porque Ricky actualmente
He has another very pretty girlfriend too
tiene otra novia muy guapa también por
true as Ricky says put you in
cierto como dice Ricky te Pon en
contact me so that he can sue me for
contacto con mi para que me demande por
because of gender violence is that I
por violencia de género es que que yo me
I have contacted it gives validity to
he puesto en contacto le da validez a
Whatever Ricky says, [ __ ] off.
todo lo que diga Ricky a tomar por culo
okay or so he is his job here He ASSUMES
vale o sea él su trabajo aquí Él ASUME
by the people who follow him who are haters
por la gente que le sigue que son hater
that he has taken eh For the people who go to him
que ha cogido eh Por la gente que le va
to support him a little he ASSUMES he has me
a apoyar un poco él ASUME que me tiene
to contradict me and support
que dar la contraria a mí y apoyar a
Anyone who is against me is fine.
todo el que esté en contra mía Vale
then he does not discuss one iota of
entonces él no discute ni un ápice de
Ricky's entire text is worth nothing.
todo el texto de Ricky ni un ápice vale
So I have contacted the ex of
o sea que yo he contactado con la ex de
Ricky to file a complaint against him
Ricky para que le ponga una denuncia
Now it turns out that it is my fault that
Ahora resulta que es culpa mía que a
Ricky, give him a level, you trust him, eh?
Ricky le pongan una fíate tú el nivel eh
That is to say the level is that it is my fault that
o sea el nivel es que es culpa mía que a
He tells Ricky to get one
él le que al Ricky le pongan una
complaint, that is, Ricky should put a strike
denuncia o sea Ricky que ponga un strike
chill my fault okay but that to Ricky Lo
chill culpa mía vale pero que a Ricky Lo
report gender violence
denuncien por violencia de género
it is also fault
también es culpa
mine is that we are not talking about a
mía es que no estamos hablando de una
joke If you are aware that Ricky
broma Si tú eres consciente de que Ricky
Eddie has not mistreated that person and
Eddie no ha maltratado a esa persona y y
He has put you in touch as Ricky says
te ha puesto en contacto como dice Ricky
He's in contact with my ex to
está puesto en contacto con mi ex para
to report me for gender violence
que me denuncie por violencia de género
If he is convicted of domestic violence
Si a él lo condenan por violencia de
gender the first thing to separate from
género lo primero que se aparte de
fall upon you the sentence of condemning you to get involved
caerte la condena de condenarte meterte
In a prison he does not set foot in any other Andorra than
en una cárcel no pisa más andorra que
He's trying to screw up Ricky's life.
está intentando joderle la vida a Ricky
edy everywhere and is
edy por todos partes y está
Yori, if they condemn him, it's my fault.
yori que si lo condenan es culpa mía yo
It's that I can't take it anymore, eh, it's me no longer
es que ya no puedo más eh sea yo ya no
I can do more than if they condemn him, which is
puedo más que si lo condenan que es
my fault
culpa mía
so for a rig set the level of evil
eho por un rig fijar el nivel de maldad
I'm talking to your ex-girlfriend about this guy.
de este tío hablo con tu exnovia para
that he sues you for violence of what you see
que te demande por violencia de lo ves
You see this is the chat that actually happens
lo ves esto es el chat en realidad pasa
that there are people who are saying this
que está la gente que está diciendo este
uncle who is telling me gender that I think
tío que me está contando género que creo
what has been put on it if that
que ha sido lo que le ha puesto si esa
lawsuit goes ahead against Ricki apart from
demanda sale adelante a ricki aparte de
cost you compensation money
costarle dinero de indemnización
cost him time in jail because
costarle tiempo en la cárcel porque lo
They are going to put him in jail, it costs him that
van a meter en la cárcel le cuesta que
In Andorra you can't, you can't
en andorra tú no puedes no puedes
reside with a criminal record and
residir con con antecedentes penales y
Man knows all that, because yes
todo eso lo sabe hombre pues si lo
They condemn what should have happened
condenan pues lo que Tendría que haber
done something that is not condemnable to
hecho algo que no sea condenable a de
Troy or so but trust you what is
Troya o sea pero fíate tú lo que está
saying eh, I mean if they condemn him now
diciendo eh o sea si lo condenan ya
They have the defense prepared if necessary.
tienen preparado la defensa si lo
They condemn what they are going to say is guilt
condenan lo que van a decir que es culpa
Javi's, damn Javi, it's your fault
de Javi [__] Javi es que por tu culpa
Ricky is in jail, it's mind-blowing.
Ricky está en la cárcel yo es alucinante
This little team is amazing or not.
este equipito o no es alucinante a
What do you think about telling me?
ustedes qué os parece contarme
That is, it is not
O sea no es
Amazing Senda, I love you so much
alucinante Senda te quiero Muchísimas
thanks thanks to you I have the
gracias gracias a ti tengo la
rewind monetization Because if it were
monetización del rewind Porque si fuera
for the others Senda That is not
por los demás Senda O sea no es
hallucinatory
alucinante
Uncle, I see the sense in it, man, it makes sense.
tío yo le veo sentido hombre tiene
a lot of sense if you think So that
muchísimo sentido si pensáis O sea que
If they put him in jail, what do you do?
si lo meten en la cárcel fich tú qué
barbarity eh because of me what I have
barbaridad eh por mi culpa lo que he
done How bad or what is it like What O sea
hecho Qué malo o sea es como What O sea
what what I mean I don't know aunt Are they real Or
qué qué O sea no he tía Son de verdad O
I have never seen dumber people in the
sea no he visto gente más tonta en la
life that What is this character is that I
vida que Qué es este personaje es que yo
I don't know with what head they think
no sé con qué cabeza piensan los
Javi Olivera's followers if they are
seguidores de Javi Olivera si es que son
idiots if that is what he said
idiotas si es que son lo que ha dicho
Ricky Ed I just don't know what to think anymore
Ricky Ed Es que yo ya no sé qué pensar
of those people Every day you are
de esa gente Todos los días te está
telling a different lie tells you
contando una mentira diferente te cuenta
different versions takes bits of you
versiones diferentes te coge trocitos de
click the nice thing is that they award me to
click lo bonito es que me adjudiquen a
me talking about abortion when I don't
mí de hablar de aborto cuando yo no
had not opened his mouth nor was he knowledgeable
había abierto la boca ni era conocedor
about that that Oh
de eso eso Ay
Perea laziness is making me sleepy
Perea pereza me está dando hasta sueño
Micao, I have to take the dog out, man, that's it.
micao tengo que sacar el perro tío es lo
best car and I have to record a video
mejor car y tengo que grabar un vídeo
for the main one that comes to you in
para el principal que a ti te llegue en
the order and I have to do one
la orden y tengo que tengo que hacer una
transfer to my lawyer that I don't know
transferencia a mi abogado que no se me
forget about hate and a guy from the north of
olvid de odio y un tío del norte de
Spain making you a video that it was a
España haciéndote un vídeo de que era un
son of a [ __ ] that if they were your clay and you
hijo de [__] que si fueran su barro y te
He pounded with a stick that if I don't know what everyone
machacaba a palo que si no sé qué todos
I have suffered them because I said that
los he que yo sufrí porque yo dije que
Nature and God are wise when
la naturaleza y Dios son sabios cuando
They don't give children to certain people
no le dan hijos a ciertas personas a
certain women and certain people
ciertas mujeres y a ciertas personas
like me who hasn't given me children. Listen, then
como a mí que no me ha da hijos Oye pues
I take it for her And what the hell do I know about
se lo tomo por ella Y yo qué [__] sé de
your life and if you start repeating it
tu vida y si encima te pones a repetirlo
and repeat it until the uncle that this
y a repetirlo hasta las tío de que esto
They do this a lot, that is, they do this
esto lo hacen mucho o sea esto lo hacen
a lot of the people on the team
mucho la las personas estas del equipito
What they do is that when they leave
em lo que hacen es que cuando se van
uniting together because they are
uniendo entre sí por el porque son
Victims of Jabi
Víctimas de jabi
[Laughs]
[Risas]
oliveira what they do is Search for that
oliveira lo que hacen es Buscar que que
that each member supports him in his cause
que cada miembro le apoye en su causa
Okay, for example, Joan Planas, what is it?
vale por ejemplo Joan planas qué es lo
What I'm looking for by joining the team then
que busco juntándose con el equipo pues
that they support him because they have
que le apoyen a él que a él lo han
harassed that he didn't bother anyone and
acosado que él no se metía con nadie y
We sank him for free. Okay.
le hundimos por la cara de gratis Vale
What is Antonia looking for?
qué es lo que busca la Antonia
approaching the little team because she is
acercándose al equipito pu que ella es
a poor victim who bids her good night
una pobre víctima que la buenas noches
Here is the contribution of this humble panitto
Aquí el aporte de este humilde panitto
There is a rumor that there will be a raffle in the
hay un rumor que habrá sorteo en el
extensible Juan Bueno could be a
extensible Juan bueno podría ser una
idea but I want money because I'm going to
idea pero quiero dinero porque voy a
wish for something if money but yes yes Juan
sorar algo si dinero pero sí sí Juan
Thank you, money is also accepted from
Gracias también se acepta dinero de
Panchitos bastards These are click that me
Panchitos cabrones Estos son clic que me
They cut and then I can't tell him
recortan y yo luego no le puedo decir
racist to Ricky Eddy okay listen to me
racista al Ricky Eddy vale escúchame
listen to me, do you understand me, that is, among themselves
escúchame me entendéis o sea entre ellos
What they do is that Peppa joins
lo que hacen es eso la Peppa se une a
These people, why, why, why
esta gente para que la para que para que
Damn, they supported Tania's situation all the time.
[__] lo de la Tania apoyaron todo el
world to Tania supported Tania uncle
mundo a la Tania apoyaron a la Tania tío
which is like uncle the worst thing you think you are
que es como tío lo peor que te crees que
No one will ever support you because they support you.
nunca nadie va a apoyar pues lo apoyan O
be the pppa it is not that the pppa thing is
sea la pppa no es que lo de la pppa lo
Of the 240, it is already off, that is
de los 240 es que ya está apagado o sea
A woman collects money in a live show
una señora recoge dinero en un directo
saying it's for cancer and he is
diciendo que es para el cáncer y se le
forget to donate it and in 7 months he fights with
olvida donarlo y en 7 meses se pelea con
a friend and the friend tells him so
un amigo y el amigo se lo dice se lo
reproaches and then runs away
echa en cara y entonces va corriendo el
Monday morning so that we don't
lunes por la mañana para que no nos
let's find out and give the 240 bucks to the
enteremos y le da los 240 pavos a la
association what they say to each other
asociación qué es lo que se dicen entre
they are the little team when they play
ellos el equipito cuando se juegan
when I know when I know a
cuando se cuando se un
Tampa, how good that the Peppa thing is happening
Tampa qué bueno que lo de la Peppa se le
has forgotten but has already paid for it
ha olvidado pero que ya la ha pagado que
There is nothing left to blame him for
ya no hay nada que echarle en cara que
You already paid for it, you know, and it's like nothing.
ya la ha pagado sabes y es comoes nada
among themselves they come together to look for the
entre ellos se juntan para buscar el
support you know the support of those affected by
apoyo sabes el apoyo de afectados por
by
por
Javi, to me it seems like real cinema, I
Javi a mí me parece cine de verdad yo os
I promise these are people
prometo que estos son gente
that I don't hire them, eh, that they are
que que yo no las contrato eh que son
So
así
how how how how
cómo cómo cómo cómo
luare Just say
luare Just say
Item
it
aj gata giving low blows To rebor what
aj gata dando golpes bajos A rebor qué
surprise the truth And if it is more than obvious
sorpresa la verdad Y si es más que obvio
that the orange cat has it as a
que el gato naranja lo tiene como un
object to me
objeto a mí me
They told me
dijeron a mí me
They told us to prepare the channels
dijeron que nos preparemos los canales
of gossip is worth it yes
de salseo vale si
finally the break that has been
finalmente la ruptura que se ha
confirmed I confirmed it let's see I know it
confirmado la confirmé yo a ver yo la sé
for a long time but I confirmed yesterday the
desde hace tiempo pero confirmé ayer la
breakup because it was already a very very thing
ruptura porque ya era una cosa muy muy
You know, definitely, things have already gotten better.
definitiva sabes Ya se ha puesto la cosa
chunga You've already seen the cat, not a little bit.
chunga Ya visteis a gata no un poquito
special not there in those tiktok that
especial no ahí en esos tiktok que
You saw then what I saw
visteis entonces la a mí lo que me
They said it was people close to them who prepared them
dijeron fue gente cercana prepararon los
gossip channels Because these two are going to
canales de salseo Porque estos dos va a
give is going to give cinema okay or so this is a
dar va a dar cine vale o sea esto es una
conversation about who will do it cat and
conversación de quién lo har gata y
They left Rebor, it's not the first time
rebor lo dejaron no es la primera vez
that they left it already happened at the end of April
que lo dejan ya pasó a finales de abril
but they returned then spent a small
pero volvieron luego pasaron una pequeña
crisis in August but it was fixed ago
crisis en agosto pero se arregló hace
a few weeks they left the cat out with
unas semanas lo dejaron gata salió con
your friends to
sus amigos para
I know how to renew myself because I am close to one
renovarse lo sé porque soy cercano a uno
of her friends but I don't like her so
de sus amigos pero ella no me agrada Así
I don't care what happens, she says.
que me da igual lo que pase ella dice
that he left it and has paid that account
que lo dejó y le ha pagado a esa cuenta
of gossip to publish it To whom to
de salseo para que lo publique A quién a
to fay who has paid fy fay has
a fay que le ha pagado a fy fay lo ha
I am delighted that I am
hecho encantadísima es que se me
He went ahead, fy, eh, he got ahead of me there
adelantó fy eh se me adelantó ahí
while we were live eh
mientras que estábamos en directo eh
[Music]
[Música]
In addition to that he has been sending
em Además de que ha estado mandando
information to gossip channels through
información a canales de salseo a través
of her friend mew mods as well as others
de sus mod amiga mew además de otros
Mods Also he is speaking very badly of
Mods Además está hablando muy mal de
rebor to the point of even contacting friends
rebor al grado de contactar hasta amigos
personal to say that rebor is doing it
personales para decir que rebor la está
harassing and making yourself look like the victim
acosando y hacer ver como la víctima
I have been told something similar
esto a mí me han contado algo parecido
but well no
pero bueno no
so much of which is a half-truth because
tanto lo cual es una verdad media porque
Rebot received some important information
rebot recibió una información importante
and now he realized many things
y ahora se dio cuenta de muchas cosas
even well-known people will come out muddied
incluso saldrá gente conocida embarrada
because this is something very strong that more
porque esto es algo muy fuerte que más
one will fall from where they have it
de uno se va a caer de donde lo tienen
It is not my place to give names, I do not want to
no me corresponde dar nombres no quiero
legal problems but there is talk of theft
problemas legales pero se habla de robo
of accounts and information So cat already
de cuentas e información Así que gata ya
He is giving low blows in rebor but still
está dando golpes bajos a rebor pero aún
so he was in love with what
así él sí estaba enamorado por lo que
My friend says that the boy had it in him
dice mi amigo es que al chaval la tenía
As a queen she fought with friends and even worse
como reina peleó con amigos y peor aún
with his family this is true this is it
con su familia esto es verdad esto lo
I commented more or less yesterday not like that
comenté yo más o menos ayer no como que
He is super excited and he is very
él está super enchochado y que está muy
hurt and crying for all the
dolido y que está llorando por todas las
corners In fact he is crying with his
esquinas De hecho está llorando con sus
friends, okay, he's crying and all that stuff
amigos vale va llorando y todo el rollo
that and and she doesn't she is the one who says no
ese y y ella no ella es que dice que no
it fills her that it doesn't fill her that she
le llena que no le llena que ella se
He expected something else from his life with reverence
esperaba otra cosa de su vida con rebor
his grandmother is worth as much as his father
vale tanto su abuela como el padre los
brothers have said they can't stand her
hermanos han dicho que no la soportan
even his brother had a strong
incluso su hermano tuvo una fuerte se
fight with cat and rebor supported her
pelea con gata y rebor la apoyó les
I tell you this. You know if you put it or
cuento esto ustedes Saben si lo ponen o
No, but Cat is going to take advantage of this.
no pero gata va a sacar provecho de esto
since they have no idea and it's not going to happen
como no tienen idea y no le va a
return a cat no no no no no no no no
devolver un gato no no no no no no no no
no pet story care eh In
no historia de mascota cuidado eh En
breakups
rupturas
eh pet story be careful that the
eh historia de mascotas cuidado que las
the devil loads
carga el [__]
eh but he doesn't mention me But okay okay
eh pero no me menciona Pero bueno bueno
a little exact one that we have taken out
un exactito que nos hemos sacado no
places he doesn't mention to me Let's see when he says
lugares no me menciona A ver cuando dice
a gossip account that paid him a
una cuenta de salseo que le pagó una
gossip account so that it is reported no
cuenta de salseo para que se chive no
so that he can tell it, he is referring to
para que lo cuente se está refiriendo a
Fay who was the first to do so
fay que fue la primera que lo
tweeted okay I understand I don't know I understand
tuiteó vale entiendo no lo sé entiendo
I don't know in the end the T that I put
no lo sé al final el T que yo puse
It hasn't had that much impact either.
tampoco ha tenido tanta repercusión no
238,000 being such an exclusive
238.000 siendo una exclusiva así
m being an exclusive like this is not much
m siendo una exclusiva así no es mucho
no I mean it's not a No it hasn't been a
no O sea no es una No no ha sido un
true gossip that no one has done
salseo verdad al que nadie haya hecho
much attention
mucho caso
not lately that I gave the channels of
no últimamente que di los canales de
gossip says no
salseo dicen no
and there are missing topics and it's like, topics yes
e faltan temas y es como o sea temas sí
What happens is that the issues are
que hay lo que pasa es que los temas al
final pa are commented in a pl and and out
final pa se comentan en un pl y y fuera
That is, today, for example, everyone is here
o sea hoy por ejemplo está todo el mundo
talking about Dallas encouragement trying to
hablando de Dallas nimo intentando que
blow up yours from Dallas No that's going away
explote los suyo de Dallas No eso se va
that's already it and it's going to have a bit of it
eso ya lo y va a tener un poco a lo
better more tomorrow since I'm commenting on it
mejor más mañana que lo estoy comentando
Me today but that's tomorrow morning and a half
Yo hoy pero eso ya mañana mañana y medio
tomorrow and a half or so on top of that he catches the
mañana y medio o sea encima pilla el
Saturday no Saturday Saturday nobody is
sábado no el sábado sábado nadie está
talking about c aldala they have it
hablando de c aldala lo hayan
condemned And that is what happens that the
condenado Y es que es lo que pasa que la
people it is already complicated for them
gente ya es complicado que le
fill it is already complicated to fill it
llene ya es complicado que le llene un
gossip something powerful has to happen
chisme ya tiene que pasar algo potente
[Music]
[Música]
HM so that people care
HM para que a la gente le importe a
something and here we leave the live of
algo y por aquí dejamos el directo de
Today family, tomorrow I remind you that Fran
hoy familia mañana recordaros que Fran
is doing its is that I don't know what time
está haciendo su es que no sé a qué hora
But well, stay tuned, I understand.
pero bueno estaros pendientes entiendo
that everyone follows Fran de los
que todo el mundo seguí a Fran de los
that you are here is fine but stay
que estáis aquí vale pero estaros
earrings because tomorrow is going to be a
pendientes porque mañana va a ser un
live video of Dallas from How Good
directo vídeo de Dallas de Qué bueno
Well, come on, go to the Dallas video.
Pues venga iros al vídeo de Dallas
and tomorrow Fran is going to be live
e mañana Fran va a ser un directo
commenting not showing his game to see
comentando no enseñando su juego a ver
as
cómo
Hey, what are you doing?
juega Oye pero esto que están haciendo
Uncle Shur and the S react to a
el tío shur y el s de reaccionar a un
such Spartacus what the [ __ ] is he
tal Espartaco qué [__] es lo
but sh how many channels are you going to
que pero sh Cuántos canales te vas a
make your
hacer su
reacts But this for
reacciona Pero esto por
how sh reacts to the success of the fall of
qué sh reacciona al éxito de la caída de
dala sh reacts
dala sh reacciona
the mother who gave birth to him
la madre que lo parió
Hey, it's gone up
eh dala que ha subido
Okay, no, nothing appears to me.
dala Ah no a mí no me aparece nada
new good chill Okay huh
nuevo bueno chill Vale eh
Guys, see you tomorrow, I love you so much.
chicos nos vemos mañana os quiero mucho
Rest well, I'm going to record a video.
Que descanséis Vale Voy a grabar vídeo
on the main channel and you will have it
en el canal principal y lo tendréis
tomorrow ok One
mañana ok Un
big kiss boo
besote bu